<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>slcli on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/slcli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in slcli on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/slcli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Threads for improved API performance</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/mtSpeedup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/mtSpeedup/</guid>
      <description>Basic of Threads If you are unfamiliar with Threads, these examples will use the concurrent.futures library within python (available after python3.2) which is fairly simple to get setup. I wont really go over HOW it works on a technical level, only how to best use it threads to improve performance when making SoftLayer API requests.&#xA;For some technical details on how python handles Threads the following are good reading on the topic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Golang Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-go project homepage. Contains the source code for the library, and a place to submit feature requests and bug reports Golang Example Library A collection of examples on how to use softlayer-go to work with the SL API. IBMCLOUD SL contains the source code for the ibmcloud sl command, any issues with that plugin should be reported to the github page. Authentication The first thing we need to do before making API calls, is setup our authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Python Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-python project homepage. For source code and submitting issues. Documentation Covers both the SLCLI and softlayer-python library. PyPi project For latest information about the softlayer-python package, which is kept updated on PyPi. Python 2.7 Support As of version 5.8.0 SoftLayer-Python will no longer support python2.7, which is End Of Life as of 2020 . If you cannot install python 3.6+ for some reason, you will need to use a version of softlayer-python &amp;lt;= 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and building an order using the Softlayer order CLI</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering/</guid>
      <description>In version 5.4.0 of softlayer-python, there is a new slcli command for placing IaaS cloud server orders using the API. This command can also be used to place orders for products that are normally ordered through the IBM Cloud infrastructure customer portal. There are multiple helpers to assist you in creating a specific order. In these examples, you will learn how to:&#xA;Build an order Understand the order structure Search for server packages Identify categories of items Verify the order Place the order Place an order programmatically using Python.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSI Flavors</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vsiflavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vsiflavors/</guid>
      <description>The introduction of Flavors to VSI ordering significantly changes how VSIs are ordered, and the old style of ordering will eventually become unsupported. This page will hopefully explain what changes need to be made to any scripts that order VSIs.&#xA;Support for flavors has been added to the SLCLI, so make sure you have at least version 5.4.0.&#xA;Getting a Flavor List SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getCreateObjectOptions is where you can find out the flavor listing, along with all other options you might want to supply to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
