<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Slcli on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/slcli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Slcli on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/tags/slcli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and building an order using the Softlayer order CLI</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/understanding-ordering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/understanding-ordering/</guid>
      <description>In version 5.4.0 of softlayer-python, there is a new slcli command for placing IaaS cloud server orders using the API. This command can also be used to place orders for products that are normally ordered through the IBM Cloud infrastructure customer portal. There are multiple helpers to assist you in creating a specific order. In these examples, you will learn how to:
 Build an order  Understand the order structure Search for server packages Identify categories of items Verify the order Place the order  Place an order programmatically using Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSI Flavors</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/VSIFlavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/VSIFlavors/</guid>
      <description>The introduction of Flavors to VSI ordering significantly changes how VSIs are ordered, and the old style of ordering will eventually become unsupported. This page will hopefully explain what changes need to be made to any scripts that order VSIs.
Support for flavors has been added to the SLCLI, so make sure you have at least version 5.4.0.
Getting a Flavor List SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getCreateObjectOptions is where you can find out the flavor listing, along with all other options you might want to supply to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>