<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>article on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in article on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VLAN Trunking</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vlanTrunking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vlanTrunking/</guid>
      <description>Basics of VLAN Trunking Trunking VLANs allows you to enable bare metal servers that are in the same POD, but on different primary VLANs, to be able to communicate as if they were on the same VLAN. So if you have Server1 on VLAN1, and Server2 on VLAN2 (in the same POD), you could trunk VLAN2 to Server1&amp;rsquo;s switch port allowing Server1 to communicate on VLAN2.&#xA;This article will explain how to do that with the CLI and API tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threads for improved API performance</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/mtSpeedup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/mtSpeedup/</guid>
      <description>Basic of Threads If you are unfamiliar with Threads, these examples will use the concurrent.futures library within python (available after python3.2) which is fairly simple to get setup. I wont really go over HOW it works on a technical level, only how to best use it threads to improve performance when making SoftLayer API requests.&#xA;For some technical details on how python handles Threads the following are good reading on the topic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step By Step Ordering</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/step_by_step_ordering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/step_by_step_ordering/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer Catalog API Video Slides </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events and Notifications</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Events/</guid>
      <description>The Basics There are two types of Events that the SoftLayer API deals with.&#xA;Maintenance Events These are the Classic Infrastructure Planned, Unplanned and Announcement events in the portal. These events DO NOT include other cloud.ibm.com services and notifications. ONLY classic infrastructure.&#xA;Monitoring Events These are the Hardware and Virtual monitoring events that will let you know if a server has gone down/up.&#xA;From the API perspective, these are two separate things, but we will talk about them both in this article since both events can trigger an email alert that we will want to configure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the softlayer-go library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/go/the_go_library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/go/the_go_library/</guid>
      <description>The Basics The softlayer-go library helps users make API calls to the SoftLayer (aka IBM Cloud Classic Infrastructure) API.&#xA;To get started, here is a simple example.&#xA;(We are working in the go/src/github.ibm.com/SoftLayer/sl-test directory for these examples) This file will be main.go&#xA;1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 package main import ( &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; &amp;#34;github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deprecation</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/deprecated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/deprecated/</guid>
      <description>As of the publication of this article, SLDN will now highlight areas of the API that are deprecated in red. These features still exist, but will usually not actually do anything, and will be removed in a future version of the API.&#xA;Deprecated features will usually still return the same type of data, but with a placeholder values instead of valid data. For example a property that returned an array of objects might now just return an empty array ([]), or a boolean might just return false at all times now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Golang Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-go project homepage. Contains the source code for the library, and a place to submit feature requests and bug reports Golang Example Library A collection of examples on how to use softlayer-go to work with the SL API. IBMCLOUD SL contains the source code for the ibmcloud sl command, any issues with that plugin should be reported to the github page. Authentication The first thing we need to do before making API calls, is setup our authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Python Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-python project homepage. For source code and submitting issues. Documentation Covers both the SLCLI and softlayer-python library. PyPi project For latest information about the softlayer-python package, which is kept updated on PyPi. Python 2.7 Support As of version 5.8.0 SoftLayer-Python will no longer support python2.7, which is End Of Life as of 2020 . If you cannot install python 3.6+ for some reason, you will need to use a version of softlayer-python &amp;lt;= 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching with the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/softlayer_search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/softlayer_search/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The SoftLayer_Search service is only available in v3.1 of the API. You will get a &amp;ldquo;Service does not exist&amp;rdquo; error if you use v3&#xA;The SoftLayer_Search is an API service that lets you make complex queries about data indexed by the service. While most of the SoftLayer API is contained in a SQL database, the SoftLayer_Search service uses an Elastic Search database to generate its results, allowing for more complex and responsive queries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessing your Virtual Guest Console</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/virtual_guest_kvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/virtual_guest_kvm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Management</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Users/</guid>
      <description>Hierarchy Each account will have a &amp;ldquo;Master&amp;rdquo; user. This &amp;ldquo;Master&amp;rdquo; user is the main user for the account, considered the account owner, and can do anything possible for an account. This user is a bit special, in that it needs no permissions set, as it has them all. So when looking at permissions set for this user, you will notice that none are set, which is normal for this specific type of user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the SoftLayer API slides&#xA;Welcome to SLDN, the home of the documentation for the SoftLayer, or IBM Classic Infrastructure, API. Here you can find a collection of Articles that cover some of the core concepts in details, Reference Documentation which is the automatically generated API specifications and documentation, and also a collection of examples in a variety of programming languages like Golang, Python, and Java&#xA;Before You Start Choosing a Protocol SoftLayer&amp;rsquo;s API can be accessed by SOAP, XML-RPC, or REST.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandwidth</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/bandwidth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/bandwidth/</guid>
      <description>Bandwidth Any device directly connected to the network will have its bandwidth tracked. This includes Hardware_Server, Virtual_Guest, Hardware_Firewall, and Network_Vlan_Firewall objects. We collect the data periodically from the switch port (or virtual port in the case of Virutal_Guests) and store it in our Metric_Tracking datastore. To interact with this raw data it is required to use the Metric_Tracking_Object service directly, as it wont be possible to pull in this information using a normal objectMask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basic and Advanced Ordering</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering-basics/</guid>
      <description>The Catalog Before we can order anything, we need a list of the valid price IDs that represent our order. This article on The Catalog will explain how to retrieve those. Always remember that the price ID that represents a specific item can change at any time, without notice, but the item&amp;rsquo;s KeyName will not. So it is always important before submitting an order to lookup the item keynames to fine the current price ID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Catalog</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/catalog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/catalog/</guid>
      <description>Packages The first step in ordering is to find the appropriate SoftLayer_Product_Package for what you need to order. These packages contain a varierty of items that will describe the order. Each of those items will have properties that define where it can be ordered, how much it costs, and any restrictions needed to order the item.&#xA;SoftLayer_Product_Package::getAllObject() is used to get a list of all packages.&#xA;Curl Example $ curl -s -g -u $SL_USER:$SL_APIKEY &amp;#39;https://api.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Infrastructure Networking</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/Networking/</guid>
      <description>POPs and PODs A Point Of Presence (POP) refers to the networking equipment responsible for handling traffic from The Internet and customer Direct Links. Each POP is connected to at least two others on our backend network&#xA;A Point of Delivery (POD) is a segmentation of our physical datacenters. Each POP will service several POD, although some POPs are standalone. These PODs are generally recognizable by their router in the datacenter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer API 101 Presentation</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/apiTraining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/apiTraining/</guid>
      <description>API 101 SoftLayer API: Getting Started SoftLayer API: Object Masks SoftLayer API: Object Filters </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billing and Invoices</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/billing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/billing/</guid>
      <description>Getting Invoices Everything that will be charged to your total balance will appear on an invoice, of which there are three main type.&#xA;To get the total balance on your account, simply use SoftLayer_Account::getBalance.&#xA;curl -u $SL_USER:$SL_APIKEY &amp;#39;https://api.softlayer.com/rest/v3.1/SoftLayer_Account/getBalance.json&amp;#39; NEW Anything that is newly ordered will appear as a NEW type invoice. After the billing cycle ends, these will roll into the RECURRING type of invoice.&#xA;RECURRING Usually each month you will have one recurring invoice, containing everything that was billed to the account, outside of any charges that appear on NEW and ONE-TIME-CHARGE invoices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exception Handling in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/exception-handling-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/exception-handling-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Like any programming interface the SoftLayer API at times needs to return error messages to its users. The SoftLayer API brings these exceptions forward to the user so their application can handle the unexpected result. Exceptions are returned as SOAP, REST, or XML-RPC faults depending on the RPC method used to execute your API method call. Programming and scripting languages with SOAP and XML-RPC support usually have built-in methods for handling faults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Account Billing Detail</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/single-account-billing-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/single-account-billing-detail/</guid>
      <description>Account Level Billing This tutorial walks you through accessing detailed billing data for a single specified account using a specified time and date range.&#xA;Objectives Understand how to use multiple API services and methods to access detailed billing data for a specified account using a specified time and date range. Services used This tutorial uses the following technologies:&#xA;SoftLayer Python Library Billing_Invoice Service Billing_Invoice_Item Service Billing_item Service Architecture This tutorial will leverage account Invoice and Billing Item API&amp;rsquo;s to collect and display detailed billing detail for a specified time and date range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Block Storage</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/AutomatingStorage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/AutomatingStorage/</guid>
      <description>The Process Order a VSI with a postInstall script Order a storage volume Update the metadata of the VSI to include the needed information to mount the storage volume postInstall script gets metadata from the metadata service, and mounts the volume Ordering Code This script will order a VSI, based on a configuration in the file, then order some storage, authorize storage to the new VSI, and set the VSI&amp;rsquo;s metadata with the needed information for it to be mounted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-Organization Billing Detail</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/sub-org-billing-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/sub-org-billing-detail/</guid>
      <description>Sub-org Billing Detail This tutorial walks you through accessing the steps required to access detailed billing data across sub-organization accounts using a specified date and time range.&#xA;Objectives Understand how to use multiple API services and methods to access detailed billing data for all sub organization accounts for a specified time and date range.&#xA;Services used This tutorial uses the following technologies:&#xA;SoftLayer Python Library Account Service Billing_Invoice Service Billing_Invoice_Item Service Billing_item Service Architecture Accounts (refered to in this document as a sub account) can be owned by a Brand Account, which is the top level account type for an organization which can enable sub-organizational level billing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and building an order using the Softlayer order CLI</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/understanding-ordering/</guid>
      <description>In version 5.4.0 of softlayer-python, there is a new slcli command for placing IaaS cloud server orders using the API. This command can also be used to place orders for products that are normally ordered through the IBM Cloud infrastructure customer portal. There are multiple helpers to assist you in creating a specific order. In these examples, you will learn how to:&#xA;Build an order Understand the order structure Search for server packages Identify categories of items Verify the order Place the order Place an order programmatically using Python.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSI Flavors</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vsiflavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/vsiflavors/</guid>
      <description>The introduction of Flavors to VSI ordering significantly changes how VSIs are ordered, and the old style of ordering will eventually become unsupported. This page will hopefully explain what changes need to be made to any scripts that order VSIs.&#xA;Support for flavors has been added to the SLCLI, so make sure you have at least version 5.4.0.&#xA;Getting a Flavor List SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getCreateObjectOptions is where you can find out the flavor listing, along with all other options you might want to supply to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLDN Articles</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-Filters</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/object-filters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/object-filters/</guid>
      <description>Overview slides&#xA;Object filters can be used to limit the results returned by the API. They differ from objectMasks in that they determine which objects are returned while objectMasks define what properties to retrieve from the returned objects.&#xA;Structure An object filter is created by defining a property hierarchy through the relational and local properties. The property to be filtered will be a structure that represents the object filters conditional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Solve: Error fetching http headers</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/how-solve-error-fetching-http-headers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/how-solve-error-fetching-http-headers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Error Fetching http headers&amp;quot; is a common error to encounter when working with the SLAPI. Fortunately, it is not terribly difficult to avoid. This error most commonly met when working with a large sets of data and can be a bit cryptic, as it seems to imply some sort of connection issue. In truth, it is a client side error provided when a timeout occurs while waiting for a response from the API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-Masks</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/object-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/object-masks/</guid>
      <description>Overview slides&#xA;In order to obtain relational data from an object in the API you must declare an object mask in your API call. With standard object masks, relational data is pulled using a SOAP header, an XML-RPC struct or a GET parameter in REST.&#xA;Extended object masks make use of a Domain-specific language to reduce the effort required to express what data should be returned from the API. In order to support this new method of object mask, a new input method has been added to each protocol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSL Management</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/ssl-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/ssl-management/</guid>
      <description>3/14/2012: Added the ability to provide SSL offloading to the local Load Balancing service in Softlayer. The load balancing service allows you to manage the offload capability, as well as, access the SSL certificate manager. In order to utilize SSL offloading, a load balancer must be purchased that offers the capability.&#xA;The SoftLayer_Security_Certificate service provides access to the new certificate manager. There are no restrictions on the number or origin of certificates, so please feel free to use it as a centralized storage location for all of your SSL certificates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP in Perl</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/implementing-soap-perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/implementing-soap-perl/</guid>
      <description>Since writing this guide we&#39;ve created a Perl specific implementation and manual page. Check them out!&#xA;Our Perl SOAP API examples perform simple retrieval operations and output results to your Perl console. We use the SOAP::Lite Perl module to handle generating our SOAP headers, generating our SOAP request, then interpreting the result from the method call. Each of these examples execute a single method call to retrieve its data. We&#39;ll start out with a simple direct call, implement an object mask, then combine the two.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authenticating to the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/authenticating-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/authenticating-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>IBMid IBMid is how access is managed across IBM&amp;rsquo;s cloud platform. Basically it is the email and password you use to login to https://cloud.ibm.com . Once IBMid can have access to multiple accounts. For accessing Classic Infrastructure (AKA SoftLayer) services, this IBMid will have a SoftLayer user on each account they have access to.&#xA;IAM Documentation: IAM API API Keys for Services User Management SoftLayer Username and API key To authenticate with a SoftLaye username and APIkey, you will first need your accounts username.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C Sharp</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/c-sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/c-sharp/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&amp;nbsp; Consuming SOAP WSDLs Creating Web References Using wsdl.exe Making API Calls Creating Service Objects Binding Authentication Setting Initialization Parameters Using Object Masks Using Result Limits Error Handling Caveats Setting &#34;Specified&#34; Properties What to do When API Services Change Referenced API Components Services Data Types Methods External Links Consuming SOAP WSDLs There are two ways to import SoftLayer&#39;s API WSDLs into your project. Visual Studio can consume a SOAP service into a web reference accessible by your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Date Handling in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/date-handling-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/date-handling-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Most of the data presented in the SoftLayer API is date-sensitive. Servers have provision dates, tickets have modify dates, and nearly everything has a creation date. To maintain compliancy and consistency standards for all of our users worldwide, SoftLayer presents its dates in [http://www.iso.org/iso/date_and_time_format ISO 8601] format under the data type &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;dateTime&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;. ISO 8601 represents a complete date including date, time and time zone. Every data type property in the SoftLayer API that ends with the string &amp;ldquo;Date&amp;rdquo; is represented by the &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;dateTime&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legacy Object Masks</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/legacy-object-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/legacy-object-masks/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&amp;nbsp; Structure Creating an Object Mask Referenced API Components Services Data Types Internal Links Most of the data types modeled in the SoftLayer API contain relational properties that tie one data type to another. For instance, a SoftLayer_Account has links to its domains, support tickets, hardware, users, and much more. By default, calling the [[SoftLayer_Account]] service&#39;s getObject method won&#39;t retrieve relational and count properties. In order to retrieve this information, you would have to call getUsers, getTickets, and other methods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERL</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/perl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/perl/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&amp;nbsp; Making API Calls Using Object Masks Using Result Limits Error Handling Referenced API Components Services Data Types Methods External Links SoftLayer provides a Perl-based API client that takes the heavy lifting out of making manual SOAP API calls. To use this API client, the following system requirements must be met:&#xA;Perl 5.6 or higher SOAP::Lite XML::Hash::LX Download the SoftLayer Perl API client from its project page on SoftLayer’s github profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Permission Enforcement in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/permission-enforcement-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/permission-enforcement-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>The SoftLayer API is built around the same system of user permissions that power the SoftLayer customer portal. What the API exposes and allows depends on the user&amp;rsquo;s account that is making the call and that user&amp;rsquo;s permission set. Your account&amp;rsquo;s master user has full permissions to every service and method associated with your account. Please be wary if you choose to execute API method calls using your account&amp;rsquo;s master user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHP</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/php/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides a PHP-based API client that takes the heavy lifting out making manual SOAP or XML-RPC calls. To use the PHP-based API client, the following system requirements must be met:&#xA;PHP 5.2.3 or higher One of the following PHP extensions: SOAP XML-RPC Download the SoftLayer PHP API client from its project page on SoftLayer&#39;s github profile. Once downloaded, extract the PHP API Client to a directory local to your PHP project or into your PHP installation&#39;s include_path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/rest/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides a RESTful API in addition to RPC-style API services. Use the REST API in cases where your programming language may not have good SOAP or XML-RPC support but can perform simple HTTP protocol actions and can interpret XML or JSON data.&#xA;REST URLs REST API URLs are structured to easily traverse SoftLayer&amp;rsquo;s object hierarchy. A basic REST request is structured as follows:&#xA;curl -u [username]:[apiKey] -d &amp;#39;{&amp;#34;parameters&amp;#34;: [&amp;#34;first&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;second&amp;#34;]}&amp;#39; https://api.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/ruby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/ruby/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&amp;nbsp; Making API Calls Authentication Calling Service Methods Identifying Particular Objects Using Object Masks Error Handling Referenced API Components Services Data Types Methods External Links The Ruby client is available as the softlayer_api Ruby gem. On most systems, the command:&#xA;gem install softlayer_api installs the gem and makes it available to Ruby scripts. Where the gem is installed on your computer will depend on your particular distribution of Ruby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/soap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/soap/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides a SOAP interface in addition to XML-RPC and REST. We recommend using the SOAP API, as it is the most comprehensive API that we currently offer.&#xA;WSDL URLs and Files The SoftLayer SOAP API has one endpoint per available API service. Each endpoint has a unique URL containing the service name of the API service that it calls. For example: https://api.softlayer.com/soap/v3/&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt;?wsdl or http://api.service.softlayer.com/soap/v3/&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt;?wsdl&#xA;In these examples, &amp;quot;&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt;&amp;quot; would be replaced with the name of the API services you wish to call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Initialization Parameters in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-initialization-parameters-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-initialization-parameters-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&#xA;Structure Creating an Initialization Parameter SOAP XML-RPC REST Exceptions to the Rule Parameters Optional Headers Prior to calling methods on some objects represented in the SoftLayer API, a unique identifier must be used during instantiation of the service. SoftLayer provides a way to instantiate your service objects by passing the service&amp;rsquo;s initialization parameter in the header of your API calls. Once this action is complete, all methods following this header will be directed to the method containing the initialization parameter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Result Limits in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Many of the methods in the SoftLayer API return arrays of data types. In these cases it may be useful to limit the number of results that the API retrieves from your method call. Fortunately SoftLayer provides an easy way to accomplish this via a method analogous to the SQL LIMIT statement that you can apply in the header of your method calls. Result limits are optional for all method calls, and a method&amp;rsquo;s manual page states whether or not it can use a result limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Basic .NET</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/visual-basic-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/visual-basic-net/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents&amp;nbsp; Consuming SOAP WSDLs Creating Web References Using Wsdl.exe Making API Calls Creating Service Objects Binding Authentication Setting Initialization Parameters Making the API Call Using Object Masks Using Result Limits Error Handling Caveats Setting &#34;Specified&#34; Properties What to do When API Services Change Referenced API Components Services Data Types Methods External Links Consuming SOAP WSDLs There are two ways to import SoftLayer&#39;s API WSDLs into your project. Visual Studio can consume a SOAP service into a web reference accessible by your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XML-RPC</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/xml-rpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/xml-rpc/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides an XML-RPC interface in addition to SOAP and REST. The XML-RPC API is built to mimic the SOAP interface. We recommend using the XML-RPC API when your chosen language doesn&amp;rsquo;t have proper SOAP support.&#xA;Endpoint URLs The SoftLayer XML-RPC API has one endpoint per available API service. Each endpoint has a unique URL containing the service name of the API services that it calls. For example: https://api.softlayer.com/xmlrpc/v3/&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt; or http://api.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
