<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>API Reference</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/softlayerapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/softlayerapi/</guid>
      <description>In effort to extend SoftLayers dedication to automation to our customers and partners, we have provided this set of APIs to interact with all of our products. The APIs listed below will be your programmatic access point for integrate with your SoftLayer services. Our customer portal was built on top of the same API set we provide to our customers and is a great example of the tasks which can be performed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer ObjectStorage API</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/objectstorageapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/objectstorageapi/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer Object Storage is built from Open Stack Swift</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Storage Uploader</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/python/swiftUploader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/python/swiftUploader/</guid>
      <description>Overview We’ve recently added the option to import customer-supplied Virtual Hard Disks (VHDs) to our object storage offering. This is a great option for our customers who may have special virtual machines that they have spent hours perfecting. Since learning to import these images can pose a slight challenge, especially for those unfamiliar with object storage (OpenStack Swift), I wrote this blog to share scripts that will streamline the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Cloud for AWS professionals</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tools/compareorator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/tools/compareorator/</guid>
      <description>IBM Cloud for AWS professionals This article will hopefully help anyone coming from the AWS ecosystem translate their workloads into IBM Cloud.
Basic Concepts IBM Cloud has three main silos. Infrastructure , Applications , and Services.
Infrastructure is built on SoftLayer and is available in over 30 SoftLayer Datacenters across the world. All of which are interconnect with our unmetered private network.
Applications can be either Cloud Foundry, Docker, or Open Whisk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tools/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/tools/tools/</guid>
      <description>Bluemix for AWS professionals A general comparison between Bluemix products and AWS or Azure products. With some comments to point out the key differences.
Ansible Ansible offers an agentless way to administer your servers and is a great way to quickly make changes across your infrastructure.
Vagrant Vagrant allows for development environments to be configured in consistent ways and can provision SoftLayer servers as part of the environment creation process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/python/</guid>
      <description>toc_collapse=0;Table of contents&amp;nbsp;  Python Making API Calls Using Object Masks Using Result Limits Error Handling Managers More Resources    Python SoftLayer, an IBM company, provides a Python-based API package that takes the heavy lifting out of making manual XML-RPC API calls. Our Python-based API requires a minimum of Python 2.6 To install the Python package into your Python installation’s site-packages directory, run the following command:

pip install softlayer</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>