<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tools on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tools on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Golang Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/golang/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-go project homepage. Contains the source code for the library, and a place to submit feature requests and bug reports Golang Example Library A collection of examples on how to use softlayer-go to work with the SL API. IBMCLOUD SL contains the source code for the ibmcloud sl command, any issues with that plugin should be reported to the github page. Authentication The first thing we need to do before making API calls, is setup our authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Python Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-python project homepage. For source code and submitting issues. Documentation Covers both the SLCLI and softlayer-python library. PyPi project For latest information about the softlayer-python package, which is kept updated on PyPi. Python 2.7 Support As of version 5.8.0 SoftLayer-Python will no longer support python2.7, which is End Of Life as of 2020 . If you cannot install python 3.6+ for some reason, you will need to use a version of softlayer-python &amp;lt;= 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBMCloud CLI</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/ibmcloudcli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/ibmcloudcli/</guid>
      <description>IBMCloud is a Golang project used to interact with everything on cloud.ibm.com. Inside that command is a sub-command called ibmcloud sl which is a port of the SLCLI, and includes many of the features slcli does.&#xA;Links IBMCloud Install IBMCloud Bug Report IBMCloud Documentation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer  CLI</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/slcli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/slcli/</guid>
      <description>The SoftLayer Command Line Interface (SLCLI) comes as part of the SoftLayer-Pyhton project, and can be easily installed like any other python package by using pip install softlayer.&#xA;Links SoftLayer-Python SLCLI Bug Reports SLCLI Documentation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Reference</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/softlayerapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/softlayerapi/</guid>
      <description>In effort to extend SoftLayers dedication to automation to our customers and partners, we have provided this set of APIs to interact with all of our products. The APIs listed below will be your programmatic access point for integrate with your SoftLayer services. Our customer portal was built on top of the same API set we provide to our customers and is a great example of the tasks which can be performed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Storage Uploader</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/swiftUploader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/swiftUploader/</guid>
      <description>Overview We’ve recently added the option to import customer-supplied Virtual Hard Disks (VHDs) to our object storage offering. This is a great option for our customers who may have special virtual machines that they have spent hours perfecting. Since learning to import these images can pose a slight challenge, especially for those unfamiliar with object storage (OpenStack Swift), I wrote this blog to share scripts that will streamline the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Cloud for AWS professionals</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/compareorator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/compareorator/</guid>
      <description>IBM Cloud for AWS professionals This article will hopefully help anyone coming from the AWS ecosystem translate their workloads into IBM Cloud.&#xA;Basic Concepts IBM Cloud has three main silos. Infrastructure , Applications , and Services.&#xA;Infrastructure is built on SoftLayer and is available in over 30 SoftLayer Datacenters across the world. All of which are interconnect with our unmetered private network.&#xA;Applications can be either Cloud Foundry, Docker, or Open Whisk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer Knife</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/knife-softlayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/knife-softlayer/</guid>
      <description>knife-softlayer Configuration Add your SoftLayer username and API key to your knife.rb file.&#xA;log_level :info log_location STDOUT node_name &amp;#39;node&amp;#39; client_key &amp;#39;/path/to/key.pem&amp;#39; validation_client_name &amp;#39;some-validator&amp;#39; validation_key &amp;#39;/path/to/validator.pem&amp;#39; chef_server_url &amp;#39;https://example.com/organizations/org&amp;#39; syntax_check_cache_path &amp;#39;/path/to/syntax_check_cache&amp;#39; knife[:softlayer_username] = &amp;#34;&amp;lt;SOFTLAYER USERNAME&amp;gt;&amp;#34; knife[:softlayer_api_key] = &amp;#34;&amp;lt;SOFTLAYER API KEY&amp;gt;&amp;#34; Usage See knife softlayer --help for more information.&#xA;EXAMPLES:&#xA;# look at some options user@local&amp;gt; knife softlayer flavor list [--all] # the minimum number of pieces of flare user@local&amp;gt; knife softlayer server create --hostname test --domain example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/tools/</guid>
      <description>Bluemix for AWS professionals A general comparison between Bluemix products and AWS or Azure products. With some comments to point out the key differences.&#xA;Ansible Ansible offers an agentless way to administer your servers and is a great way to quickly make changes across your infrastructure.&#xA;Vagrant Vagrant allows for development environments to be configured in consistent ways and can provision SoftLayer servers as part of the environment creation process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer SDKs</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/softlayer-sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tools/softlayer-sdk/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of language specific bindings for interacting with the SoftLayer API. None of these are strictly required to use the API, but will likely make using the API a lot easier.&#xA;Softlayer-Python This library provides a simple Python client to interact with SoftLayer&amp;rsquo;s XML-RPC or REST API.&#xA;A command-line interface is also included and can be used to manage various SoftLayer products and services.&#xA;SoftLayer-Go This library contains a complete implementation of the SoftLayer API for client application development in the Go programming language.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
