<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debugging on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/debugging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debugging on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/tags/debugging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Order an SSL Certificate</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/python/orderSSLCert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/python/orderSSLCert/</guid>
      <description>Generating a CSR You will need a csr to make this request, it should be on your local file system.
The contents of the CSR MATTER, they need to match the information for what you are ordering. + orderApproverEmailAddress must match the Email Address of the CSR + The CSR Common name must be set and must be a part of the orderApproverEmailAddress
$ openssl genrsa -out domain.key 2048 $ openssl req -new -sha256 -key domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exception Handling in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/exception-handling-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/exception-handling-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Like any programming interface the SoftLayer API at times needs to return error messages to its users. The SoftLayer API brings these exceptions forward to the user so their application can handle the unexpected result. Exceptions are returned as SOAP or XML-RPC faults depending on the RPC method used to execute your API method call. Programming and scripting languages with SOAP and XML-RPC support usually have built-in methods for handling faults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy Object Masks</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/legacy-object-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/legacy-object-masks/</guid>
      <description>toc_collapse=0;Table of contents&amp;nbsp;  Structure Creating an Object Mask Referenced API Components  Services Data Types   Internal Links    Most of the data types modeled in the SoftLayer API contain relational properties that tie one data type to another. For instance, a SoftLayer_Account has links to its domains, support tickets, hardware, users, and much more. By default, calling the [[SoftLayer_Account]] service&amp;rsquo;s getObject method won&amp;rsquo;t retrieve relational and count properties.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>