<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>release notes on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in release notes on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240426/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240426/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed a bug where compute resources added to a pool would enter a state where they could not be added or removed from any pool. Restore the state of allotment details if an SLDN call fails to add allocations after ejecting them NETWORK-14419 Announce deprecation of Network Backbone. Add deprecation tags and monitorUsage to Network Backbone references NETWORK-14415 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 19, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240419/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240419/</guid>
      <description>API Removed Following SLDN Variables and Methods Variables - vSRXVersion from class SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_Member_Attribute. Methods - createObject, createObjects, editObject from class SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_Member. Methods - getAllByUpgradePkgUrlId from class SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_VersionUpgrade. Methods - createObject, editObject, checkAccountWhiteList, isAccountWhiteListed, changeGatewayVersion, getRollbackSupport from class Softlayer_Network_Gateway. Enable new permission checks on Network_Firewall_Update_Request NETWORK-13774 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 12, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240412/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240412/</guid>
      <description>API Allow accounts to self-service conversion to VRF without a support ticket via SoftLayer_Network::enableVrf which will immediately start the process of converting the account to VRF which incurs a backend network connectivity disruption. This action requires NETWORK_VLAN_SPANNING permission.. Introduce Network::enableVrf() NETWORK-14373 Fixed bug where calling getBandwidthList and only having firewalls on the account would result in a &amp;ldquo;Missing device parameter(s)&amp;rdquo; exception. Fix validation for customers who call getBandwidthList that only have firewalls NETWORK-14381 Added new capacity units for software licenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 22, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240322/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240322/</guid>
      <description>API Added new vendor codes for vmware add ons. Create new vendor code for VMWare VCF Addons SOFTWARE-1890 Fix regenerating quotes with default partition template ids &amp;gt; 1 and custom partitions disabled. Failures ordering from quotes with a default partition template and a package that disables custom partitions SALES-14340 Fix for a problem on VSI orders with Windows on other environments outside of commercial.. Account for different default template IDs across environments SALES-14284 Disallow migrating dedicated hosts to non-dedicated hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 01, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240301/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240301/</guid>
      <description>API Removed code which checks if guest is powered off before detaching a vlan. Added new guest attribute type for skipping PV driver checks. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: Feburuary 16, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240216/</guid>
      <description>API Add special characters when generate password for VMWare( this change should apply to ESXi (vSphere) versions 7.0 &amp;amp; later) Deprecation of datatypes and services associated with subnet registrations: SoftLayer_Account_Regional_Registry_Detail_Property_Type SoftLayer_Account_Regional_Registry_Detail_Property SoftLayer_Account_Regional_Registry_Detail_Type SoftLayer_Account_Regional_Registry_Detail SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Details SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Status SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration SoftLayer_Account_Rwhois_Handle SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Event_Type SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Apnic SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Arin SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Ripe SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Event Prevent upgrades from allowing SAN disks added to Local guests </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 19, 2024</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2024/20240119/</guid>
      <description>API Deprecate Domain Name Registration Allow UTF8 characters for VLAN name at order time Improve caching of IAM Token for SoftLayer user. Delete billing item when transaction is manually canceled. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 20, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231220/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231220/</guid>
      <description>API Deprecation of SoftLayer_Account::transcodeAccounts </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 17, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231117/</guid>
      <description>API Prevent the creation of users in the status IamId invalid. New API &amp;ldquo;rename&amp;rdquo; in SoftLayer_Network_Gateway class to update the gateway name. Adds new &amp;ldquo;Canceled&amp;rdquo; status to events. This status will be given to events that are stopped without being completed. Backend Fix issues with order forms causing logouts. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 3, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231103/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231103/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress::findUsage not returning results with customer notes. Renamed the following properties SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_Member_Attribute.vSRXVersion =&amp;gt; version SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_Member_Attribute.lastvSRXVersion =&amp;gt; lastVersion </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 13 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231013/</guid>
      <description>API Update partitions to use the id provided by the software description attribute and fix handling of partitions with multiple volumes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 6 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20231006/</guid>
      <description>API Removed SoftLayer_Hardware::getCustomBandwidthDataByDate, SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::getCustomBandwidthDataByDate and SoftLayer_Hardware::getCustomMetricDataByDate. Please use the SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object API for bandwidth data. Restrict acknowledgeSupportPolicy to only allow a Customer to acknowledge for themselves Backend Fixes a problem with adding users to NON-linked SL accounts that use IBMid. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 18 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230918/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230918/</guid>
      <description>API Removed unused MobileDevice classes Adding LBAAS uuid to SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_UsageDetail::resourceContext Addressed a bug where Global IP Addresses routed to compute resources were errantly reclaimed when the associated compute resource was reclaimed. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 23 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230623/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230623/</guid>
      <description>API Add CoreApi SoftLayer_Network_Service_Resource_Type Improved speed and reliability of bandwidth pool membership mutation methods SoftLayer_Network_Bandwidth_Version1_Allotment::setVdrContents SoftLayer_Network_Bandwidth_Version1_Allotment::requestVdrContentUpdates SoftLayer_Network_Bandwidth_Version1_Allotment::requestVdrCancellation SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getIpAddressUsage and SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::getIpAddressUsage to provide detail on primary IP address assignment. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 12 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230512/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230512/</guid>
      <description>API While authorizing Block volume, code will fetch only block (IscsiGroup) Clusters, so customer won&amp;rsquo;t face issue while authorization Deleting unused API endpoints on the SoftLayer_Network_ContentDelivery_Account class Adding permissions requirements to Ticket Attachment File Class On hardware order containers, primaryDiskPartitionId will be ignored and removed after verify if the order container also has storageGroups. 2/4/10 IOPS/GB tier enabled and 0.25 disabled in order duplicate page Restore SLDN masking for SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::podName. Add for SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::podName.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 28 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230428/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230428/</guid>
      <description>API Fixes an issue where the Refresh Dependent Duplicate PI feature would fail if a snapshot was not found. With this fix, the feature will gracefully handle cases where the snapshot is not available. Improved Error Handling Documentation. Added ability to document permissions for api methods. Add SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::podName Better error handling for modifying storage volumes Fix issue where getUpgradeItemPrices methods would mark some port speed price with currentPriceFlag set to true that were not the current price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 14 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230414/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230414/</guid>
      <description>API New API getGwOrdersAllowedLicenses in SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_VersionUpgrade to get a list of gateway licenses for manufacturer and versions. New API getGwOrdersAllowedOS in SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_VersionUpgrade to get a list per package of price ids for allowed vSRX or vFSA OS-es for new orders. Added an API (SoftLayer_Brand::migrateExternalAccount) to allow enabled brands to migrate an external account into their brand. Backend Reduce the file volume provision time, provisioning will be faster compare to existing time of 60-80 secs Throw an Exception when trying to convert a NAS volume to an independent duplicate </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 17 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230317/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230317/</guid>
      <description>API Remove duplicate host pool member entries Add network card to the schedule new transaction firmware upgrades </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 13 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230313/</guid>
      <description>API Adds the SoftLayer_Product_Item Service Remove all SoftLayer_Scale* classes and references Deprecated unused API endpoints on the Account class Account::getHistoricalTicketGraph Account::getHistoricalBackupGraph Account::getHistoricalUptimeGraph Account::getAggregatedUptimeGraph Account::getDiskUsageMetricImageByDate Account::getDiskUsageMetricDataFromMetricTrackingObjectSystemByDate Account::getDiskUsageMetricDataFromLegacyByDate Account::getAllGroupTicketCountsByTimeframe Account::getDiskUsageMetricDataByDate Account::getHistoricalBandwidthGraph SoftLayer_Network::disconnectPrivateEndpointService and SoftLayer_Network::connectPrivateEndpointService now require the MANAGE_PRIVATE_ENDPOINT_SERVICE permission </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 3 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230303/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230303/</guid>
      <description>API Removing &amp;lsquo;HIPAA_BRIDGE_LETTER&amp;rsquo; option from compliance report request tool and also updating the document delivery statement in the portal. Prevent obsolete Customer Permissions from being added to Customers Adding exceptions and fixing parameter in SendGrid reclaims Add subnet identifier as note to attached billing items. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 10 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230210/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230210/</guid>
      <description>API Improved error message for SoftLayer_Network_Message_Delivery_Email_Sendgrid:deleteEmailListEntries Add force_refres parameter to https://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_Storage/refreshDependentDuplicate/ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 2 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230202/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230202/</guid>
      <description>API Performs a check to see if the user has access to the guest the disk image is attached to before moving it to another guest Adding SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::datacenter Fix term length validation for optional disk categories in order API In rare cases customer would see an error during volume modification. With this code fix the issue will be resolved and the snapshot size modification will go through properly without any issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 13, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230113/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2023/20230113/</guid>
      <description>API VSI bandwidth data will now be accurately presented when no dates are provided to SoftLayer_Account::getBandwidthList Remove all SoftLayer_Scale* services and datatypes Add SoftLayer_Network_Component_Network_Vlan_Trunk::isUpdating to indicate updates to a VLAN trunk are in-progress. Backend Enables vlan and subnet selections for additional private interface products. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221111/</guid>
      <description>Backend Bandwidth Overage notifications now include alerts for Bandwidth Pools approaching their total allocation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 4, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221104/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221104/</guid>
      <description>API Properly handle upgrade rules when block/file volume is magnetic Removed the dead PhoneFactor code Allow for editing a firmware driver version entries Add new guest attribute type for ACTIVE_LIVE_MIGRATION Made the SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::virtualGuests ORM key return an empty collection for customers (SLDN calls), since we no longer offer customer-managed-guests and therefore customers do not need to know host/server information for their guests anymore. Fully deprecated SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::secondaryRouter Backend Fixed an issue where block and file snapshot counts where not accurate </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 21, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20221021/</guid>
      <description>API Reliably populate SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::gateway and broadcastAddress for non-static subnets. Removed PhoneFactor Exceptions and Exception message translations Added validation to Customer rate limit values Allow upgrades to use additional private network interfaces Expose permissionCheckLikeMasterUserFlag to API Backend Fix an issue causing some order verification and order placement to return generic errors from the API. Auto-resume guests when live migration bug occurs that suspends the guest unintentionally Prevent IPSec VPN orders on VRF enabled accounts Fixed multiple bugs/inconsistencies related to parent/child device access violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 9, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220909/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220909/</guid>
      <description>API Do not permit static subnet route requests to target actively re-routing subnets. Change the status to &amp;lsquo;Approved&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;Complete&amp;rsquo; for subnet cancellation requests when the reclaim is yet to complete. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 2, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220902/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220902/</guid>
      <description>API Secondary subnets no longer prevent automatic or premium VLANs from being cancelled and reclaimed. As part of VLAN reclamation, secondary subnets will be unrouted for potential future use. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 26, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220826/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220826/</guid>
      <description>API Removed all guest-related methods from SLDN exposure on the SoftLayer_Virtual_Host class, since customer-managed guests are no longer available as a product and therefore host information is not exposed to customers for their guests. Update volumeStatus as string in case of ISCSI volume Updated SLDN Documentation for SoftLayer_User_Customer_ApiAuthentication to match behavior Deprecate Autoscale for Classic API methods Adding new package names to Sendgrid product items. Clarify 2nd event log entry for IAM Token good with 2FA failure Backend Prefer keeping the same IP addresses when restarting a provision Added code to delete networks after the deletion of provisioning network in SoftLayer_Virtual_Host Unroute static subnets targeting primary IP addresses upon host reclaim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 12, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220812/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220812/</guid>
      <description>API Deprecated the following ORM relations:&#xA;SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::network SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::secondaryRouter Deprecated the following methods:&#xA;SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getFirewallProtectableIpAddresses SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getFirewallProtectableSubnets SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getNetwork SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getPrivateVlan SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getPublicVlanByFqdn SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getReverseDomainRecords SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::getSecondaryRouter SoftLayer_Network_Vlan::updateFirewallIntraVlanCommunication SoftLayer_Hardware::networkStatus / SoftLayer_Hardware::getNetworkStatus() SoftLayer_Hardware::networkStatusAttribute / SoftLayer_Hardware::getNetworkStatusAttribute() SoftLayer_Hardware::downstreamNetworkHardwareWithIncidents / SoftLayer_Hardware::getDownstreamNetworkHardwareWithIncidents() SoftLayer_Hardware_Group::networkStatus SoftLayer_Hardware_Group::downstreamHardwareWithIncidents Updated documentation of SoftLayer_Network_Vlan service and data type.&#xA;Deprecate all customer-managed guest. Information about guests running on customer managed hardware will no longer be available in the API&#xA;Deprecate Host::billedPerGuestFlag and Host::billedPerMemoryUsageFlag&#xA;Deprecated the following SLDN properties and methods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 8, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220708/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220708/</guid>
      <description>API SLDN Documentation added for SoftLayer_User_Customer::getAuthenticationToken &amp;amp; SoftLayer_User_Customer::validateAuthenticationToken Backend Migrate Reserved Capacity Instance when there is an os mismatch </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 24, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220624/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220624/</guid>
      <description>Backend Correctly check for consistent disk types during guest upgrades. Disk types (local/SAN) are more consistently checked when performing upgrades on virtual servers, preventing them from having multiple disk types at a time. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 17, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220617/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220617/</guid>
      <description>API A new orm key in server class that will allow for additional private networks. Backend Fix minor suspendable guest billing issues. Fix IAM login for SL user with IP address restrictions AND 2FA Prevent compute orders in closing DCs when the account has no presence there Lowering subnet size limit to /29 for select VLANs previously limited to /28 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 10, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220610/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220610/</guid>
      <description>API Update link to virtual server capacity documentation. In the SoftLayer_Tag class put a limit on the number of tags in setTags Fix errors when ordering from large quotes Customers can know the progress of a dependent duplicate conversion as and when needed. LBaaS ability to enable secure flag and set same-site=none Updating SoftLayer_User_Customer SLDN documentation for the editObjects call. Improved minimum size overflow error messaging for subnet orders Backend Update email URL link on subnet orders to new subnet page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 27, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220527/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220527/</guid>
      <description>API Expose information about remaining credit, allowing customers to evaluate how much money they can use from a Flex Credit enrollment Added account property length validation Last name: 30 Phone: 50 Address 1 &amp;amp; 2: 100 City: 100 Updated &amp;lsquo;datacenter&amp;rsquo; ORM key in the guest class to use targetDatacenterId property Allow empty array for as the templateObject for SoftLayer_Network_Firewall_Update_Request/createObject/, which will delete all firewall rules. Portal make PhoneFactor feature unavailable in UI </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 20, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220520/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220520/</guid>
      <description>Backend Fix major bugs with suspendable VSI billing for VMs that are unused during the billing cycle Updated description for new vendor code for vmware Added new vendor code for vSphere SWD Enable ordering of Secondary Subnets in unrouted state. Enable ordering of private static Secondary Subnets. Enable ordering of Global IP Addresses in statically routed state. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 12, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220512/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220512/</guid>
      <description>API Adds provision tracking variables: SoftLayer_Provisioning_Version1_Transaction_OrderTracking Add incoming external transaction id(s) to event log for getPortalLoginTokenOpenIdConnect Improved documentation of SoftLayer_Network_Subnet Backend Improve customer tickets for custom image ping check failures Changed ticket wording around emergency host evacuations Enable storage groups to be defined with PCIe drives including Mirrored M.2. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 29, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220429/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220429/</guid>
      <description>API There will be an orm key orderTrackingState on the Transaction class Ensure removal of Permission Resources of a specific device type when adding an ACCESS_ALL_ Permission Improved VLAN cancellation error message Deprecated the extensionRouter key on SoftLayer_Network_Vlan A new API validateAccessHosts was released which checks if an ip is behind gateway or not Backend Fix an issue that prevented verifying some virtual guest orders and quotes that included placement groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 18, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220318/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220318/</guid>
      <description>API API will throw error if a snapshot is not deleted when requested. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 11, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220311/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220311/</guid>
      <description>API Deny SLDN access to network VLAN trunks for which user lacks component access Backend Prevent storage upgrades from creating unnecessary records that would inflate volume counts. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 4, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220304/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220304/</guid>
      <description>API Deduplicate list of users that have access to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest Fix File/Block volume-detail API call to return one Target IP (out of 2 its configured with) when classic block volume is moved into different HA pair. The Target IP Address returned after this fix for any block volumes may differ from what was returned in the past. This is because we are now returning one out of the two Target IPs we are offering for multipath configuration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 4, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220204/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220204/</guid>
      <description>API Correct volume usage and limits should show in command output Backend Support IAM Policy equivalent to VPN_MANAGE permission Improve performance when querying package regions, which should result in faster load times of order forms. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 26, 2022</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220126/</guid>
      <description>API Global IP billing items will only have a null provisionTransaction Reduced payload of SoftLayer_Network_Component getObject calls for unmasked keys Backend The hardware power state record will be updated whenever the power state is changed via IPMI VLANs can be cancelled when associated to scale groups. The association will be automatically deleted during reclaim. Added support to order VMware with vSphere version 7.0 Prevent a very rare disk image attach bug that deletes destination disk Set Debian default boot mode to HVM only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 8, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211208/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211208/</guid>
      <description>API Deprecate the &amp;lsquo;bundleItems&amp;rsquo; relational property on &amp;lsquo;SoftLayer_Billing_Item&amp;rsquo;. Not to be confused with &amp;lsquo;bundledItems&amp;rsquo;, which is the correct relational property to use. Functionality to enable disable snapshot usage warning notification. SoftLayer_Network_Storage::setSnapshotNotification and SoftLayer_Network_Storage::getSnapshotNotificationStatus Update getbandwidthData function call to work properly. Adds deviceStatus to virtual guest class Update powerOff and powerOn and powerOffSoft methods to call updateDeviceStatus method and update the device status accordingly. Add SoftLayer_Hardware_Status link from SoftLayer_Hardware Update SoftLayer_Billing_Item::cancel to call updateDeviceStatus Addresses over billing when PlanId changes Adds deprecation tagging support for SLDN and metadata documentation Backend Fix dedicated host migrations to retain proper CPU, memory, and disk space allocations </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 12, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211112/</guid>
      <description>API Fix issues with SoftLayer_Account_Authentication_Attribute_Type::getAllObjects. Replaced softwareComponent[0] to the operatingSystem ORM key to fix if software components are in incorrect order. Customers can choose to enable or disable getting snapshot usage warning notification </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 22, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211022/</guid>
      <description>API Improved SLDN documentation for some SoftLayer_User_Customer services. he change will prevent stalling the reclaim PI and also prevent a customer from waiting until its manually fixed Deprecated SoftLayer_Network_Tunnel_Module_Context::activeTransaction and SoftLayer_Network_Tunnel_Module_Context::transactionHistory This feature will provide an option ( configurable from slcli ) to enable and disable snapshot space usage warning notification. Added a condition to avoid No outgoing transition for Check Clone Quota On Status could be selected to continue the process Backend Prevent multiple processes from running at the same time to reconfigure a guest&amp;rsquo;s KVM console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 1, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211001/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20211001/</guid>
      <description>API Fix incorrect metrics in SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getMemoryMetricDataByDate API to get active transaction on a firewall Fixes an issue where spaces in objectMask causes SoftLayer_Event_Log::getAllObjects to error. Backend Prevent stalling Network_Storage reclaim jobs to prevent a customer from waiting until its manually fixed Corrects checking for existing vaults during ordering Updating reserved capacity to allow non-Core/RAM upgrades. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 3, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210903/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210903/</guid>
      <description>API Expose resetLink methods (resetLinkOpenIdConnect/resetLinkOpenIdConnectUnified ) to SLDN, allow master users to self-service change their own IBMid. Backend Seamlessly perform block volume failover without manual intervention when certain errors are thrown by backend storage </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 27, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210827/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210827/</guid>
      <description>Backend Update physical size limit for VSI images templates to be imported from COS to 250GiB </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 6, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210806/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210806/</guid>
      <description>API Remove property SoftLayer_Location::onlinePptpVpnUserCount Deprecate SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::activeTransaction and SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_Global::activeTransaction Provide flag and API on the hardware object to denote billing change available SoftLayer_Hardware::getAvailableBillingTermChangePrices Backend Prevent image captures for servers not in ACTIVE status Allow bare metal customers to migrate to term-based pricing. Customers can now upgrade from monthly to one-year, monthly to three-year or one-year to three-year term agreements. Ensure phone field validation methods are executed during user sync from cloud.ibm.com to SLDN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 30, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210730/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210730/</guid>
      <description>API Reverted a change from 2021-07-16, making SoftLayer_Hardware_Chassis.unitSize and int again, due to issues with the golang client not being able to properly un-marshal the data. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 23, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210723/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210723/</guid>
      <description>API Fix a rare issue that would prevent orders with very specific payloads and account conditions. Restrict apiKey creation to ACTIVE or VPN_ONLY users. Backend Prevent stalling on File and Block storage volumes during a reclaim. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 16, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210716/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210716/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed an issue that prevented resultLimits from working with the SoftLayer_Account::getVirtualGuests() API call when filtering based on a datacenter. Add an exception for the visibility of the apiKey during the initial creation of the key and value Changed SoftLayer_Hardware_Chassis.unitSize from int to float to accommodate larger values Backend Fixed an issue preventing VPC Block Storage volumes from getting reclaimed properly. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 28, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210628/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210628/</guid>
      <description>API Added &amp;lsquo;hardwareFunctionDescription&amp;rsquo; property to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest class SoftLayer_Hardware_Component_Firmware_SeverityTypes records names for &amp;lsquo;minor&amp;rsquo; is update to &amp;lsquo;Optional&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;important&amp;rsquo; updated to &amp;lsquo;Recommended&amp;rsquo; Create new option for more restrictive rules on VPN access management, if an account attribute that selects the new behavior is set. Restricts sslVpnAllowedFlag update to users with VPN_MANAGE permission Backend New features like duplication, snapshots, etc will be enabled for v1 File and Block customer volumes </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 7, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210607/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210607/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an error where CPU/RAM graphs for virtual servers were showing 5x their actual value. Update https://cloud.ibm.com/infrastructure/vmware-solutions/console/settings page with current user&amp;rsquo;s api key to fix no bare matel error due to hardware permissions. API Backend Successfully complete reclaim of host authorized block replica volumes, if same host is authorized to multiple block storage volumes. Prevent servers with Veeam software from being captured Fixed an error when converting a storage volume to independent would cause a stuck transaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 21, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210521/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210521/</guid>
      <description>API Deprecate SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::activeTransaction. Expect an empty response from this key during subnet provisioning. Backend Added validation for missing required security groups allow_https and allow_outbound for new orders Removed the ability to order a File or Block replica volume using an interval schedule </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 7, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210507/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210507/</guid>
      <description>API Improve performance for getIamId for deleted users, will help user listing on account with large #&amp;rsquo;s of deleted users. API improvement for consoleData Add websocketPath to SoftLayer_Container_Virtual_Guest_ConsoleData Fix issue with customers not being able to generate a valid signed JWT token. Rename SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_BrowserConsoleAccessLog to SoftLayer_Virtual_BrowserConsoleAccessLog Rename SoftLayer_Container_Virtual_Guest_ConsoleData to SoftLayer_Container_Virtual_ConsoleData Backend Fixed an issue with sending compliance report email. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 30, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210430/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210430/</guid>
      <description>API VMWare order: an incorrect error message is displayed if a name is too long Adds the sourcePort property to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_BrowserConsoleAccessLog class Backend Fixing compliance reports tool. Updated the way we determine if a billing item has a reclaim transaction for Storage As A Service billing items. Allow customers to reclaim a storage as a service billing item that has been previously un-cancelled. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 21, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210421/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210421/</guid>
      <description>API Exposes Browser Console Logs to the SLDN so that customers may access them. SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_BrowserConsoleAccessLog SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::browserConsoleAccessLogs Optimized the &amp;lsquo;datacenter&amp;rsquo; ORM key on the Virtual_Guest class Backend Ensure pricing not available to a customer does not inadvertently cause an OS reload of the current OS. Fix the manual snapshot after dr failover Updated chunk size for image exports to COS from 64mb to 128 mb disallowing image captures on private network only servers </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 15, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220415/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220415/</guid>
      <description>API Adds SoftLayer_Network_Storage::validateHostsAccess() Extend SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::route and clearRoute to all secondary subnets. Removed SoftLayer_User_Customer::salesforceUserLink property </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 9, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210409/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210409/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix UI so that an impatient user cannot make multiple requests by banging on the button. API Improve the message in getApiAuthenticationKeys method when subuser get the key of another Deprecating SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_Global::route and SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_Global::unroute, which will continue to function as proxies to SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::route and SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::unroute, respectively. A transaction record will no longer be returned from either endpoint. Add payment type validation for anonymous orders in the API. exposed API call that allows the customer to check on the most recent timestamp of the replication process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 1, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2022/20220401/</guid>
      <description>API Removed usages Of getBandwidthByHour methods in the SoftLayer_Network_Bandwidth_Version1_Allotment class. Update getCpuMetricDataByDate to stop passing in all 256 CPU types Permit a single speed change request per host, per network at a time. Backend Block RedHat&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;EL for SAP HANA&amp;rsquo; and CentOS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;CentOS Stream&amp;rsquo; from image mobility capture </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 26, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210326/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210326/</guid>
      <description>Backend Let either USER_MANAGE IMS permission or user-management IAM Policy be sufficient for doing device access management When a user is deleted, change the username so that a deleted user is not &amp;ldquo;squatting&amp;rdquo; on the username. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 19, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210319/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210319/</guid>
      <description>API Fix an issue causing some order API requests to fail to get the orderServerMonthlyAmount and orderNonServerMonthlyAmount properties. Backend Fixed an issue where an Event log was not generated when IP Restriction was added\removed from User profile in the cloud portal. Update subnet category cancellation flags to allow a user to cancel the billing items without them being a child. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 8, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210308/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210308/</guid>
      <description>API ApiKeys should now only be visible to the owner of the api key. The master user will be able to see if a user has a key, but not the actual value of the key. Return false instead of exception for SoftLayer_Network_Storage::isIndedicatedServiceResource function. Improved SLDN documentation on SoftLayer_User_Permission_Group_Type Added new api for disaster recovery failover for Network Storage volumes. Added a check in failbackfromReplicant to prevent flagged parent volume from failing back Added Method to get a firewalls version: SoftLayer_Network_Vlan_Firewall::getFirewallFirmwareVersion SoftLayer_Network_Message_Delivery::sendEmail() endpoint has been deprecated and will be removed in API version 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 26, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210226/</guid>
      <description>API SoftLayer_Network_Protection_Address::serviceProvider has been deprecated and will no longer provide filtering or yield data. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 12, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210212/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210212/</guid>
      <description>API New datatype: SoftLayer_User_Permission_Resource_Type Backend Allow Network_Storage Host authorization before invoking split PI </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 5, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210205/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210205/</guid>
      <description>API Delete user&amp;rsquo;s apiKey(s) when user is deleted Backend Improved check for availability in selected location when ordering IPSec VPN services. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 29, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210129/</guid>
      <description>API Added SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::findByHostName() Backend Add index to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::hostname Prevent Classic Infrastructure apiKey generation for users in Pending state. Sync legacy SoftLayer SAML Federated users over to PaaS upon creation. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 22, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210122/</guid>
      <description>API Correct documentation on Customer::createObject (re ACTIVE users in linked account pair w/ IBMid) Discontinue support for SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getCustomGraphImage() </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 15, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210115/</guid>
      <description>API SoftLayer_Network_Tunnel_Module_Context::applyConfigurationsToDevice will not generate a transaction. Error handling has been updated to use typed errors and altered messaging. Backend Volume refresh transactions will no longer stall on a known error, alleviating the need for manual intervention from Customer Support. Dependent duplicate will become independent after the completion of the convert_to_independent process </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 12, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210112/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210112/</guid>
      <description>Depreciated Notice SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getCustomGraphData() will no longer return image data starting on 2021-01-20. The method will still return a SoftLayer_Container_Graph object, but the image property will be empty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 8, 2021</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210108/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2021/20210108/</guid>
      <description>API Add validation for email address (must be specified except in special cases) when creating a SoftLayer_User_Customer Backend Adds a retry when netapp connection failure occurs Prevent duplicate volume from being refreshed while duplicate provision is still happening. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201211/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201211/</guid>
      <description>Backend Improve handling of upgrades for FileBlock volumes when the replicant is reclaimed in-between upgrade placement and upgrade processing. Fix issue with userdata not getting set from the order </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201204/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201204/</guid>
      <description>API Improve error message for active user in Inactive account. &amp;lt;SOAP-ENV:Fault&amp;gt; &amp;lt;faultcode&amp;gt;SoftLayer_Exception_Public&amp;lt;/faultcode&amp;gt; &amp;lt;faultstring&amp;gt;Account &amp;lt;$ACCOUNT_ID&amp;gt; is not ACTIVE. Your request cannot be processed. Please contact support.&amp;lt;/faultstring&amp;gt; &amp;lt;faultactor/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/SOAP-ENV:Fault&amp;gt; Properties added that allows enablement of 3D Secure. Cardinal Cruise Hybrid (https://cardinaldocs.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/CC/pages/360668/Cardinal+Cruise+Hybrid) is a prerequisite in order to use this feature to leverage the authentication. SoftLayer_Container_Product_Order_Billing_Information::payerAuthenticationEnrollmentReferenceId Improved SLDN documentation for the SoftLayer_User_Permission classes that make up the customer permission system. Backend Adding support for using cloud subscription for all linked customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201120/</guid>
      <description>API Updated storageGroupDetails to be returned as a container </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201116/</guid>
      <description>API Added &amp;ldquo;getAccountId&amp;rdquo; to SoftLayer_Resource_Metadata service Fixed Property &#39;monitoringServiceEligibilityFlag&#39; not valid errors. Backend Ensure that a server provisioned from a captured block device has the same boot mode as the captured server. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 30, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201030/</guid>
      <description>Backend Refresh a guest&amp;rsquo;s secondary disk category code upon detaching a disk, similar to what happens when attaching a disk Improve error message when reset link attempted with non-existing IBMid. Skip BDS for Fast Server Provisions, only create when TPM, SGX, or UEFI is requested Allow master user IBMid link reset for MU in SUSPENDED state </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201023/</guid>
      <description>API New SLDN endpoints are exposed to route and unroute customer-owned subnets. SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::route SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::clearRoute Restrict management of an apiKey to the user themselves (not parent, not master user) or an Employee. Deprecated Advanced Monitoring related apis Add deprecated tag to getPortalLoginTokenOIDC API. Backend Prevent File/Block volumes from being deleted if there are other active processes related to that volume. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201016/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed bugs with SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getBandwidthTotal and getBandwidthForDateRange Added checksumAlgorithm to SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image Backend Replica volume cancellation is not allowed when volume failover is initiated. Added Validation to verify that the User has View Passwords Permission that is required to Order a Workflow. Allow a user to delete their own parent when IAM Policy overrides hierarchy Corrects setting the old billing item id on upgrade order items and associating new billing items with member servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 9, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20201009/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed some issues where SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template_Group::createFromIcos() would reutrn a HTTP 200 Status code, but an error message. Display RegisterVolumeEncryption with a value of 1 if present on listVolumes API response Backend Updates to improve SSL certificate offering. Changed volume independent duplicate provision to do split or move and then resize. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200924/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200924/</guid>
      <description>Portal Customer should be able to provision duplicate volume based on original volume location type flash or magnetic via UI Backend Allow Lenova Chassis to be captured Prevent Customer from being created or edited with a phone number containing invalid characters. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200917/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200917/</guid>
      <description>API Add supportedHardware to SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image Add diskFileExtension to SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image Fixed an issue where SoftLayer_Search limit greater than 25 does not work with SoftLayer_Event_Log </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 11, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200911/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200911/</guid>
      <description>API throw an exception if we customer requests refresh on duplicate which has replicas. SoftLayerAPIError(SoftLayer_Exception_InvalidValue): Invalid value provided for &#39;Duplicate Volume is unable to be refreshed while it has replica.&#39;. Allow snapshots to be refreshed on independent Volumes. New SoftLayer_Network_Storage::refreshDuplicate() API call. Utilizes same parameters as SoftLayer_Network_Storage::refreshDependentDuplicate(). Exposed isCloudInit method on the Virtual_Guest class and cloudInitiFlag ORM key attribute on the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template class Backend Fix for billing upgrade order perf type volumes in dependent and independent refresh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200904/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200904/</guid>
      <description>Portal Customer will be able to see Snapshot capacity warnings information properly in notification tickets. API Removed SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_VersionUpgrade:getAllByFromVersion API, no longer supported. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 28, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200828/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200828/</guid>
      <description>API Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Component_HardDrive::PSID Expose storage groups on Hardware_Server objects so they can be used for image mobility SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::logicalVolumeStorageGroups SoftLayer_Hardware_Component::logicalVolumeStorageGroups SoftLayer_Configuration_Storage_Group::captureEnabledFlag Added SLDN docs for diskImage::storageGroups Backend Correct bug that was preventing assigning a role to an agent user in the BAP. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200821/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200821/</guid>
      <description>API Resolves an issue where the getUpgradeItemPrice methods did not return pricing specific to the location the resource was located in. BAP issue where agent only updates are missing from their ticket view </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 14, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200814/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200814/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where &amp;ldquo;Transaction in progress&amp;rdquo; was shown for a completed captured image Prevent user from capturing image with no billing items Backend IPMI must be enable to start capture transactions </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 7, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200807/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200807/</guid>
      <description>API Updates the behavior of OR statements in SoftLayer_Search::advancedSearch queries SoftLayer_Network_Gateway::canRollbackVersion() was removed and replaced with SoftLayer_Network_Gateway::isRollbackAllowed() Add &amp;lsquo;origin&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;realm&amp;rsquo; fields to receiveEventDirect API payload Backend Fixes an issue that prevented users that did not have the account summary permission from seeing fees on current pricing when using the getUpgradeItemPrices service methods. Customer will be able to see Snapshot capacity warnings information properly in overage warning tickets. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200724/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200724/</guid>
      <description>API Ticket update relationships should now properly exclude brand agent updates. Deprecated Global Load Balancer services. SoftLayer_Network_LoadBalancer_Global_Account SoftLayer_Network_LoadBalancer_Global_Host </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200717/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200717/</guid>
      <description>API Allow a user to delete themselves (API level) Backed Allow the successful restoration of monthly-billed Netscaler guests that are still in 24 hour RECLAIM_WAIT status Enhanced authentication security for Cloud storage. Fixed VSI provisioning emails to use correct currency symbols. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 10, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200710/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200710/</guid>
      <description>API Removed automatic masking of &amp;lsquo;subnet&amp;rsquo; key from IP addresses fetched by SoftLayer_Network_Subnet::getRoutableIpAddresses Updated SLDN documentation for creating a brand. DEPRECATED SoftLayer_Account::updateVpnUsersForResource Added SoftLayer_Product_Package::noUpgradesFlag Added bnppCompliantFlag Backend Fix an issue causing some hardware orders to use the wrong partitioning layout. Merge master user / account owner IP restrictions when existing accounts are linked </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 26, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200626/</guid>
      <description>API Begins the process of deprecating bandwidth related SLDN endpoints on the SoftLayer_Account and SoftLayer_Network_Bandwidth_Version1_Allotment class that are no longer being supported. fixes bug in ordering fixed config presets with both core and processor restricted prices Backend Volume name were not appearing in the snapshot capacity warnings. Fixed an issue preventing device from be added on a BAP account when added from the Support Center Fixed a bug with migrating dedicated host that have no guests attached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200619/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200619/</guid>
      <description>API Implement disabledSnapshot for Block and File volume replicas&#xA;SoftLayer_Network_Storage::disableSnapshots Prevent detach of local disks for VSIs greater than 300GB&#xA;Exception: &amp;lt;faultcode&amp;gt;SoftLayer_Exception_Public&amp;lt;/faultcode&amp;gt; &amp;lt;faultstring&amp;gt;Disk capacity exceeds the maximum size eligible for portability on local storage and can not be detached.&amp;lt;/faultstring&amp;gt; Fixed an issue causing fixed configurations to not handle disk controller limits properly.&#xA;When verifying or placing an order, fixed configuration presets will populate the storageGroups property on server order containers with those defined by their preset, rather than remaining empty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 12, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200612/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200612/</guid>
      <description>API SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createArchiveTransaction and SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createArchiveTemplate will return a Image template, and not a transaction Network_Subnet::setTags() and Network_Subnet::tagReferences UTF-8 support for SoftLayer_Network_Subnet and SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress note fields. Deprecate RWHOIS service &amp;amp; SWIP based Registrations. See RIR Registrations and RWhois deprecation notice for more information. The following have been removed. Account::getRwhoisData() Network_Subnet::getSwipTransaction() Network_Subnet::activeSwipTransaction() Network_Subnet::findAllSubnetsAndActiveSwipTransactionStatus() Network_Subnet::getRwhoisData() Network_Subnet::createSwipTransaction() Network_Subnet_Rwhois_Data (all) SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction (all) Backend Bug fix for live migration SWAP disk coalescing issues. Enables ordering and reloading bare metal servers with an image template.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 29, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200529/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200529/</guid>
      <description>API Fixes a bug when users attempt to create some load balancer pools. Backend Fixed ordering bug for reserved capacity groups. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200522/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200522/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed bug where sub-brand accounts could not be created. Clarify the text of error message when an operation is performed with an invalid user status. API Deprecation Server.getPrivateVlanByIpAddress() Network_Vlan.getPrivateVlanByIpAddress() SoftLayer_Network_Component.storageNetworkFlag SoftLayer_Hardware.storageNetworkComponents Backend Will now properly notify customers for potential Evault overages. Catalog Created disk drive destruction price category and allowed for drive destruction ordering. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200515/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200515/</guid>
      <description>API customers can better identify which specific storage product is on their bills Added regions to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template_Group Added SoftLayer_Network_Gateway::getAllowedOsPriceIds() Added SoftLayer_Network_Gateway::isLicenseServerAllowed() Backend Fix emails when substitutions have extended characters Catalog Remove Item ID 11327 from Package 2634 as it is not qualified by HWSOL. Add 8280 processor to 1111 and 2670 packages Add 2-CPU SAP-certified Intel Cascade Lake servers for HANA Add 4-CPU SAP-certified Intel Cascade Lake servers for HANA Add WDC04 to product package 2670 New Release: Microsoft SQL Server 2019 Enable 4U E5-2650v4 in TOK05 Add SJC01, SJC03 and SJC04 to package 2634 Remove DAL07, MEL01, &amp;amp; SEA01 from Catalog/Order Forms Add GPU VSIs to IKS GPU package AC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200504/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200504/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improve wording on the IaaS order and quote checkout pages and improve the tax estimations provided for quotes. API Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getCpuMetricDataByDate throwing an Exception about too much data requested. Backend Fixed a private to private lbaas image upgrade issue Restricting deletion of SSL certificates configured in Loadbalancer HTTPS listener Allow user to specify public subnet to provision public load balancers More accurately show that packages and presets have GPU products or not in the catalog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200421/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200421/</guid>
      <description>API Update SoftLayer_Account::getNetworkStorage() API call for replicationStatus, should no longer throw Exceptions on certain volumes. Fix for SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::setTags() when tags are empty. Effectively calling setTags with an empty tag will clear tags on the VM. Update storage and image information tables with backingFileWdek and ImageWdek fields to support custom encrypted images. Prevent SUSPENDED-&amp;gt;IAMID_INVALID transition for SoftLayer_User_Customer::editObject() SoftLayer_User_Customer_Notification_Hardware::createObject will return the created object. Improve documentation for SoftLayer_User_Customer_Notification_Virtual_Guest. Add start and end date, and server ID parameters to the new SoftLayer_Account::getBandwidthList() API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200403/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200403/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixes an issue where IBM Cloud Backup usage was not showing in the customer portal. API Customers who use the api to manage their users&amp;rsquo; permissions may notice that the type of exception and exception message for invalid requests to some SoftLayer_User_Permission services have changed. These scenarios were already considered invalid and does not affect permissions being managed via Customer UI. New: Hardware_Server::captureEnabledFlag Fixed an issue preventing users making SOAP API calls from being able to properly setup Verisign 2FA with SoftLayer_User_Customer::addExternalBinding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200320/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200320/</guid>
      <description>API Update thrown exception type in User_Customer::silentlyMigrateUserOpenIdConnect &amp;lt;faultcode&amp;gt;SoftLayer_Exception_NotReady&amp;lt;/faultcode&amp;gt; &amp;lt;faultstring&amp;gt;Only ACTIVE and PENDING users can be migrated to IBMid.&amp;lt;/faultstring&amp;gt; IBM Cloud CDN - Multiple file purge SOAP API support. Added SLDN description for the SoftLayer_User_Permission_Group_Type::groups </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200313/</guid>
      <description>API Improved error handling in removeVirtualGuestAccess API. This changes the &amp;lsquo;SoftLayer-Total-Items&amp;rsquo; header representing the total number of tagged items to be the full number in the list even if a result limit is applied. The affected endpoints are SoftLayer_Tag::getUnattachedTagsForCurrentUser and SoftLayer_Tag::getAttachedTagsForCurrentUser. New feature that allows enablement of 3D Secure. Cardinal Cruise Hybrid Removed forum related text from API docblocks Improve error messages when reassigning parent for a user. Customers who were using the SoftLayer_User_Customer api to obtain phone factor will need to go through the proper ordering process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 28, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200228/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200228/</guid>
      <description>API SoftLayer_User_Customer::removeAllVirtualAccess will no longer be blocked when the user has lingering access on a device that is in deleted state. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200221/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200221/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrects the EU terms and conditions link on customer facing quote checkout pages. API Added SoftLayer_Account::getBandwidthList()&#xA;The following permissions are now obsolete:&#xA;ID KeyName Description 1288 TICKET_MANAGE Add / Edit Tickets 1309 ACCOUNT_PASSWORD_AUXILIARY_ADD Add Auxiliary Password 1310 ACCOUNT_PASSWORD_AUXILIARY_EDIT Edit Auxiliary Password 1311 ACCOUNT_PASSWORD_AUXILIARY_DELETE Delete Auxiliary Password 3738 CUSTOMER_PLACEMENT_GROUP_MANAGEMENT Manage Placement Group 3740 CUSTOMER_RESERVED_CAPACITY_GROUP_MANAGEMENT Manage Reserved Capacity Group 1305 TICKET_VIEW_BY_HARDWARE View Tickets by Hardware Access View Tickets by Hardware 1306 TICKET_VIEW_BY_VIRTUAL_GUEST View Tickets by Computing Instance Access Backend Prevent Dedicated Host VSI upgrade orders when the user placing the upgrade does not have permission for the dedicated host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 14, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200214/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200214/</guid>
      <description>API SoftLayer_User_Customer::minimumPasswordLifeHours and SoftLayer_User_Customer::secondaryPasswordTimeoutDays will no longer allow NULL value to be set. Adds two new public API calls that allow requesting account-specific tag information. getUnattachedTagsForCurrentUser getAttachedTagsForCurrentUser SoftLayer_Software_Component_AntivirusSpyware::updateAntivirusSpywarePolicy() will only accept values 1-5 for newPolicy Backend Fixed an issue preventing some bare metal gateway appliance orders from being completed </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 31, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200131/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrects an error thrown when displaying closed alarms in the customer portal. API SoftLayer_Account::getCurrentBackupStatisticsGraph has been marked deprecated. This method no longer returns binary image data of the account backup statistics. Allow clone conversion dependent to independent calls in Network_Storage class. SoftLayer_User_Customer minimumPasswordHours/secondaryPasswordTimeoutDays will not allow a NULL value. Provide SoftLayer_Network_Storage::getVolumeCountLimits to allow customers to view their storage account limits SoftLayer_Account::networkCreationFlag deprecation notice. Fixed an issue when calling SoftLayer_User_Customer::createObject Backend Fixed BAP Agent updates not showing in tickets Fixed an issue preventing customers from attaching hardware to tickets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200117/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed an issue preventing importing Windows 2019 images from COS Updated strict and fuzzy logic search documentation on SoftLayer_Search Forces Hardware_Component serial numbers to be stored in lower case, even when the serial numbers look like they are numbers in Exponential Notation. For example, 1234E5 will now be 1234e5. Backend Clear Tamper Flag on HSMs if HSM was zeroized. Enable cookie persistence for LBaaS to support multiple pools. Catalog Enable U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 10, 2020</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2020/20200110/</guid>
      <description>Backend Prevent additional notification emails from being sent when customers have disabled notifications. Fixed bug in live migrations </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191218/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191218/</guid>
      <description>API Fix issue where requests to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest generateOrderTemplate did not include the primary subnet id of the frontend and backend network components from the virtual guest template object in the response&amp;rsquo;s order container. Better validation and error responses in SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration and SoftLayer_Account_Regional_Registry_Detail Fixed bug when creating Federated user. SLDN Changed the CSS on the datatypes and services pages. If those pages look strange, please clear your browser cache or forcefully re-download the custom css </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Disruption Notice</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191216/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191216/</guid>
      <description> Bandwidth Graph methods are being depreciated The following methods will be depreciated on Dec 18, 2019, and removed entirely at a later date.&#xA;SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getBackboneBandwidthGraph SoftLayer_Network_Backbond::getGraphImage SoftLayer_Account::getCurrentBackupStatisticsGraph SoftLayer_Account::getCurrentTicketStatisticsGraph Some pod relationships are being removed The following relationships will be removed on Dec 18, 2019.&#xA;SoftLayer_Hardware-&amp;gt;pod SoftLayer_Hardware_Router-&amp;gt;pod SoftLayer_Network_Component-&amp;gt;interface SoftLayer_Hardware_Router_Backend-&amp;gt;pod SoftLayer_Hardware_Router_Frontend-&amp;gt;pod </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191212/</guid>
      <description>Portal Name of dedicated host device is displayed correctly in ServiceNow case API SoftLayer_Account::getCurrentTicketStatisticsGraph has been marked deprecated. This method no longer returns binary image data of the account ticket statistics. Allow brand agent users to select a subject when escalating a ticket. Add graceful handling of bad order data when StaaS orders are missing prices for an entire category. Customer removeExternalBinding exceptions return Customer class rather than Binding class Fixed bug in SoftLayer_Brand::createCustomerAccount API where an empty postal code was causing an incorrect validation error for countries that do not require a postal code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191122/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed an issue causing exceptions to be thrown if NVMe disks were not added to the end of an order&amp;rsquo;s price list. Backend Introduces ability for customers to add or upgrade their network gateway licensing. The new upgrade path has no impact without the new software license products being available in the product catalog. This issue also improves the customer experience when attempting to perform hardware upgrades for a gateway which is not allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191101/</guid>
      <description>Catalog New Cascade Lake Hourly FSP&amp;rsquo;s Silver 4210 64GB 2X1.7TB SSD NoRAID - Preset 1214 Gold 5218 64GB 2x1.7TB SSD NoRAID - Preset 1216 Gold 6248 384GB 4x1.7TB SSD RAID10 - Preset 1218 Remove 7.68TB SSDs from the ReadyNode package 1053 Managed services premium application for package 993 Enable UEFI boot for several operating systems Windows / RHEL 7 / CentOS 7 / Ubuntu 18.04 NO OS / XenServer 7.1.2 / XenServer 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191025/</guid>
      <description>Portal Update legacy order form UI for NVME Fix issue preventing some server descriptions from being displayed correctly when ordering. API Adds IP version validation when ordering subnets. Backend Properly handle IPMI errors during the assign server step of server provisions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20191004/</guid>
      <description>API Block NextGen images from being ordered on classic VSIs. Image templates have &amp;ldquo;features&amp;rdquo; that track which platform the image is capable of provisioning, Classic, Generation Classic (GC), and NextGen. Classic VSI&amp;rsquo;s can only be provisioned with image templates identified by the Classic feature. SoftLayer_User_Customer::selfPasswordChange will return a new session token after success. Backend WebCc components of evault provisions alongside servers will now function as intended. Customers will no longer need to re-order evaults and ask backup ops for assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190927/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190927/</guid>
      <description>Backend API Fixed &amp;quot;error&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Property &#39;gpuCount&#39; not valid for &#39;SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest&#39;.&amp;quot; Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_User_Customer::InitiatePortalPasswordChangeByBrandAgent() not working as documented. Creating Premium Support For Preferred Partners brand attribute to support a new offering allowing BAP to escalate tickets at a high priority. Create new &amp;ldquo;SUSPENDED&amp;rdquo; user status, statusId=1005 Display complexity related errors when user attempt to update vpn password. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190920/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190920/</guid>
      <description>Backend Fix issue where ordering from a quote did not total the monthly cost at checkout correctly. Customers will no longer have to wait for volume moves as part of resize. Adding Bare Metal Gateway License category code. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190913/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190913/</guid>
      <description>Portal Remove &amp;ldquo;CANCEL_PENDING&amp;rdquo; in UI in favor of &amp;ldquo;Deleted&amp;rdquo; API The following are removed from SLDN SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Allowed_Host::createFromHardware SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Allowed_Host::createFromVirtualGuest SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Allowed_Host::createFromIpAddress SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Allowed_Host::createFromSubnet These methods have never worked as stand-alone API calls. They were designed to be used in other host authorization methods. Please, continue to use the following API methods to authorize hosts: - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHardware - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHardwareList - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromVirtualGuest - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromVirtualGuestList - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromIpAddress - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromIpAddressList - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromSubnet - SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromSubnetList&#xA;Notify Backup Storage Customers with tickets about their un-billed Backup storage Don&amp;rsquo;t allow NVMe disks to be part of storage group Password requirements are returned in SoftLayer_User_Customer::getRequirementsForPasswordSet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190830/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adds a new product group to the order forms for NVMe SSD disks Fix owner IBMid change broken by 2FA/SecAnswers API allowedPptpVpnQuantity set to zero for all accounts. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190823/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190823/</guid>
      <description>Portal Add redirect for Manage portal /login and /index to appropriate login page API Add logging of iSCSI and NFS Host Authorization to the SoftLayer_Event_Log for authorization and deauthorization events Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getPendingMaintenanceActions() Fix issue with verifyOrder checking public pool capacity on VPC guests Adding a new trait (DEFAULT_NEW_ACCOUNTS_PREMIUM) that if set to 1 will initialize all new brand sub-accounts with Premium support. Backend Fix issue where retention disk billing would sometimes be inaccurate after reloading a virtual server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190816/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190816/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix issue preventing orders from completing for new EU customers. Fix the payment method disappearing when selecting PayPal, leaving the user unable select another payment method. API Adds SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getPendingMaintanceActions() Added ability to skip platform account creation and linking when using the SoftLayer_Brand::createCustomerAccount API Exposed gpuType and gpuCount on the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest class Add iamidVerificationFlag to SoftLayer_User_Customer_Link Allow gateway orders to define the router id on the hardware template object. &amp;#34;hardware&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;hostname&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;softlayer&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;domain&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;local.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190802/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190802/</guid>
      <description>API Create new Software_Description HSM_OS attribute type Backend Do not require postal code for ARIN addresses outside US &amp;amp; Canada Fix accepting Master User invitation on account linked at create time Fixed an issue upgrade GPU enabled VSIs Prevents ordering GPU&amp;rsquo;s when provisioning from an image template set to boot in PV. Catalog Adding a category code for dynamic CDN bandwidth. cdn_service_dynamic_bandwidth cdn_service_dynamic_bandwidth_usage Add 500GB Bandwidth option to package 1111 Update Single Node Preset 1051 in package 1075 with updated pricing Create rule to conflict Windows 2019 and vCenter 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190726/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190726/</guid>
      <description>Portal Changes to order currency selection logic. Existing customers will have orders default to the currency selected on their billing information, or US Dollars if unavailable. Surfaces helpful validation messages to customers upgrading to PAYGO API Allow customers to query read-only information about the keyName of their assigned Catalog SoftLayer_Account-&amp;gt;brand-&amp;gt;catalog-&amp;gt;keyName Backend Improve the process of provisioning IBM Backup Storages. Allow customer cancellation of VLANs with other canceled resources on the VLAN IBM Cloud CDN - Update the IBM CNAME to use new domain &amp;lsquo;cdn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190712/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190712/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Fix issue where some order receipts did not have consistent data provided in API responses. Adding exception message if interconnect tenant has no billing item when trying to upgrade. Remove depreciated Network Core Account Defined Networks code from User_Cusomer All customer users pptpVpnAllowedFlag is set to 0 Backend Prevent attempts to attach a portable disk to multiple VSIs at the same time. Restrict performing an OS reload of a guest with GPUs into PV boot mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190719/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190719/</guid>
      <description>Portal Choosing a secondary IP Address brought on requirement questions. These are now translated for other languages. Prevents Bare Metal Reserved servers from appearing on the server list page. Fixed an issue where cases created from the support center are not coming through as BAP escalated API Allow user to set default IBMid link, correct permissions required SoftLayer_User_Customer_OpenIdConnect::setDefaultAccount() IBM Cloud CDN - Support &amp;ldquo;/&amp;rdquo; at the end of purge url path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190701/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190701/</guid>
      <description>Portal Email can be removed from watchlist by control portal API Fix a bug that could&amp;rsquo;ve resulted in additional conflict rules from being retrieved when querying via the package. Add SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::nextGenFlag field to indicate that image is a next gen image New API getIscsiIsolationDisabled, added to SoftLayer_Account to display the iSCSI isolation status of an account. Backend Users with the user-management Editor or Admin role should now be properly allowed to delete users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190621/</guid>
      <description>API Fixed lookup of getAllowableSubnets call for Network_Storage Immediately completes accounts during the creation process Load balancer lookup by name should be case insensitive </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190614/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190614/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adding option to suppress user ticket emails API Add the &amp;rsquo;name&amp;rsquo; field for the ram usage category. Reduce ancillary relations from being returned by Account.publicIpAddresses, Account.publicIpAddresses, Account.ipAddresses, Account.subnets, Account.publicSubnets, and Account.privateSubnets. This may require additional masks be provided to receive information previously available in API responses. Enforces non-duplicate rule for createCustomerAccount during as well as after account creation Backend Cloud LbaaS : public-to-public loadbalancer feature </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 07, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190607/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190607/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added some missing translations from the order forms. Changed the mobile app URL scheme to ibmcloud. Stop cc&amp;rsquo;ing master users when orders are approved. API isEncrypted is not a required data type when the createFromIcos method is called by API. Fixed users being unable to change user status for a child with user with user-management Editor/Admin role and USER_MANAGE permission Backend Correctly prorate storage upgrade orders. Cloud LBaaS will now use new domain clb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190531/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190531/</guid>
      <description>API Prevent VLAN trunking API from operating on Gateway inside VLANs for Gateway member ports. Prevent the Gateway API from allowing VLAN association if a Gateway member port has the VLAN trunked already. Backend Cancel storage upgrades early if the storage volume is deleted while the upgrade is being processed. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190524/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190524/</guid>
      <description>Portal Requires company name on new account orders Fixed issue with certain Korean addresses failing account validation. Changed IBM Cloud Docs URLs in emails and automated tickets to new format. API Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Component_Locator::getPackageItemsAvailability($packageId) User_Permission_Group::addResourceObject verifies that the resource object exists in the source table. Prevents non-anonymous users from using the IOT service and adds SLDN docs stating as much. https://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/IntegratedOfferingTeam_Region/getAllObjects/ Rename the Customer variable iamUserPermission to iamUserRetrievePermission in the Customer and Ticket classes </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190517/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190517/</guid>
      <description>Portal SafeNet Luna should no longer appear as a software option for non-hsm devices API Add expirationDate validation to User Permission Group Fixed the SLDNDocumentation for the ORM key apiAuthenticationKeys. Added the numeric check to the beginning of addDeviceAccess function. Add short description to Network_Vlan.upgrade, and update description to utilize Automatic and Premium nomenclature. Catalog VSI Reserved Instance Pricing Update Reserve Bare Metal - GA SAP HANA hardware updates Update Monthly and Hourly pricing for Windows Server 2012, 2012 R2, and 2016 Standard Editions only for VSI 32GB V100 GPU on Bare Metal Make Package 200 Presets available in Several Data Centers HOU02 DAL07 SJC04 SAO01 BYOL Support for IC4V VMware OS </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190510/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190510/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix an issue where users were unable to change user status from VPN_ONLY/ DISABLED to ACTIVE with a user with user-management Editor or Admin role Fix issue where receipt pages may show inaccurate totals after PayPal payment. Removes the now defunct edgecast URLs from the WWW portal API New service Hardware_Component_Locator </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190503/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190503/</guid>
      <description>API Fix Customer::createObject to be synchronous again (in the delegate-to-Bluemix case) Added endpoint to modify account information. Backend R1soft - remove the option to reload with r1soft for private only servers Fix an problem that was causing issues when multiple HSMs were provisioned on the same order. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190426/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190426/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adding missing translations for the order forms API Endpoint to allow Brand Agents to re-activate accounts SoftLayer_Brand::disableAccount SoftLayer_Brand::reactivateAccount Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Component_Model::getServerPackageAvailability -Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Component_Model::getGenericComponentModelAvailability Backend Fix issue where usage fees could become incorrect after os reloads in some cases. Handle a user being brought back from CANCEL_PENDING in a linked account pair. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190419/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190419/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Fix SLDN Network_Component.redundancyCapableFlag to correclty report false when secondary ports are not available to the bare metal server as ordered. Adds a note to the BluePages_Search docs mentioning the service will not work for normal customers Backend L7 policy should not allow HTTP listener to have redirect pool with HTTPS protocol Catalog VMware OSs ( 6.5.0u1 and 6.7) that need to be removed from legacy packages packages effected: 255, 259, 261, 263, 265, 267, 269, 271 Package 257 available in Sao Paulo Enable 2U 2650v3 in FRA02 Create a new pre-set for 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190412/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190412/</guid>
      <description>Portal GEP enrollment request form page cache should be cleared, so that the form can generate an unique device finger print API Enabling object masks on the SoftLayer_Product_Promotion.findByPromoCode API Add UEFI boot message to order API response Change SoftLayer_User_Customer::ibmIdLink ORM key definition to be more efficient Add more information to a storage group template exception message Backend Removed location from DTS request since the location used was no longer in the package the request uses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190405/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190405/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix issue where the order forms were unhelpful in handling paypal payments that were cancelled. Backend Prevent placing an order for more than one private cloud service at a time. This issue lets copy to ICOS actions automatically refresh their IAM access token before it expires during large exports. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190329/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190329/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an error message being displayed when editing a Dedicated Host Fixed an issue with selecting more PCIe components on the order forms. API Expose enable data logs api in SLDN Adds the ability to look up a promotion and it&amp;rsquo;s requirements by promotion code from the SLDN API with SoftLayer_Product_Promotion class. Backend Sanitized Cos Imports/Exports source/target paths Catalog Changing the Micro VSI product to its new name Variable Compute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190322/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190322/</guid>
      <description>Portal When ordering from quotes, it is no longer possible to select a different country or currency than what the quote was generated with. The order was always ordered from the original quote, this only affects the interface. Correct being able to select hourly hardware security modules when ordering. API Fixed a bug in which erroneous input to Server.toggleManagementInterface could cause the generation of transactions which did nothing. Force volume modification of magnetic to not unselect magnetic clusters Improve performance of removeHardwareAccess methods Return correct authenticationKey from SoftLayer_User_Customer_ApiAuthentication::editObject method SL_Storage_Allowed_Host exposing additional orm key iscsiAclCredentials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190315/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190315/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adding Ticket integration for adding watch list users from control API Permission logs are returning null when there is only one record Restrict access to only accounts user owns when using getSummaryData() Gracefully handle case when network component is not attached to guest during detach vlan Backend Refactors the monitoring metrics to be read from influxdb. Fix major bug regarding image template transactions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190308/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190308/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added some missing translations for the checkout page API Cleanup SoftLayer_User_Permission_Resource when there are no groups referencing it. Refactored SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Hub_Swift_Metrics::getSummaryData to use improved data source. Deprecate the allowedPptpVpnQuantity property on the Account.class Deprecate the pptpVpnAllowedFlag on the Customer.class Update implementation of getAllObjects() on SoftLayer_User_Customer_Status Fix User_Customer_Status and Locale_Timezone SLDN exposed getAllObjects to return properly if request is REST Soap response restructuring - When the API fetches no results for virtual guest the soap response should not send empty collection Backend Fix issue delaying provisioning of HSM offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190226/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adds option for new customers to select if they are ordering on behalf of a business or as an individual. Also adds a checkbox allowing customers to specify they do not have a VAT ID. API Adds validation for userStatusId on api request SoftLayer_User_Customer::createObject Improved performance of SoftLayer_User_Customer::removeAllVirtualAccessForThisUser Adds the Exception field tor the SLDN API documentation Added SLDNDocumentation tag to new iamAuthorizationFlag variable Adds SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::createFirmwareReflashTransaction and SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::massFirmwareReflash to hardware servers allowing customers to reflash the components to the firmware currently installed on the device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190220/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190220/</guid>
      <description>Portal Use cloud.ibm.com URLs when sending emails to, or creating ticket updates for, linked customers. Replace nonfunctional KnowledgeLayer links in emails and automated ticket updates with IBM Cloud docs links API Improved performance of SoftLayer_Account::getVirtualGuests() when using objectFilters findGCImagesByCurrentUser is currently returning all the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template_Groups associated with a user&amp;rsquo;s account. This needs to be updated to return an array of only the applicable parent SVGBDTG Improve Server.activatePublicPort, Server.activatePrivatePort, Server.shutdownPublicPort, and Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 08, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190208/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190208/</guid>
      <description>Portal IAM User Management editor Role is now able to add VPN only user Show suspend usage rates as hourly fees in order email Replaces Bluemix URLs in email templates with IBM Cloud URLs Fixed html being sent as plain text in notification emails. API Update SLDN doc for Customer::createObject Backend Restore ability to enable IPMI ports in select pods Fix bug that would&amp;rsquo;ve prevented duplicate volume orders with an IOPS to space ratio of 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190131/</guid>
      <description>Portal Two translation keys are not shown correctly when an sub user with ES language places a Bare Metal Server order from Manage portal API SoftLayer_Account::getEvaultNetworkStorage will now properly allow objectFilters using billingItem ids. Previously any filters on this method using a billing item would return empty result. SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::removeTag will return False if a tag could not be found to remove, previously this would return True Fixed a bug preventing users who have migrated to IBMid being only able to see tags of hardware that their user or sub users have created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190125/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix ordering of dedicated hosts with GPUs from the control portal. Replace SoftLayer home page URL in emails, and one automated ticket update, with IBM Cloud URL. Replace KnowledgeLayer URL in emails with IBM Cloud Docs URL. API getCurrentBillingTotal will now include any usage based items Include the missig permission keyNames in change parent exception. Backend Removes the restriction on cloudinit RHEL to be BYOL. Automatically adds subscriptions to newly created activation keys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2019/20190118/</guid>
      <description>Portal Auto close invoice ready and payment due tickets. API Fixes a bug that caused the brand/sub-brand creation to fail when IBMid feature is turned off. User_Customer::getAllowedVirtualGuestIds() should no longer be returning RESERVED_CAPACITY guests. Update the accountId on queries on the permission_log class. Catalog New Package - BI.S3.NW1500 (OS Options) New Package - BI.S3.NW1500 (Vmware) Remove Package 911 from Availability in Sao Paulo Remove 800GB SSD Added 7.68TB SATA SSD ( HARD_DRIVE_7_68TB_SSD_SED_1DWPD ) to the following package: 1U 273, 253, 551, 837, 200, 737, 146, 261, 255, 257, 259, 126, 143 2U 265, 251, 553, 797, 737, 200, 839, 142, 148, 144, 50 4U 263, 248, 555, 267, 271, 234, 158, 56, 147, 833 Add SYD05 to 1075 Package Add redundant power supply (50221 / 469) to the order form for the following packages (all 1U) - 837 (Skylake dual proc), 911 (Kabylake 1270), 551 (Broadwell dual proc), 253 (Haswell dual proc), 257 (Haswell 1270) Except in AMS01, DAL01, DAL05, DAL06, DAL07, SEA01, SJC01, WDC01 Backend Fixed an issue impacting Nessus scanners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 19, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181219/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181219/</guid>
      <description>Portal Change favicon for ordering page API None Backend Remove hostPciDeviceId unassignment from VSI Reservation during Migration before GPU Upgrade. This resolves the issue where the VSI reservation hostPciDeviceId is null when trying to assign it again. Fixed an issue preventing where reloading a VSI from Redhat 7 to Redhat 6 when the boot mode is order specified causes the VM not to boot Blocked accounts using SAML authentication from linking with IBMid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181214/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181214/</guid>
      <description>Portal More style tweaks to the manage order forms. API Fix failed verifyOrder for dedicated GPU orders Backend Fixed an issue preventing CCI_CANCEL Events from getting properly added to the Event_Log Enable MZR support by deploying load balancer to multiple datacenters if they are MZR enabled and VLAN spanning is enabled Fix issue where hourlyBillingFlag changed status after a guest was cancelled but before the guest was actually deleted. Catalog Make Package 200 Presets 533, 535, 783, 785, 787, 789 available in the following sites (this is in addition to the sites they are already in) DAL12, FRA04, FRA05, LON04, LON05, LON06, PAR01, MIL01, SYD04, SYD05, TOK04, TOK05, WDC04, WDC06, WDC07 Remove Package 200 Presets 533, 535, 783, 785, 787, 789 from the following sites: DAL01, DAL07, WDC01 Adding additional configurations to package 801 (VSI containers) IaaS Flavor CPU RAM 1st Disk 2nd Disk M1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181207/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181207/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix SoftLayer IBMid invitation emails to have the correct portal URLs for accounts that are or will be linked The link cloud.ibm.com/devices should be cloud.ibm.com/resources Fixed a bug where a cookie is used to display the users preference in Ticket Status pane was not being created by default. Improve caching of customer SSH keys on the public portal to display recently added keys. API Fix Customer::parentCheck not to skip the check for a user without a childUser Updated pciDevices relationship to has_many for DedicatedHost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 30, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181130/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix incorrect URL generation when reconfiguring certain shopping cart items, from checkout. Add billing agreements link in manage billing items page API Fixes a bug retrieving a list of child users for one parent user through the API. Don&amp;rsquo;t allow creating a user in PENDING state on input to API, PENDING is a system state </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181116/</guid>
      <description>Portal For capacity restricted pricing that is billed with usage, return the correct usage pricing when verifying and placing orders. Control Portal Login Redirects in cloud.ibm.com domains Fix redirect error for ordering.cloud.ibm.com API Fix edge case for rule validation that would mistakenly determine an item was conflicting when the given item was NOT being upgraded. IBM Cloud CDN - Hotlink protection configurable through API to prevent unauthorized use of a CDN&amp;rsquo;s content Remove the PPTP_VPN_ALLOWED trait from all customer accounts Fixed an issue causing SoftLayer_User_Customer::addBulkPortalPermission to timeout Added methods to allow Brand Agents and Brand Managers the ability to disable accounts Premium VLANs are now available to order, or upgrade to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 9, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181109/</guid>
      <description>API Added IAM authorization flag to user objects. Small fixes to PERMISSION classes; methods that perform bulk actions Add BDS_WAIT Transaction Status for chassis transfers Improve authenticating an API client with IAM API key or IAM token. Enforce IP address restrictions during IAM API key authentication Add the createDate and modifyDate parameters to the security group rules. Backend Add Event Logs for SAML Add and Edit </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 2, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181102/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181102/</guid>
      <description>API Add SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::isVirtualPrivateCloudNode Defaulting simple ordering ( SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject()) to suspend for hourly SAN based VSIs Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::getBootModeOptions(). The boot mode options are dependent on the firmware installed on the server. It will always return at least [&amp;ldquo;BIOS&amp;rdquo;] or [&amp;ldquo;BIOS&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;UEFI&amp;rdquo;] for web servers. If the server is not a web server (e.g. HSM), return an empty list. Backend Fixed an issue where some reserved instance guests were not showing up in SoftLayer_Account::getVirtualGuests() Adds a requirement for customers to have the same level of permissions to order a reserved capacity as is currently required to order virtual and hardware servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 30, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181030/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181030/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixes bug where MDMS validation wasn&amp;rsquo;t getting the correct countries when checking COS Bucket. API Correct Hardware_Server and Hardware_SecurityModule port speed API behavior change announcement dates. Please review API documentation for the following Hardware_Server APIs if you use them:&#xA;setPrivateNetworkInterfaceSpeed&#xA;setPublicNetworkInterfaceSpeed&#xA;shutdownPrivatePort&#xA;shutdownPublicPort&#xA;activatePublicPort&#xA;activatePrivatePort&#xA;Provides the usagePrices property on SoftLayer_Container_Product_Order, which is set after verifying or placing orders for usage-based service offerings that provides the usage pricing which will be used when billing the services on the order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 22, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181022/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Changes On January 14, 2019 the following API methods will have their behavior changed. Please check each method&amp;rsquo;s documentation for details.&#xA;setPrivateNetworkInterfaceSpeed setPublicNetworkInterfaceSpeed shutdownPrivatePort shutdownPublicPort activatePublicPort activatePrivatePort The same methods in Hardware_SecurityModule will also be effected. However Virtual_Guest will NOT be effected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 18, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181018/</guid>
      <description>Portal Manage Reserved Capacity Groups permissions is now visible from viewUser account page. API Include each price&amp;rsquo;s item attributes in the response from verifyOrder and placeOrder API calls Add EventLog Types for Security Question Answers Add Event Logs for Security Question and Answers Add Event Logs for External Binding Edit Fixed an issue where more VSIs than the maximum were able to be provisioned inside a placement group. API Authentication Edit EventLog metaData is now an array Fix SoftLayer_Virtual_ReservedCapacityGroup::occupiedInstances bug Added SoftLayer_Network:connectPrivateEndpointService() Added SoftLayer_Network:disconnectPrivateEndpointService() Added an order_by to the networkDevice key so that the A side of the router would show on querries rather than B side Add UEFI Supported attribute to Hardware_Component_Model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 4, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20181004/</guid>
      <description>API Prevents $0 reserved capacity instance prices from showing up as available upgrade prices. Remove the SoftLayer_Billing_Order_Note data type. Fix date filter for permission logs https://api.softlayer.com/v3.1/sldn/rest/SoftLayer_Event_Log/getAllObjects.json?objectFilter={ &amp;#34;eventName&amp;#34;:{&amp;#34;operation&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Permission/Resource change&amp;#34;}, &amp;#34;eventCreateDate&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;operation&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;betweenDate&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;options&amp;#34;:[ {&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;startDate&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;:[&amp;#34;10/02/2018&amp;#34;]}, {&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;endDate&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;value&amp;#34;:[&amp;#34;10/03/2018&amp;#34;]} ] } } Backend Fixed bug with dedicated host evacuations. Improved speed for transferring images between locations </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 28, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180928/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180928/</guid>
      <description>API Fix additional issues with the hourlyBillingFlag API property on SoftLayer_Hardware and SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest. add a permissionCascadeFlag to SoftLayer_User_Customer::removeBulkPortalPermissions and SoftLayer_User_Customer::removePortalPermission, which if set to true will remove the permissions for the user and children users. Refactor customer editObject. Allows customers to submit a placementGroupId on a virtual guest object when ordering a VSI. Expose SLDN on placementGroupId and the placementGroup key in SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest Add the view event log permission check to SoftLayer_Event_Log::getAllObjects Deliver new function to import VSI image from IBM Cloud Object Storage (IBM COS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 20, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180920/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180920/</guid>
      <description>Portal Remove SSH keys and provision scripts from the checkout page in www.softlayer.com Fix an issue preventing the ordering of Multi-VLAN Firewalls. API Prevent ticket generation for order placed through Direct Link API service and sort the vlan list before assigning the next vlan for a provider. Direct Link: Allow Deletion of connection only of Connection is deleted from Equinix side Deprecate the SoftLayer_Ticket_Survey class Added SoftLayer_Network:isConnectedToPrivateEndpointService() with a return of a bool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180914/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180914/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Created GT_GC_CAPABLE Disk Image Attribute. Added image transfer region group type Added method getValidCountriesForRegion to return countries assigned to the region if it has pricing info set. Added SoftLayer_Virtual_PlacementGroup Added SoftLayer_Virtual_PlacementGroup_Rule Fix issues where hourlyBillingFlag properties were returning an invalid value. Backend Ability to provision encrypted images on Public VSIs </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180907/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180907/</guid>
      <description>Portal Update tax display for &amp;rsquo;new&amp;rsquo; customers and avoid showing stale information regarding the taxes for their order. API Added SoftLayer_Tag::deleteTag() Added SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::removeTags() and SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::removeTags() Added SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::sentTestReclaimScheduledAlert() to allow for testing of the transient webhook service Added SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request::getDeviceModel() Backend Zero dollar invoices will now use the closed_complete state Added cleanup logic for ipmi connectivity issues during reclaims. The Lenovo SR630 motherboard should be purchasable with a TPM module </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 31, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180831/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180831/</guid>
      <description>Portal Performance improvements at order checkout. Correct the tab for the private network only dedicated host instance options in the order forms. Clarified the error message presented when a disabled account attempts to create a user. Support for dedicated GPU hosts Changed GPU column on order form for GPU flavor to show description instead of capacity. API A resultLimit of 1 was returning empty array using v3.1 in the endpoint. Ensure the firewallType returns the appropriate value for SoftLayer_Network_Vlan_Firewall API to support rebuilding a vSRX HA cluster Implementing creating/updating Gateway Member Attribute records for gateway member(s).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 24, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180824/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180824/</guid>
      <description>API Fix bug that allows SL customer to change password via direct soap request without providing appropriate security question parameters. API orders from quote now properly validate the quote status Refactors and updates the getWebCcAuthenticationDetails Disabled auto registration of a subnet during subnet assignment. SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration::createObject will validate the detailReferences(SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Details), and network properties to better detect and error on conflicts. SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration::createObjects was added to enable creation of multiple registrations for the provided detailReferences(SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Registration_Details).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180815/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180815/</guid>
      <description>Portal Pre-select the first host in the Dedicated Hosts table when ordering a DH. API Correct validation when creating a quote Event logs for 2FA status change Adding the ability for customers to delete tags. Add check for SOAP request call to prevent commit in customer&amp;rsquo;s removeSecurityAnswers method. Added ability to filter Event_Logs based on username https://api.softlayer.com/rest/v3.1/SoftLayer_Event_Log/getAllObjects.json? resultLimit=0,100&amp;amp; objectFilter={&amp;#34;eventName&amp;#34;:{&amp;#34;operation&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;Permission/Resource change&amp;#34;}, &amp;#34;label&amp;#34;:{&amp;#34;operation&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;sl205-mb-test02&amp;#34;}} Fix bug to not allow editing of &amp;rsquo;name&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;category&amp;rsquo; in SoftLayer_Network_Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 8, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180808/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180808/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue in the Bluemix control portal rendering the wrong template when an order failed. API Fix incorrect totals calculation when using the getCurrentBillingTotal service methods on guests, hardware, and dedicated hosts. Exposing Device model through SLDN for a device that is assigned to a mass data migration request. Added SoftLayer_Network_Gateway::getCapacity() Added CUSTOMER_EXTERNAL_BINDING_ACTIVATE and CUSTOMER_EXTERNAL_BINDING_DEACTIVATE SoftLayer_Event_Log_Type Added validation around name field when creating brands through the API Added API/Class called SoftLayer_Network_Gateway_Member_Attribute Backend Restore ability to cancel global IP addresses Fixed an issue where users were unable to create federated user by SAML authentication if the &amp;ldquo;sn&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;givenName&amp;rdquo; are long Added more verbose metadata information on some eventlog entries </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 3, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180803/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180803/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed currency translations on the order page. Fix a bug that was preventing discounts from being properly applied to certain promos with special configuration rules. Updates the logo on invoices (pdf and Excel) from IBM Bluemix to IBM Cloud. Add Learn More link to Checkout page next to SSH keys label. Update order forms to support new Archive metrics for Cloud Object Storage. Allow customers to subscribe or unsubscribe unplanned incidents and maintenance events per severity level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 27, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180727/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180727/</guid>
      <description>Portal Public changes to our WWW order form to improve the experience when applying promo codes to an order Fix an issue where pricing was not properly filtered based on other order form selection Update redirect to control for login to a HTTP code 302 API Prevent fatal error when loading active usage prices Fix rule validator for IPv6 addresses when creating firewall rules When a .vhd or .iso file is imported the API should not allow any encryption parameter to be specified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 20, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180720/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180720/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed numerical format for a variety of currencies. Fix an issue that would&amp;rsquo;ve incorrectly determined a promotion as not meeting location requirements for certain configurations. Fixes a bug that allowed users to select an irrelevant datacenter when ordering CDN. The datacenter selection did not break the order, it was just ignored. This fix clears up possible confusion. API Relaxed validation rules for the country state field on account creation which was erroneously made more restrictive in a recent release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180713/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180713/</guid>
      <description>Portal Update ReCAPTCHA to version 2 Added functionality for legacy, non-email formatted IBMids to be persisted during account creation. Customer created tickets that have managed hardware should route to the managed services queue. Improve order form load time for uncached packages Fix issue where states for countries that are not US or Canada were failing on SSL certificate orders. Data centers should now be shown for bare metal servers in all portals Multiple usability updates for order forms API Fixed a bug that was causing customer power strip power cycle API calls to fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180706/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180706/</guid>
      <description>Portal Validation of EncryptedToken fails if the impersonating user is an brand agent Remove invalid datacenters from fixed config bare metal order form Allow non-empty COS Buckets to be placed for MDMS orders. API Duplicate firewall rules should not allowed to be added A new property has been added to SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image, isEncrypted. This value returns if the disk on the image is encrypted. Backend Fix the load balancer deletion failure which keeps the load balancer in delete_pending state after billing item gets cancelled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 29, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180629/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180629/</guid>
      <description>Portal Allow Master User to clear security questions for users on account. Fix issue when ordering SSL certs for non-US organizational addresses that had a state Updates to dedicated vsi and dedicated hosts order forms for encryption Fixed an issue where a customer cannot delete the CDN service Billing Item from Customer Portal API The Permission/Resource change event log type should only show for the customer with the GENERATE_PERMISSION_REPORTS set. Exposes the setupFeeDeferralMonths property for the SoftLayer_Billing_Invoice_Item service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 21, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180621/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180621/</guid>
      <description>Portal Evault Performance enhancements. Evault Password enhancements. API Blocked deactivated templates from being pushed to cache. Backend Have account disable/enable cascade to users Corrects Australia/West time zone to be correct GMT offset. Fix missing paren pair in cloud init attribute validation Fixes an issue that caused some Bring Your Own License orders to go to Pending Finance Approval. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180614/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180614/</guid>
      <description>Portal Missing pending transaction details information during volume modification process. This change will allow customers to see the status of their ordered volume modification in portal Improve order forms speed Direct Link - Backend Edit related changes for control portal Add localization of currencies and countries to order page currency selector. API Modify SoftLayer_Event_Log::getAllEventNames to return events names without brand references Added pciDevices and pciDeviceAllocationStatus fields to the DedicatedHost object. These fields are mirrors of the underlying host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 8, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180608/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180608/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue when placing orders with a state of &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; Fixing a bug where selecting None for multiselect options would not update the summary total on the order form. Loading conflicts out of band on order forms &amp;amp; move WWW order form assets to CDN API Improve getActiveTransactionStatus performance Fix issues with some storage group validation edge cases </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 31, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180531/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180531/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where the device list wouldn&amp;rsquo;t display any devices. Correct Customer Add User form when state is &amp;lsquo;Other&amp;rsquo; Updated display logic to not show null userData values without blocking other attributes that are null API longName field is now required when creating brands in the API Added validation for keyId in &amp;lsquo;removeApiAuthenticationKey&amp;rsquo; method Enables customers to upgrade or downgrade the number of GPUs on a virtual guest. Backend Changed HSM password generator to not use vowels and to use Gemalto provided special characters for HSM passwords.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 24, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180524/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180524/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue when a user with TOTP has a successful login after fewer than 10 failed attempts, the previous failed attempts are not cleared. Customers were unable to create EU only tickets. This change fixes the filter to pull EU data centers. Adds a checkbox to the WWW order form on the save quote dialog that allows the user to accept the GDPR terms and conditions. This check box must be checked to place a quote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180517/</guid>
      <description>Portal Add Virtuozzo transaction provisioning and reload groups and icon. This changes a link in the footer of the Www Store pages This issue removes Google Tag Manager and Adobe Target from the SoftLayer Www template API Fixes a bug that causes the euCompliantFlag on SoftLayer_Location to always return false. Direct Link - Fix the error message to indicate problem clearly when edit fails Direct Link - Increase Vendor Circuit and Vendor Name length from 30 to 40.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 10, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180510/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180510/</guid>
      <description>Portal Stopped creating surveys related to Bluemix assets in the SoftLayer portal API The IQN of a host can no longer be changed when that host has assigned storage volumes. This is to ensure consistency within the system Making new storage authentication error messages viewable Backend Change how &amp;ldquo;reset Master user IBMid link&amp;rdquo; treats the user from whom the IBMid is &amp;ldquo;stolen&amp;rdquo; in a linked account pair. Show the correct linkSpeed for Dedicated and Dedicated Hosting tenants correctly Fixed bug where only the first VSI guest was added to the outage ticket instead of all VSI guests associated with that host and account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180426/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180426/</guid>
      <description>Portal Add boot mode to order forms when provisioning a public vsi. Adds order form validation for the VLAN and SSH Key selection for just HSM. Remove the &amp;ldquo;Save As Quote&amp;rdquo; option from the order forms when the order has products that are not currently quotable. Foreign language usability updates to WWW order forms API Fixed the bug where the following services are returning tickets to which the current user doesn&amp;rsquo;t have access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 13, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180413/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180413/</guid>
      <description>Portal Add GPU column to flavors table for GPU Flavors Display link to privacy policy on order forms API Fix issue where dedicated host orders would fail order verification. Bandwidth Usage Detail contains the data used to billing bandwidth at the end of the billing cycle. The timestamps used to pull metrics is using GMT instead of Central. This issue validates that BYOL and CloudInit attributes are set to 1 when creating a template via the api.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 6, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180406/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180406/</guid>
      <description>Portal adds the sshKeys selector back into the confirmation page when ordering a hardware security module. Remove forums.softlayer.com links. API Make createObject orders for hourly SAN virtual servers use correct package when presets are account restricted. Fixed getPortalLoginToken function registering a failed login before it registers a successful login Fix bug preventing scheduler from being used when request comes from SLDN Terminating Status is added when guest vsi are being reclaimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 30, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180330/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180330/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added feature to notify customers about host outages to the Virtual/viewMemberDetails/ page Removes Provision Scripts and User Data sections from the CHECKOUT page when ordering HSM devices. API Fixed SoftLayer_Scale_Group&amp;rsquo;s editObject method to automatically scale the group up or down appropriately when the desiredMemberCount parameter is specified Fixes an issue that prevented the &amp;lsquo;IOPS&amp;rsquo; ORM value from being updated for performance replicas. Added SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image::getAvailableBootModes() Method Expose Account::securityLevel Round up the Load Balancer as a Service telemetry monitoring metrics value to 3 decimal points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180315/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180315/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adds the Hardware Security Module(HSM) to the manage order form. Adds a Learn More link to the sub-section header for HSM. Improve order forms rendering speed API Added SoftLayer_Network_Interconnect_Tenant::getAllPortLabelsWithCurrentUseage Adds SERIAL_NUMBER property to SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Iscsi volumes which can be used as an objectFilter Provide API to retrieve load balancer monitoring metrics and ssl ciphers Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancerMonitoringMetricDataPoint Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::getListenerTimeSeriesData Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::getSslCiphers Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::updateSslCiphers Backend Added HSM 750 compatibility to provisioning workflow Blocks monthly suspend-able virtual server orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180314/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180314/</guid>
      <description>Added SLDN Documentation We have finally retired the old SLDN site, and migrated its content over to softlayer.github.io.&#xA;The following content types have been added, in addition to the existing release notes, and code examples.&#xA;Articles Blogs Services and their associated Methods Datatypes If you notice any issues with the content here, please create an issue on our github page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes March 9, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180309/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180309/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Add new account attribute type &amp;lsquo;NEW_ASSIGN_NETWORK_ENABLED&amp;rsquo; Updates the simple ordering methods, createObject and getCreateObjectOptions, to properly handle ordering suspend-able virtual servers. Backend Addresses a problem where SoftLayer_Network_Storage::enableSnapshots() wasn&amp;rsquo;t working properly for Weekly snapshot schedules. Block public image creation when incorrect location data is sent in. Removed trailing and ending spaces from ipAddressRestriction value before creating a user. Added try/catch block to Virtual Guest workflow in reclaim guest to catch exception where a Scale Group tries to provision a VSI to meet the member requirement when a VSI is reclaimed (causing the Scale Group to drop below the minimum).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API SERVICE DISRUPTION March 1, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180301/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180301/</guid>
      <description>API SERVICE DISRUPTION: March 1st, 2018 IBM Cloud will stop supporting TLS 1.0 and 1.1 on api.softlayer.com and api.service.softlayer.com&#xA;What Is Happening? On March 1, 2018 at 0900 UTC (0300 CDT) IBM Cloud Infrastructure will stop supporting TLS 1.0 and 1.1 encryption on api.softlayer.com and api.service.softlayer.com; these API endpoints will only support callers using TLS 1.2 encryption levels or higher.&#xA;When Will It Happen? On March 1, 2018 at 0900 UTC (0300 CDT) TLS 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes February 28, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180228/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180228/</guid>
      <description>Portal User should be get locked for 30 minutes when they enter invalid TOTP code more than 10 times. Remove forum link from Notification Messages Modifies translation text for the order checkout page to use &amp;lsquo;user data&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;metadata.&amp;rsquo; API Check if active user is parent of user being edited dutring addPortalPermission and removePortalPermission Support forced delete of scale groups regardless of status Added http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/getBootMode updated validationRules for partitionName to allow for slashes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180216/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improvement to verbiage shown for servers with active billing for an inactive package. GPU Flavor prices were not factoring the price of the GPU. Fixed an issue where the master user could set themselves as &amp;ldquo;VPN_ONLY&amp;rdquo; user. API Backend Fix Reloads being blocked when a user suppresses the email for RELOAD_COMPLETE Fix Micron Hard Drive Storage Group Member&amp;rsquo;s Grow Flag Update automated messaging update on Data Transfer Request tickets Add dal10 to the list of data centers supporting security groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180207/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180207/</guid>
      <description>Portal Allow customers to suppress order emails API Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;.. to change a user link&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;rsquo;to edit a user&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;Access Denied. Only the Master user..&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;Account 1234 is authenticated by IBMid&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called for subuser Validator added for bare metal servers orders that use the userData field, the allowed length is 2000 characters. Update getCreateObjectOptions to return Spot options Child user is now unable to delete his/her own Phone Factor authentication using the APIs A bootMode property is added to the SoftLayer_Container_Product_Order_Virtual_Guest class to allow customers to specify the mode the VSI should be booted in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 22, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180122/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180122/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixes bug when checking for available vGPU resources. Update favicon on IBM cloud template Fixed an informative popup to properly display entire username when deleting or disabling a user with a long username API SoftLayer_Network_Storage::getAllowableDatacenters() performance improvements Added a SUPPORTED_BOOT_MODE attribute to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image_Attribute_Type class to hold what boot modes the image can support. Update SLDN doc for Virtual_Guest.createObject to add Security Group parameters Replace checking for parentId with isMasterUser flag for add/remove device access Added quantity validation on StaaS orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180115/</guid>
      <description>SLCLI https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/releases/tag/v5.4.0&#xA;Changes: https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/compare/v5.3.2...v5.4.0&#xA;Upgraded Requests and Urllib3 library to latest. This allows the library to make use of connection retries, and connection pools. This should prevent the client from crashing if the API gives a connection reset / connection timeout error&#xA;reworked wait_for_ready function for virtual, and added to hardware managers.&#xA;fixed block/file iops in the slcli block|file detail view&#xA;Added sub items to hw detail --price, removed reverse PTR entries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 3, 2018</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2018/20180103/</guid>
      <description>Portal Replace &amp;ldquo;formerly IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;formerly SoftLayer&amp;rdquo; in all affected templates. API Autoscale: Prevent Multiple Scale Actions per Policy. https://stackoverflow.com/questions/39696067/invalid-guest-template-for-autoscale-in-sl Only block BYOL sharing and making it public if the software description is a licensed product. Adds support for Spot instances to simple VSI ordering. spotGuestFlag would be used to indicate in a createObject() parameter block if the order is for a Spot Instance. http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/createObject Added an API to tell if an account is eligible to link with PaaS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 11, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171206/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171206/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adds warning messages to that will pop to alert EU only processing users that they are selecting a data center or package that it not EU compliant. This change will add a checkbox on the WWW order from checkout page that allows customers to opt-in to EU localized support. For a customer that opts-in, any servers they have in an EU datacenter will only be serviced by technicians also in the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 04, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171204/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fix issue where LVM was set on storage groups erroneously when editing a configuration on the order form. Add a new order approval e-mail notification template for SAP Certified servers. API Added account validation support for combining unicode characters, such as diacritical arabic characters. Added new check to prevent multiple partitions being set with grow flag. Allow the customers who does not have USER_MANAGE permission to see their own login attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171127/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171127/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message. Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group. Backend Added more validation around partition sizeing Changed the wording on raid alert tickets Fixed an issue reclaiming Virtual Servers Fixes bug when trying to find reverse DNS records. Fixed an issue with account link invitations not getting a proper activation url Fixed a bug preventing some provisioning transactions from completing automatically </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171115/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message. Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group. API Added more validation to ordering Direct Link products through the SLAPI to mirror validation done by the portal Adds functionality to allow upgrade for Fortigate firewall appliances Backend Fixed an issue where disk groups would be improperly partitioned when a HOT_SPARE volume was present Allowed various unicode hyphens through account validation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171120/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited. Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid. API Enforce the same set of input requirements for SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject in a linked account, as for a non-linked account. Backend Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 13, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171113/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited. Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid. API Enforce the same set of input requirements for SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject in a linked account, as for a non-linked account. Backend Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171025/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added 2 links to the order approval email when ordering MDMS. The links will guide the customers to the User Guide and device Checklist. Removed the warning on the order forms that 2nd disk is required for Balanced local flavor VSIs. API When a user is created with double quotes in email address from API, Error message pointed to a problem with username. This has been fixed to show the correct error message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171012/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an error that was being displayed when an end user clicks on Reconfigure System Configuration link on complete order page. API Removed the ability to edit or view a users profile via the API if the users status is set to cancel_pending. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 05, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20171005/</guid>
      <description>Portal IBM Bluemix Load Balancers are now live in the customer portal. Performance and Endurance Block volumes can no longer have their LUN Id changed unless all host authorizations are first removed. This is to ensure synchronization between the customer portal and the storage systems. API None Backend Added more logic when auto-scaling Virtual Guests. The new logic checks the dates in the logs first and makes sure there are no other provisions or reclaims within the cooldown period of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170927/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170927/</guid>
      <description>Portal Security Groups are now live in the customer portal at https://control.softlayer.com/security/securitygroups. Pushed some code to tidy up the Virtual Guest Family size order forms. API Created the enableEuLocalizedProcessing and disableEuLocalizedProcessing methods for the SoftLayer_Account. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 21, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170921/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170921/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue where a subset of DCs where not displaying the 1,2,4 or 8 core options for Dedicated Host Virtual Guests. Pushed code that that corrected a display issue when ordering Dedicated Host Virtual Guests. When selecting Local drive Virtual Guests do not show the 3rd, 4th, and 5th disk options. API Added validation to prevent monthly LBaaS orders via the API since the SoftLayer_Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer service is only available with hourly billing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 14, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170914/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170914/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where standard disk prices were being incorrectly hidden for some datacenters during the order process. Virtual Guest Family sizes are now live on the order form. You can read more about the Family sizes here. Added new functionality to the order forms to support multiple disk controllers for bare metal offerings. Added the following new offerings in the Bluemix catalog: Container Registry, Informix On Cloud, Master Data Management on Cloud, Information Server on Cloud, JanusGraph, Monitoring, and Log Analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 7, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170907/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170907/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Exposed the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request, SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request_KeyContact, and SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request_Statu for interacting with the Mass Data Migration offering. Fixed an issue with the SoftLayer_Billing_Currency_ExchangeRate::getAllCurrencyExchangeRates method. When customers would supply the current days date, the call would not return any exchange rate information. Backend Fixed a bug with ISO importing. The fix now allows import transactions to complete even without a Software Description set on the ISO. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170824/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170824/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Fixed a bug where cancellation tickets were not being closed after the cancellation had completed. Corrected an issue where Security Groups were not being properly applied to the private network of Windows VSI provisions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 17, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170817/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170817/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue on the order form where Dedicated Host Instance orders were not showing all size options available in some Datacenters. API Corrected a bug where using SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject to order a dedicated host instance with SAN disks would error out with Unable to find a price for block device 0. Backend Pushed code to handle active/active clustering for the Cloud Load Balancing offering. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170810/</guid>
      <description>Portal Opened up Security Groups beta to more users. Added London 04 to the Datacenters that can utilize Security Groups. You can now configure the VSI on the checkout page to add security groups. Customer Portal Audit Logs now report Security group changes. You can now see when a security group is attached or removed from a Virtual Guest. API Fixed File/Block Storage replicationStatus key to always return a string. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 3, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170803/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170803/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added the new Dedicated Host offering to the catalog. A dedicated host is a physical server with workload capacity entirely dedicated to a single clients use. Corrected an issue where customers were unable to attach more than one dedicated host to a ticket. API Exposed the SoftLayer_Virtual_DedicatedHost Service. This allows you to interact with the new Dedicated Host offering. Added the addBulkDedicatedHostAccess method to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170726/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170726/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Deprecated the blueIdAuthenticationRequiredFlag method and replaced it with the ibmIdAuthenticationRequiredFlag method for the SoftLayer_Account service. Added isoCodeAlphaThree to the returned data for the SoftLayer_Locale_Country::getCountries and SoftLayer_Locale_Country::getAvailableCountries methods. This returns the 3 character ISO code for a country. Backend Added logic for Brazil and India to support local currency for billing. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 19, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170719/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170719/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Added the getLocalCurrencyExchangeRate method to the SoftLayer_Billing_Invoice service. This allows users to retrieve the exchange rate used for billing an invoice. Users can now call SoftLayer_Network_Storage::createOrUpdateLunId to change the LUN ID on a block volume. For example, if a user is trying to access multiple volumes from a single initiator, then it is possible that some volumes will have the same LUN ID which may cause conflicts on the initiator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170706/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue where applying security groups may cause errors during the provision of a Virtual Guest. API Pushed code to resolve an issue with the resultLimit for SoftLayer_Ticket_Subject::getAllObjects method. Before the fix the API was returning less data than the limit set. Addressed an issue with the PHP Library for the SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_Global::route method. If the endpoint IP address provided is associated with an unrouted subnet a fatal error was being returned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 28, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170628/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added the ability to order the Mass Data Migration Service. This offering can only be ordered by the master account user. It allows for the secure migration of up to 120TB of data per device into / out of Cleversafe Object Storage using physical storage appliances housed in waterproof, tamper-evident, shockproof cases. Official Documentation. API Resolved an issue that was allowing customers to order duplicate volumes without specifying a datacenter location using placeOrder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 22, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170622/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170622/</guid>
      <description>Portal Released code to support Volume Duplication. This offering adds the ability to order a new volume, pre-loaded with the contents of a File or Block Volume or Volume Replica, or a snapshot of a Volume or Volume Replica. Changed the default option for monitoring from Basic to None, for VSI order forms. Added the ability to assign Security Groups to an interface on the Virtual Guest order form for customers that are enrolled in the Beta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170608/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170608/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrected an issue in the portal where VMware ESXI 5.5 was not showing the licensing cost disclaimer on the order summary page in quotes and at checkout. Added additional Flex pricing information and external documentation links to the Cloud Object Storage S3 order page. API Pushed code that improves the performance of SoftLayer_Network_Storage::createSnapshot on Endurance and Performance volumes. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 1, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170601/</guid>
      <description>Portal When a server is reloaded customers now have the option to enable LVM on the storage groups during the reload. Added support for performance pricing when you duplicate storage volumes. Rolled out the ability for a user to create a new volume from an existing volume or snapshot. When creating the new volume a user will have the ability to either keep the configuration of the new volume (size, IOPS tier, etc) or make changes to the configuration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170524/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170524/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrected an issue that was causing the order form to not display hardware selection when loading from a Flex Image template. API None Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 18, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170518/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170518/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was causing SAP Certified servers to not be orderable from a Quote. API None Backend Resolve an issue where upgrading a Bluemix account to add infrastructure services would occasionally fail but still upgrade the account. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 18, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/20170518/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/20170518/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was causing SAP Certified servers to not be orderable from a Quote. API None Backend Resolve an issue where upgrading a Bluemix account to add infrastructure services would occasionally fail but still upgrade the account. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170510/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170510/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where it was possible to order a clone API Added the getHardwarePools method to the SoftLayer_Account service. Backend Resolved an issue that was causing Virtual Guest image templates to not be imported properly due to mismatched software descriptions. This only affected Windows image template imports. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 3, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170503/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170503/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved a bug that was causing duplicate pricing information to be shown for storage options on the portal order form. API Fixed SoftLayer_Network_Storage::storageTierLevel to always return a string value instead of a SoftLayer_Billing_Item object. Backend Fixed a bug that would automatically allow inactive image templates to be used for VSI OS Reloads. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170426/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170426/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Pushed code to resolve an issue where mixed case IBMId accounts were unable to upgrade to a Pay as you Go Bluemix Developer Services account. Resolved an issue that was causing NetScaler provisions to fail due to the license not being bound to a valid MAC address on the host system. Pushed code which added the requirement of using an IBMid in order to link a Platform as a Service account to an Infrastructure as a Service account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 19, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170419/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170419/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue that prevented the relevant locations from being returned on replicas with Account Defined Networking. Fixed an issue that prevented the relevant mounting point from being returned on accounts with Account Defined Networking. Resolved a bug which allowed servers to be ordered with IPv6 subnets for the primary interfaces. This causes servers to fail provisioning. Added userData field to the order forms for Bare Metal Servers. Previously only supported on Virtual Guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170412/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170412/</guid>
      <description>Portal Rolled out code that improves order form performance on page load time. Fixed issue where order validation was not always consistent between regular orders and orders from quotes, such as with hostname and domain validation. Corrected the error message when customers without the MANAGE_USER permission attempted to create sub-users. API None Backend Fixed a bug causing customer ISO image templates to fail to transfer to new Datacenters. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 5, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170405/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170405/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed a bug to enforce correct cancellation order of volumes with replicas. Previously it was possible to cancel storage with replica, but the process would fail as the replica must be cancelled first. The portal will now direct to you first cancel the replica volume. API Updated the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest service&amp;rsquo;s getCreateObjectOptions method to not show options that are no longer available, such as old operating systems that are no longer supported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 29, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170329/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170329/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrected an issue with customers being unable to claim an order quote for Performance or Endurance storage. Fixed an issue where subusers on an account were not able to order Netscaler VPX services even with the appropriate portal permissions. Exception message was unclear when a user without the &amp;rsquo;ticket add&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;ticket view&amp;rsquo; permissions tried to create an upgrade order. New change accurately indicates that the user must have these two permissions in order to create an upgrade order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170320/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue with the customer portal timing out with a large number of billing items. API Prevent server errors when using SoftLayer_Product_Package getItemsFromImageTemplate. Backend Fixed an issue provisioning Hourly Bare Metal servers that would require manual intervention to resolve. Fixes a problem that was preventing snapshots from being registered by the poller job. Allow hyphens in emails for IBMid Fixed an issue with offline migrations on windows virtual machines Update Hourly Bare Metal servers to check for mis-configurations before considering available </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170308/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170308/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrected an issue with ordering Fixed Configuration Servers. When a customer selected an operating system before a datacenter on fixed configurations servers the portal would show errors about storage groups being needed. API Added the getBuckets and getCloudObjectStoragePolicy methods to the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Hub_Cleversafe_Account service. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 02, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170302/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170302/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Resolved a bug when calling the methods failoverToReplicant, failbackFromReplicant, or immediateFailoverToReplicant from the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Iscsi class instead of the base SoftLayer_Network_Storage, in which the method would return true, but the process would not be started. Backend Created an internal tool to unlink Bluemix and SoftLayer accounts. Customers can now open a ticket to request their Bluemix and SoftLayer accounts be unlinked. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 23, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170223/</guid>
      <description>Portal Portal Exception message was unclear when a user without &amp;rsquo;ticket add&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;ticket view&amp;rsquo; permissions tried to create an upgrade order. New change accurately indicates that the user must have these two permissions in order to create an upgrade order. API None Backend Fixed two separate bugs in Endurance and Performance Storage provisioning where provisions were stalling due to API call timeout. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 16, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170216/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170216/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was preventing punny code domains from being added using the &amp;lsquo;Add Bulk Domains&amp;rsquo; tool in the customer portal. API None Backend Added some backend code to help automation issues related to sending automated password reset emails. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170208/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170208/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added a customerWaitTime field on the ticket search page in the customer portal. The customerWaitTime is the time the customer has been waiting for a response on a ticket. Multiple updates by the customer have no effect on this field and a reply by an employee resets the timer to zero. Pushed fix that tests that only numbers, letters, and spaces are allowed for all of the titles for contacts when trying to order an SSL certificate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170125/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170125/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where the &amp;ldquo;Add to Order&amp;rdquo; button overlaps dropdown list content when the list is too long API Published the SoftLayer_Network service for customers to interact with Customer Private Addressing. Refactored SoftLayer_Billing_Order_Quote::getRecalculatedOrderContainer(). Now returns the order container, instead of an array of an order container Backend Resolved an issue that was causing Virtual Guests to fail reboot when residing on a host that has been marked as disabled for new instances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170111/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170111/</guid>
      <description>Portal Pushed code to display the correct validation error when a number greater than 999 is used in the % field of Auto-Scaling policy actions. Previously a generic error message was displayed. API None Backend Updatd our Microsoft Proxy to handle new TLS requirements by .NET. A recent update to .NET for windows 2012 r2 added a much more strict TLS validation for powershell which in turn caused Post Install Scripts to fail during download.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 5, 2017</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2017/20170105/</guid>
      <description>Portal Pushed code to fix an issue that was causing an incorrect success message to be displayed when a user that has disabled/vpn only status clicked the Unlink button. Updated code to correct an error caused by a previously set VAT ID to be reported when the country selected does not use VAT. Updated the customer portal Order Form to include the new Cloud Object Storage general release offering. API None Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161219/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161219/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added VAT id support for Belarus. Added code to cleanup tag references on Virtual Guests/NetScalers/Image templates that have been deleted from a customers account. Added firewall verification during server orders that checks if a selected VLAN is eligible to be used with a server hardware firewall. Added code to filter out firewall-ineligible VLANs in VLAN selection on the order form when a server hardware firewall is being ordered. API None Backend Resolved an issue that was causing accounts to become locked when linking more than 7 accounts to an IBMId in a 30 minute window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 7, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161207/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161207/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Resolved an issue where SoftLayer_Brand::createObject requests coming in from the API were not creating an associated SoftLayer_Policy_Brand record. This bug resulted in user accounts created under the new brand to be unable to log in to the customer portal. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 14, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161114/</guid>
      <description>Portal Corrected an issue on the Bluemix order forms where the order form content appear in a different language based on the www.softlayer.com language cookie. The order forms are set to English until all language translations have been completed. Increased the space allowed for addresses when making payments via PayPal. The shorter space was causing PayPal transactions to fail when an account used a bunch of unicode characters. Fixed an issue where users might be immediately logged out after navigating to the order forms due to a non-public API call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161108/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161108/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improved the ordering form performance when provisioning (Beta) Object Storage offerings. API None Backend Pushed code that would stop the sending of order completed and approved emails for Bluemix services on Linked Accounts. Resolved an issue that was causing Guest disk billing items to have incorrect category codes after an OS reload order was placed. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161024/</guid>
      <description>Portal Changed portal layout and color scheme to match the new IBM Bluemix branding. Fixed an issue where SoftLayer tiered support customers could create a ticket with severity level higher than 4. API Added the getFileBlockEncryptedLocations method to the SoftLayer_Network_Storage service. This method can be used to get a list of SoftLayer_Location objects corresponding to datacenters which support Encryption at Rest for File and Block Storage. Backend When a user&amp;rsquo;s password expired, we are no longer automatically sending the password reset email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 17, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161017/</guid>
      <description>Portal Updated the page title and icon on the control portal compute order forms to reflect IBM Bluemix. API Resolved an issue with the getMappedAccounts method not correctly displaying the accountLinks section of the output. When any sub-brand is created by a brand master account it now automatically has the brand attribute ALLOW_ACCOUNT_CREATION set to 1.This resolves an issue what required Sales Operations to manually set the ALLOW_ACCOUNT_CREATION to 1 on sub-branded accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161011/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20161011/</guid>
      <description>Portal Updated the error message when ordering Public Subnets on a VLAN with HSRP. API Corrected an issue with the information for the getOpenIdRegistrationInfoFromCode method for the SoftLayer_User_Customer_OpenIdConnect service. Backend Fixed a potential issue that caused order verifications to fail in certain cases for accounts that have large numbers of Endurance or Performance volumes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160920/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160920/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Added the getOpenIdConnectMigrationState to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. This new method allows users to query whether an open invitation exists for a user. Backend Resolved an bug that was causing Netscaler provisioning issues due to hostname/domain validation errors. Fixed an issue with NO OS servers that was causing the Evault Bare Metal restore transaction to fail. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 12, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160912/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160912/</guid>
      <description>Portal Made changes to the order form to align with the change in colored branding to the customer portal. API Resolved issues of API response timeout when removing a users API key. This occurred on customer accounts with a lot of Object Storage users. Resolved an issue that was causing changes in products and catalog offerings to not be properly reflected in the SoftLayer_Product_Package_Server service. Added the getGlobalIdentifier method to the SoftLayer_Resource_Metadata service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 28, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160828/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160828/</guid>
      <description>Portal Pushed code fix that filters Vlans with respect to Datacenter selected when ordering Dedicated firewall. Pushed code fix that filters the severs based on Datacenter selected and the price capacity when ordering hardware firewall. Resolved an issue what was causing storage group templates with JBODs to not load correctly in the order forms. API Resolved a bug that was causing the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getMemoryMetricImageByDate method to return an incorrect graph. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160822/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160822/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Resolved a bug that was causing Resets of Dedicated Hardware Firewalls to fail if they were in a High Availablity Pair. Put code in place to ensure that cached disks from image templates are deleted when parent Virtual Disk Image is deleted. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 15, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160815/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160815/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Fixed an issue with servers not being immediately pulled from a Bandwidth pool upon cancellation. Improvements have been made to prevent static subnets and global IPs from being routed to administratively reserved IP addresses. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160808/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160808/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added some additional Language translations to the order forms in the customer portal. API None Backend Fixed a bug that was causing duplicate IP&amp;rsquo;s to be assigned to network components during Virtual Guest provisions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 1, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160801/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160801/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Resolved an issue with initial IPv6 routing for new subnet orders. Fixed a bug that was causing Evault for Virtual Guests to create unassociated billing items. Resolved an issue that was preventing SSH keys from being properly applied during an OS Reload. This only occurred if new software was added during the reload. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160725/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160725/</guid>
      <description>Portal Pushed code to allow for the ordering of Network VLAN&amp;rsquo;s from the customer portal. API Created the initiatePortalPasswordChangeByBrandAgent method for the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. The Brand Agent must have permission to Add Customer Accounts to the Brand in order to initiate the password reset in this way. Backend Resolved a bug that was causing Paypal orders to fail due to a missing property for Hourly Bare Metal servers. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160718/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160718/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed a bug that caused Public node to be highlighted when ordering a Private Virtual Guest. Fixes an issue that prevented the relevant media types from being returned in the ContentDelivery code for CDN origin mapping. API Resolved an issue with the getAllObjects method for the SoftLayer_Software_AccountLicense service returning an internal error. Backend Fixed an issue creating an IBMid with a mixed-case email address. Introduced case insensitivity in email address handling for IBMid creation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160711/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160711/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Rolled out the code that would allow customers to attach secondary Portable Storage Volumes to an existing Virtual Guest, create bootable images on those Portable Storage Volumes, detach them, then boot from those created volumes into new Virtual Guest&amp;rsquo;s. Resolved an issue that was causing OS Reloads to fail on Bare Metal servers that had inactive or deprecated service offerings. Fixed a bug in that caused Microsoft post provision scripts to fail when the script url contained an ampersand &amp;lsquo;&amp;amp;&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160706/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160706/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue that was causing the Subnet selection portion of the order process to be displayed when ordering a Network Gateway. Added a UI element to create or associate an IBM ID with an account during the order process. When creating new orders customers will be prompted to associate an existing IBM ID or create a new one. API Resolved an issue that was causing incorrect results from different parameters on REST/SOAP calls to Bandwidth functions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 27, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160628/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160628/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added support to determine if multipath is properly configured for block LUNs. API None Backend Resolved an issue that was causing OS reloads to fail on Virtual Guests during the image copy process. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160620/</guid>
      <description>Portal Enabled the ordering of new, larger CPU/RAM capacity Virtual Guests. API Resolved an issue that was causing the SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getBandwidthTotal method to fail to properly retrieve bandwidth data. Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 13, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160613/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160613/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API None Backend Resolved an issue that was preventing a server with Evault Storage from undergoing an Operating System reload. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 6, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160606/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160606/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was causing slow load times on a checkout of large orders. Fixed an issue in which only the &amp;lsquo;Default&amp;rsquo; health check option would function for UDP load balancer services. API None Backend Resolved an issue that was causing OS Reloads to fail on Bare Metal servers that were using NO_OS or where version locked. Updated the host and domain name validation logic to permit a domain comprised of all digits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 31, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160601/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160601/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved a bug that was causing the portal to report incorrect space allocation for Performance/Endurance Storage when creating a retention schedule. API Retired the traceroute, ping, and isPingable methods from the SoftLayer_Utility_Network service. Backend Resolved an issue that was causing newly created reverse zones for IPv6 subnets to be created using an older naming convention. Fixed a bug that would not allow an OS reload on a server running R1Soft backup server when the underlying OS was changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 23, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160523/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160523/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was producing an error when customers attempted place an order for an Indian data-center if the user&amp;rsquo;s account address did not have India as the country name. Updated the error message when a credit card order fails to specify the exact department to contact as well as provide contact information. API None Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 16, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160516/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160516/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was causing slow response during the order process. API None Backend Resolved a bug that was preventing orders from being edited on Branded Agent Portal accounts. Resolved an issue that was preventing the cancellation of the reclaim process if a server was part of a spare pool. Fixed an issue that was preventing orders for a vCenter Server Appliance license from going through. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 9, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160509/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160509/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue affecting the ability to edit a Saved Order or a Sales Order Quote. API None Backend Resolved an issue that was preventing a reclaim for Virtual Guests if they were powered off at the time of the cancellation request. Added translations for some email and ticket templates. Customers who set their user accounts to a non-English locale will see some emails and ticket updates translated into their locale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160425/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Resolved an issue with the syntax for getSnapshotRanges for the methods getMemoryMetricImage and getCpuMetricImage that was causing incorrect values to be returned. Corrected a bug in the Branded Agents Portals in which the count returned by getImpactedAccountCount did not match the result size of getImpactedAccounts Backend Resolved an issue that was causing host migrations to fail if a Virtual Guest was powered off. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160418/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160418/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where R1Soft Server options were not showing up while initiating an OS Reload. API Added getVmWareActiveAccountLicenseKeys to SoftLayer_Account service. Backend Resolved a bug in which hosts authorized to multiple iSCSI Volumes became deauthorized from all iSCSI Volumes when one Volume was explicitly deauthorized. Resolved an issue that was preventing Local Load Balancers and Netscalers from completing the provisioning process due to an errant RAID card check. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160411/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160411/</guid>
      <description>Portal To align closer to the IBM Cloud user experience the portal interface color scheme and feel have been updated. All functionality has remained in place. API None Backend Resolved an issue what was preventing upgrades of Network Gateway Devices in to a High Availability Pair. Added functionality to alert users via email when the email account or password is changed for their portal user. To speed up provisioning times and remove the need for manual intervention a function was implemented to pair a Raid Card when an order contains an SSD or SAS Drive during the provision process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 4, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160404/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue in which a ticket was unable to be updated if there was special text in the ticket update. Resolved an issue where the order forms were not loading properly for non-English languages. API Resolved an issue where the description for SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getObject was not appearing on SLDN or API metadata. Resolved an issue in which creating a Bare Metal server via SoftLayer_Hardware::createObject was setting the RAM value to 0GB.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 28, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160328/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160328/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue that was preventing customers from properly saving modifications on existing quotes from the Customer portal. Fixed a bug that was causing slow response on the ordering checkout page. Resolved an issue that was affecting upgrading a Vyatta to an High Availability pair. API None Backend Enable Order support for Account Defined Networking Virtual Guests. Resolved an issue that caused snapshot space threshold alerts to repeatedly update tickets with the same information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 21, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160321/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added the ability to create primary storage groups larger than 2TB when ordering. Resolved an issue that was preventing customers with Legacy (The Planet) subnets from viewing them in the customer portal. Fixed an issue with a very small subset of accounts which was causing the order forms not to load properly. Resolved an issue that was preventing customers from ordering static subnets routed to a Netscaler VPX. API SoftLayer_Account_MasterServiceAgreement::getPdf is being deprecated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 7, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160307/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160307/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where some exception errors were not getting their messages properly translated, so the actual error message was being masked. API Resolved an issue that was causing a call to SoftLayer_Resource_Metadata::getBackendMacAddresses to return duplicate results. Resolved an issue that was preventing Sales quotes from being callable via the API. Backend Customers with Private Host VSI&amp;rsquo;s can call to opt-out of host reboots for major maintenance events. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 29, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160229/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160229/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was causing Managed Hosting orders to reset when a Promo code was applied to an order. API Removed defunct methods: SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getBandwidthMinMax and SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getBandwidthMinMax Backend Resolved an issue that was causing RedHat licenses to be terminated upon an OS reload. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/2016022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/2016022/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was preventing orders from completing on accounts with Account Defined Networking enabled. Resolved an issue that was preventing order quotes from being properly saved for later use. Removed the TLS_X cipher option for SSL Offloading on Load Balancers in the customer portal. Furthermore, any attempts to configure TLS_X through the API will now result in a NotSupported exception. Improved Cancellation Error Messaging for Already Canceled Services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/20160222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/20160222/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was preventing orders from completing on accounts with Account Defined Networking enabled. Resolved an issue that was preventing order quotes from being properly saved for later use. Removed the TLS_X cipher option for SSL Offloading on Load Balancers in the customer portal. Furthermore, any attempts to configure TLS_X through the API will now result in a NotSupported exception. Improved Cancellation Error Messaging for Already Canceled Services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 17, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160217/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue where there is an additional forward slash in the return redirect from PayPal ordering. Fixed an issue preventing the warning message from being displayed with improper virtual server configurations on the ordering page. The link to order private node virtual servers in the control portal will now properly direct users to the private node order page. API None Backend Updated backend monitoring agent APIs, which will make the monitoring services more efficient and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 15, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160215/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160215/</guid>
      <description>Portal Updated the order receipt page, added some useful links to documentation about the purchased product. Streamlined the form which is used to submit orders. API Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_Hardware::createObject that was preventing processor restricted operating systems from being ordered with fixedConfigurationPreset. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 10, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160210/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160210/</guid>
      <description>Portal None API Fixed a bug in SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::createObject that was preventing sshKeys from being properly installed on the new server. Backend Disabled quotes that contain products from specific packages: 56, 126, 142, 143, 146, 147, 148, 158, 234 Updated the Linux post provisioning process to output more verbose log files. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160208/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue where private subnets were not populating in the VLAN selector for private networking only server orders. Resolved an issue preventing OS reloads from Image Templates from completing due to inactive packages on the template. API None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160214/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue with incorrect placements of order sliders during checkout. API API deprecation warning: SoftLayer_Network_Component::getPortStatistics will be functionally deprecated on May 2, 2016. After this time the method will return a deprecated exception. Upon the next release version of the API, it will be removed. Backend Fixed a rare bug in Hourly Bare Metal provisions that occurred when a customer had a VLAN on a Monthly Bare Metal server router in the same datacenter as the new Hourly Bare Metal Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 1, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160201/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue that was preventing the portal from properly enabling Private VLAN spanning. API Exposed getAllowedHardwareIds and getAllowedVirtualGuestIds to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. This helps with API timeout issues on accounts with a large amount of Bare Metal Servers and or Virtual Guests. Resolved an issue where calling denySharingAccess would cause an image template to go in to an inconsistent state. Backend Added the ability to specify userdata to Hourly Bare Metal Servers Enabled the automatic migration of local disk VSIs on disabled hosts on VSI power off or reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160125/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160125/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue where internal technical support updates were being sent in the customer facing section of tickets. Fixed an issue with Advanced Monitoring alert emails not being sent to customers. When the option to order a &amp;lsquo;Dedicated Firewall (Dedicated) Option&amp;rsquo; is selected, &amp;lsquo;Bare Metal Server Firewall Option&amp;rsquo; is now deselected to prevent the order form from producing the error when continuing to checkout. Conversely, if a &amp;lsquo;Bare Metal Server Firewall Option&amp;rsquo; is selected, the &amp;lsquo;Dedicated Firewall (Dedicated) Option&amp;rsquo; will be deselected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160118/</guid>
      <description>Portal Resolved an issue where Data Transfer tickets were not populating with ship date any notes and/or tracking details. API None Backend Fixed a bug where the incorrect storage volume name was reported in snapshot threshold alert tickets. Corrected an issue with FreeBSD provisions that was causing non-swap space to be set as EXT3 instead of UFS. Resolved an issue where license updates for RedHat were not properly occurring on VSI&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160111/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160111/</guid>
      <description>Portal Replaced the 2014 SOC1 report with the 2015 SOC1 report for users to download from the portal. Fixed an issue where some tickets were not showing as updated by the customer. Fixed an issue where the create date was not set when a new DNS domain was created from subnet page. Fixed an issue where error messages from a previous submission are not cleared when a new Catalyst user submits the signup form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 4, 2016</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2016/20160104/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue with OS Reloads failing due to outdated packages. Fixed an issue on the order page where an invalid method name was being referenced, causing no results to return. Added ClickAndBuy as a payment authorization type for ordering. API Updated getSubnetCategories to properly retrieve all subnet categories. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 28, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151228/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151228/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue with customers receiving alert/alarm emails after their server has been reclaimed. Fixed an issue with customers seeing errors when trying to remove a credit card with the type of PAYPAL API None Backend None </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 21, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151221/</guid>
      <description>Portal Introduced the Account Defined Networking option on customer order forms. The Customer Defined Network product is currently in beta and not available on all SoftLayer accounts. Replaced the old SOC2 report with the new one for period November 1, 2014 through October 31, 2015. Fixed an issue that was causing Notifications to show an empty list of impacted devices. API The SoftLayer_Account_MasterServiceAgreement::getPdf() method is deprecated. It is recommended to replace its use with the new SoftLayer_Account_MasterServiceAgreement::getFile method.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151214/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed bug that prevented setting minimum member number to zero on Netscalers when using purchased vlans. Fixed an issue with Netscaler license renewal notifications pointing to an invalid URL. Added localization for support policy documents. API None Backend Fixed an issue with hardware testing being skipped on provisions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 07, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151207/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151207/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an error that would occasionally prevent the &amp;ldquo;Reconfigure KVM Console&amp;rdquo; link from properly reconfiguring the KVM console. API None Backend SMTP Inbound traffic from the public internet is now blocked for new accounts by default. This does not effect backend networks. Reverse PTRs for new domain records will be ip4.static.sl-reverse.com and ip6.static.sl-reverse.com </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 02, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151202/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151202/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed the knowledgelayer link in tickets about XenServer licensing. API Added allow and remove methods for controlling SoftLayer_Network_Storage access to a host. SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHost() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::removeAccessFromHost() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHostList() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::removeAccessFromHostList() Added SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::cancelRequest() which allows a lockdown request to be canceled. Fixed an issue preventing Virtual Guests from being upgradeable when they had an operating system no longer sold. Submitting multiple SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disconnectCompute will now result in an exception to all requests after the first, until the compute instance is reconnected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 30, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151130/</guid>
      <description>Portal Added an error message when trying to order from a datacenter your account does not have access to. API Fixed an issue that was causing migration failures of local disk VSI&amp;rsquo;s to SAN disk VSI&amp;rsquo;s when a metadata disk was attached. Fixed an issue that was causing the preset.totalMinimumHourlyFee to be rounded to the nearest integer when using Hardware.getCreateObjectOptions on hourly bare metal servers. Users must now have permission to access a Hardware or VSI to be able to request an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 23, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151123/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Fixed an issue where newly provisioned Netscalers were being assigned licenses with near-term license expiration dates. Fixed an issue that was preventing reloads from occurring on instances that did not have a backend network component on eth0. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 18, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151118/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151118/</guid>
      <description>Portal Adds support for viewing and accepting 3rd party terms of service during the ordering process. API Fixed an error preventing the storage for virtual guests that have been live migrated to be migrated as well. Renamed SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disableCompute() to SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disableLockedAccount </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 12, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151112/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151112/</guid>
      <description>Portal Updates the invoice pdf document&amp;rsquo;s VAT summary page to provide more precise tax information. API Fixed SoftLayer_DNS_Domain returning malformed SOAP data when creating any type of DNS record. Networking configuration transactions during provisioning and reloads now run in parallel, improving provisioning speeds. Created a new API method that allows approved brands to retrieve lock information on an account locked by that brand. SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::getAccountHistory </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 10, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151110/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improved the error message on the Catalyst self-enrollment page when user enters invalid credit card information. &amp;lsquo;NEW&amp;rsquo; Invoices will now properly display the last 4 digits of the credit card. API Fix issue in which objectFilter values for (SoftLayer_Network_Subnet)[http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet] addressSpace and subnetType were being ignored. Fixed an issue that When a SSL certificate is being activated on a load balancer which is already active, the load balancer sends a response which was being improperly handled as an error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 5, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151105/</guid>
      <description>Portal Next and Pending invoices are cached once requested, greatly reducing the time it takes to download the invoice again. API Fixes an issue where tokens were not being properly replaced in the subject field for ticket watch notification emails </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 3, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151103/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151103/</guid>
      <description>Portal Changed the region sort order on order forms to be more friendly. Removed forum auto-login link. Restrict the length of first name field for credit cards to match those enforced by account first name field (30 characters) API Improved Virtual Guest provisioning times by parallelizing some provisioning transactions. Fixed an error preventing some Fast Provision Servers from getting past the SEND_SOFTWARE_INSTALL transaction. Failed post install scripts on unsupported OSes will now include a message that the OS is unsupported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151029/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151029/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improved device list performance for customers with NetScaler MPX devices API New accounts will have outbound port 25 blocked by default. More information here, here and here. This effects any new accounts created through the web sign-up process, and SoftLayer_Brand::createCustomerAccount. Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::getTransactionHistory Improved backend performance for block and file storage provisioning. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 26, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151026/</guid>
      <description>Portal Improved reliability of File and Block Storage provisioning. API Brand Master Accounts may no longer place orders Added an API endpoint that allows brands to disconnect, reconnect, and disable their customer accounts. SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 19, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151019/</guid>
      <description>Portal Storage groups default to max size if no size is specified. Changed generic error messages on Catalyst enrollment to specify more clearly the problem encountered. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151014/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151014/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Updated documentation on SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::reloadOperatingSystem Improved performance of SoftLayer_Account::updateVpnUsersForResource Speed improvement to Cloud Migrate transaction </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 12, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151012/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed an issue with some Object Storage accounts not being listed properly Fixed an issue where some ticket attachments were not getting uploaded. Adds restrictions on ordering a server in the India DC. More Information Fixed creation of billing item for managed resources that require a transfer price Eliminates false errors from being thrown during bandwidth usage polling Fixes No-OS rescue transactions from failing. No-OS rescues now default to a Linux rescue environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 07, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151007/</guid>
      <description>Portal Properly display all VAT summary rates on invoices Correct SSL VPN authentication lockouts caused by a set of automated actions API The First Name, Last Name, Street Address, City, Country, ZIP, State, Company Name, Office Phone fields must not be blank when creating a user. No longer possible to cancel Endurance Storage while there are active blocking actions happening. Adds getPublicCustomerOwnedImages to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template_Group service Fixed a bug when adding new configuration value for a Nimsoft Monitoring Robot causing a failing transaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 05, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20151005/</guid>
      <description>Portal New IBM cloud theme API Decreased monitoring robot provisioning time Improved SAML authentication logs Corrects a bug where the replications schedule may not be returned for all Endurance Storage volumes. Improved SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::lastOperatingSystemReload() request performance Adds the ability to order hardware security modules via the API. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 30, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150930/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150930/</guid>
      <description>Portal API Invalid characters are now being removed from ARIN/RIPE/APNIC registrations Engendered network address translation context awareness in VLAN verification actions. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150929/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150929/</guid>
      <description>API Adds account creation source record to brand master accounts created during the brand creation process preventing failures during account creation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 28, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150928/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150928/</guid>
      <description>Portal Correcting ability for Agents to Escalate a Ticket to SoftLayer Sales Group Fixed a minor storage view error The validator was previous incorrectly kicking out firewall orders for servers which have the private VLAN as an inside VLAN but not the public VLAN. This has been fixed and the validator should now allow those orders to go through. API SoftLayer_Account.nextInvoiceIncubatorExemptTotal is now depreciated and will be removed in a later version Numbers are no longer valid characters for a lastName field when creating an account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 23, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150923/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixes a problem where some orders would be authorized several times before being collected. API Prevents CoreOS Virtual Guests from using rescue layer as it is not supported </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 21, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150921/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150921/</guid>
      <description>API Improves response time of getUpgradeItemPrices Fixed an issue where doing an OS reload on a virtual guest from Windows to Linux would prevent the virtual guest from deploying properly. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 16, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150916/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150916/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixed a minor display issue with the data transfer service API Fixed a bug with location-based pricing and capacity restrictions. This ensures that you can continue to submit standard pricing to the API endpoints, and the back-end will automatically use the right location based prices when ordering. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150914/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150914/</guid>
      <description>API Improved resiliency of monitoring robot provisioning </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 10, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150910/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150910/</guid>
      <description>Portal Properly display an error when setting a tag of greater than 128 characters. API Fixed an issue with monitoring email subscriber changes not taking immediate effect. Fix a regression in which the Account.privateSubnets and Account.publicSubnets properties were not able to be filtered. Performance/Endurance storage provisioning improvements Improved provisioning time of monitoring robots </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 02, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150902/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150902/</guid>
      <description>Portal Correct Display Inconsistencies for Flexible Credit Participants API Improve performance of hardware and virtual guest callbacks Upgrades the interface with the APNIC registrar to support their new session based authentication system, allowing for proper modification of rwhois entires. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150829/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150829/</guid>
      <description>Portal Fixes a bug preventing editing of storage groups for quotes and orders. Fixed input validation on forward zone creation to allow for long gTLDs API Improved punycode validation for domain names. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 8, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150826/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150826/</guid>
      <description>API Prevents grouped network components from being disconnected Added a lastResponseDate to the ticket object. This lastResponseDate represents the last time a customer facing response was added to the ticket. This is exposed sldn. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 24, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150824/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150824/</guid>
      <description>Portal Deleted virtual guests should no longer show up in the portal API Improve the current workflow for processing nimsoft robots on the landing hub. This should have a significant impact in terms of reducing landing hub related escalations and transaction failures. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 19, 2015</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150819/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/release_notes/2015/20150819/</guid>
      <description>Portal Removed private IP address detection that checks whether or not the IP address starts with &amp;ldquo;10.&amp;rdquo;. This comes necessary now that we support Customer Defined Networks. Correctly identify if the primary ip address is in the private ip space, instead of relying on the &amp;ldquo;10.&amp;rdquo; prefix in the ip address. Updates the order review page to always show transfer/floor pricing. Resolve issues with discrepancy in mandatory fields in add portal user across portals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
