<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/tags/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180713/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180713/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Update ReCAPTCHA to version 2 Added functionality for legacy, non-email formatted IBMids to be persisted during account creation. Customer created tickets that have managed hardware should route to the managed services queue. Improve order form load time for uncached packages Fix issue where states for countries that are not US or Canada were failing on SSL certificate orders. Data centers should now be shown for bare metal servers in all portals Multiple usability updates for order forms  API  Fixed a bug that was causing customer power strip power cycle API calls to fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180706/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180706/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Validation of EncryptedToken fails if the impersonating user is an brand agent Remove invalid datacenters from fixed config bare metal order form Allow non-empty COS Buckets to be placed for MDMS orders.  API  Duplicate firewall rules should not allowed to be added A new property has been added to SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image, isEncrypted. This value returns if the disk on the image is encrypted.  Backend  Fix the load balancer deletion failure which keeps the load balancer in delete_pending state after billing item gets cancelled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 29, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180629/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180629/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Allow Master User to clear security questions for users on account. Fix issue when ordering SSL certs for non-US organizational addresses that had a state Updates to dedicated vsi and dedicated hosts order forms for encryption Fixed an issue where a customer cannot delete the CDN service Billing Item from Customer Portal  API  The Permission/Resource change event log type should only show for the customer with the GENERATE_PERMISSION_REPORTS set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 21, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180621/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180621/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Evault Performance enhancements. Evault Password enhancements.  API  Blocked deactivated templates from being pushed to cache.  Backend  Have account disable/enable cascade to users Corrects Australia/West time zone to be correct GMT offset. Fix missing paren pair in cloud init attribute validation Fixes an issue that caused some Bring Your Own License orders to go to Pending Finance Approval.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180614/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180614/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Missing pending transaction details information during volume modification process. This change will allow customers to see the status of their ordered volume modification in portal Improve order forms speed Direct Link - Backend Edit related changes for control portal Add localization of currencies and countries to order page currency selector.  API  Modify SoftLayer_Event_Log::getAllEventNames to return events names without brand references Added pciDevices and pciDeviceAllocationStatus fields to the DedicatedHost object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 8, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180608/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180608/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an issue when placing orders with a state of &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; Fixing a bug where selecting None for multiselect options would not update the summary total on the order form. Loading conflicts out of band on order forms &amp;amp; move WWW order form assets to CDN  API  Improve getActiveTransactionStatus performance Fix issues with some storage group validation edge cases  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 31, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180531/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180531/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where the device list wouldn&amp;rsquo;t display any devices. Correct Customer Add User form when state is &amp;lsquo;Other&amp;rsquo; Updated display logic to not show null userData values without blocking other attributes that are null  API  longName field is now required when creating brands in the API Added validation for keyId in &amp;lsquo;removeApiAuthenticationKey&amp;rsquo; method Enables customers to upgrade or downgrade the number of GPUs on a virtual guest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 24, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180524/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180524/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue when a user with TOTP has a successful login after fewer than 10 failed attempts, the previous failed attempts are not cleared. Customers were unable to create EU only tickets. This change fixes the filter to pull EU data centers. Adds a checkbox to the WWW order form on the save quote dialog that allows the user to accept the GDPR terms and conditions. This check box must be checked to place a quote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180517/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Add Virtuozzo transaction provisioning and reload groups and icon. This changes a link in the footer of the Www Store pages This issue removes Google Tag Manager and Adobe Target from the SoftLayer Www template  API  Fixes a bug that causes the euCompliantFlag on SoftLayer_Location to always return false. Direct Link - Fix the error message to indicate problem clearly when edit fails Direct Link - Increase Vendor Circuit and Vendor Name length from 30 to 40.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 10, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180510/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180510/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Stopped creating surveys related to Bluemix assets in the SoftLayer portal  API  The IQN of a host can no longer be changed when that host has assigned storage volumes. This is to ensure consistency within the system Making new storage authentication error messages viewable   Backend  Change how &amp;ldquo;reset Master user IBMid link&amp;rdquo; treats the user from whom the IBMid is &amp;ldquo;stolen&amp;rdquo; in a linked account pair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180426/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180426/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Add boot mode to order forms when provisioning a public vsi. Adds order form validation for the VLAN and SSH Key selection for just HSM. Remove the &amp;ldquo;Save As Quote&amp;rdquo; option from the order forms when the order has products that are not currently quotable. Foreign language usability updates to WWW order forms  API  Fixed the bug where the following services are returning tickets to which the current user doesn&amp;rsquo;t have access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 13, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180413/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180413/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Add GPU column to flavors table for GPU Flavors Display link to privacy policy on order forms  API  Fix issue where dedicated host orders would fail order verification. Bandwidth Usage Detail contains the data used to billing bandwidth at the end of the billing cycle. The timestamps used to pull metrics is using GMT instead of Central. This issue validates that BYOL and CloudInit attributes are set to 1 when creating a template via the api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 6, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180406/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180406/</guid>
      <description>Portal  adds the sshKeys selector back into the confirmation page when ordering a hardware security module. Remove forums.softlayer.com links.  API  Make createObject orders for hourly SAN virtual servers use correct package when presets are account restricted. Fixed getPortalLoginToken function registering a failed login before it registers a successful login Fix bug preventing scheduler from being used when request comes from SLDN Terminating Status is added when guest vsi are being reclaimed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 30, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180330/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180330/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added feature to notify customers about host outages to the Virtual/viewMemberDetails/ page Removes Provision Scripts and User Data sections from the CHECKOUT page when ordering HSM devices.  API  Fixed SoftLayer_Scale_Group&amp;rsquo;s editObject method to automatically scale the group up or down appropriately when the desiredMemberCount parameter is specified Fixes an issue that prevented the &amp;lsquo;IOPS&amp;rsquo; ORM value from being updated for performance replicas. Added SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image::getAvailableBootModes() Method Expose Account::securityLevel Round up the Load Balancer as a Service telemetry monitoring metrics value to 3 decimal points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180315/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180315/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Adds the Hardware Security Module(HSM) to the manage order form. Adds a Learn More link to the sub-section header for HSM. Improve order forms rendering speed  API  Added SoftLayer_Network_Interconnect_Tenant::getAllPortLabelsWithCurrentUseage Adds SERIAL_NUMBER property to SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Iscsi volumes which can be used as an objectFilter Provide API to retrieve load balancer monitoring metrics and ssl ciphers  Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancerMonitoringMetricDataPoint Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::getListenerTimeSeriesData Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::getSslCiphers Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer::updateSslCiphers   Backend  Added HSM 750 compatibility to provisioning workflow Blocks monthly suspend-able virtual server orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 14, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180314/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180314/</guid>
      <description>Added SLDN Documentation We have finally retired the old SLDN site, and migrated its content over to softlayer.github.io.
The following content types have been added, in addition to the existing release notes, and code examples.
 Articles Blogs Services and their associated Methods Datatypes  If you notice any issues with the content here, please create an issue on our github page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes March 9, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180309/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180309/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  Add new account attribute type &amp;lsquo;NEW_ASSIGN_NETWORK_ENABLED&amp;rsquo; Updates the simple ordering methods, createObject and getCreateObjectOptions, to properly handle ordering suspend-able virtual servers.  Backend  Addresses a problem where SoftLayer_Network_Storage::enableSnapshots() wasn&amp;rsquo;t working properly for Weekly snapshot schedules. Block public image creation when incorrect location data is sent in. Removed trailing and ending spaces from ipAddressRestriction value before creating a user. Added try/catch block to Virtual Guest workflow in reclaim guest to catch exception where a Scale Group tries to provision a VSI to meet the member requirement when a VSI is reclaimed (causing the Scale Group to drop below the minimum).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API SERVICE DISRUPTION March 1, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180301/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180301/</guid>
      <description>API SERVICE DISRUPTION: March 1st, 2018 IBM Cloud will stop supporting TLS 1.0 and 1.1 on api.softlayer.com and api.service.softlayer.com
What Is Happening? On March 1, 2018 at 0900 UTC (0300 CDT) IBM Cloud Infrastructure will stop supporting TLS 1.0 and 1.1 encryption on api.softlayer.com and api.service.softlayer.com; these API endpoints will only support callers using TLS 1.2 encryption levels or higher.
When Will It Happen? On March 1, 2018 at 0900 UTC (0300 CDT) TLS 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes February 28, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180228/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180228/</guid>
      <description>Portal  User should be get locked for 30 minutes when they enter invalid TOTP code more than 10 times. Remove forum link from Notification Messages Modifies translation text for the order checkout page to use &amp;lsquo;user data&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;metadata.&amp;rsquo;  API  Check if active user is parent of user being edited dutring addPortalPermission and removePortalPermission Support forced delete of scale groups regardless of status Added http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/getBootMode updated validationRules for partitionName to allow for slashes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180216/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Improvement to verbiage shown for servers with active billing for an inactive package. GPU Flavor prices were not factoring the price of the GPU. Fixed an issue where the master user could set themselves as &amp;ldquo;VPN_ONLY&amp;rdquo; user.  API Backend  Fix Reloads being blocked when a user suppresses the email for RELOAD_COMPLETE Fix Micron Hard Drive Storage Group Member&amp;rsquo;s Grow Flag Update automated messaging update on Data Transfer Request tickets Add dal10 to the list of data centers supporting security groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180207/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180207/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Allow customers to suppress order emails  API  Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;.. to change a user link&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;to edit a user&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;Access Denied. Only the Master user..&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;Account 1234 is authenticated by IBMid&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called for subuser Validator added for bare metal servers orders that use the userData field, the allowed length is 2000 characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 22, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180122/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180122/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixes bug when checking for available vGPU resources. Update favicon on IBM cloud template Fixed an informative popup to properly display entire username when deleting or disabling a user with a long username  API  SoftLayer_Network_Storage::getAllowableDatacenters() performance improvements Added a SUPPORTED_BOOT_MODE attribute to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image_Attribute_Type class to hold what boot modes the image can support. Update SLDN doc for Virtual_Guest.createObject to add Security Group parameters Replace checking for parentId with isMasterUser flag for add/remove device access Added quantity validation on StaaS orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180115/</guid>
      <description>SLCLI https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/releases/tag/v5.4.0
 Changes: https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/compare/v5.3.2...v5.4.0
 Upgraded Requests and Urllib3 library to latest. This allows the library to make use of connection retries, and connection pools. This should prevent the client from crashing if the API gives a connection reset / connection timeout error
 reworked wait_for_ready function for virtual, and added to hardware managers.
 fixed block/file iops in the slcli block|file detail view
 Added sub items to hw detail --price, removed reverse PTR entries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 3, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180103/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Replace &amp;ldquo;formerly IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;formerly SoftLayer&amp;rdquo; in all affected templates.  API  Autoscale: Prevent Multiple Scale Actions per Policy. https://stackoverflow.com/questions/39696067/invalid-guest-template-for-autoscale-in-sl Only block BYOL sharing and making it public if the software description is a licensed product. Adds support for Spot instances to simple VSI ordering. spotGuestFlag would be used to indicate in a createObject() parameter block if the order is for a Spot Instance. http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/createObject Added an API to tell if an account is eligible to link with PaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 11, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171206/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171206/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Adds warning messages to that will pop to alert EU only processing users that they are selecting a data center or package that it not EU compliant. This change will add a checkbox on the WWW order from checkout page that allows customers to opt-in to EU localized support. For a customer that opts-in, any servers they have in an EU datacenter will only be serviced by technicians also in the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 04, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171204/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fix issue where LVM was set on storage groups erroneously when editing a configuration on the order form. Add a new order approval e-mail notification template for SAP Certified servers.  API  Added account validation support for combining unicode characters, such as diacritical arabic characters. Added new check to prevent multiple partitions being set with grow flag. Allow the customers who does not have USER_MANAGE permission to see their own login attempts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171127/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171127/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message. Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group.  Backend  Added more validation around partition sizeing Changed the wording on raid alert tickets Fixed an issue reclaiming Virtual Servers Fixes bug when trying to find reverse DNS records. Fixed an issue with account link invitations not getting a proper activation url Fixed a bug preventing some provisioning transactions from completing automatically  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171115/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message. Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group.  API  Added more validation to ordering Direct Link products through the SLAPI to mirror validation done by the portal Adds functionality to allow upgrade for Fortigate firewall appliances  Backend  Fixed an issue where disk groups would be improperly partitioned when a HOT_SPARE volume was present Allowed various unicode hyphens through account validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171120/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited. Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid.  API  Enforce the same set of input requirements for SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject in a linked account, as for a non-linked account.  Backend  Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 13, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171113/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited. Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid.  API  Enforce the same set of input requirements for SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject in a linked account, as for a non-linked account.  Backend  Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171025/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added 2 links to the order approval email when ordering MDMS. The links will guide the customers to the User Guide and device Checklist.
 Removed the warning on the order forms that 2nd disk is required for Balanced local flavor VSIs.  API  When a user is created with double quotes in email address from API, Error message pointed to a problem with username. This has been fixed to show the correct error message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171012/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an error that was being displayed when an end user clicks on “Reconfigure System Configuration” link on complete order page.  API  Removed the ability to edit or view a users profile via the API if the users status is set to cancel_pending.
  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 05, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171005/</guid>
      <description>Portal  IBM Bluemix Load Balancers are now live in the customer portal. Performance and Endurance Block volumes can no longer have their LUN Id changed unless all host authorizations are first removed. This is to ensure synchronization between the customer portal and the storage systems.  API  None  Backend  Added more logic when auto-scaling Virtual Guests. The new logic checks the dates in the logs first and makes sure there are no other provisions or reclaims within the cooldown period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170927/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170927/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Security Groups are now live in the customer portal at https://control.softlayer.com/security/securitygroups. Pushed some code to tidy up the Virtual Guest Family size order forms.  API  Created the enableEuLocalizedProcessing and disableEuLocalizedProcessing methods for the SoftLayer_Account.  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 21, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170921/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170921/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue where a subset of DCs where not displaying the 1,2,4 or 8 core options for Dedicated Host Virtual Guests. Pushed code that that corrected a display issue when ordering Dedicated Host Virtual Guests. When selecting Local drive Virtual Guests do not show the 3rd, 4th, and 5th disk options.  API  Added validation to prevent monthly LBaaS orders via the API since the SoftLayer_Network_LBaaS_LoadBalancer service is only available with hourly billing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 14, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170914/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170914/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where standard disk prices were being incorrectly hidden for some datacenters during the order process. Virtual Guest Family sizes are now live on the order form. You can read more about the Family sizes here. Added new functionality to the order forms to support multiple disk controllers for bare metal offerings. Added the following new offerings in the Bluemix catalog: Container Registry, Informix On Cloud, Master Data Management on Cloud, Information Server on Cloud, JanusGraph, Monitoring, and Log Analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 7, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170907/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170907/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  Exposed the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request, SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request_KeyContact, and SoftLayer_Network_Storage_MassDataMigration_Request_Statu for interacting with the Mass Data Migration offering. Fixed an issue with the SoftLayer_Billing_Currency_ExchangeRate::getAllCurrencyExchangeRates method. When customers would supply the current days date, the call would not return any exchange rate information.  Backend  Fixed a bug with ISO importing. The fix now allows import transactions to complete even without a Software Description set on the ISO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170824/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170824/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Fixed a bug where cancellation tickets were not being closed after the cancellation had completed. Corrected an issue where Security Groups were not being properly applied to the private network of Windows VSI provisions.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 17, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170817/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170817/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue on the order form where Dedicated Host Instance orders were not showing all size options available in some Datacenters.  API  Corrected a bug where using SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject to order a dedicated host instance with SAN disks would error out with Unable to find a price for block device 0.  Backend  Pushed code to handle active/active clustering for the Cloud Load Balancing offering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170810/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170810/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Opened up Security Groups beta to more users. Added London 04 to the Datacenters that can utilize Security Groups. You can now configure the VSI on the checkout page to add security groups. Customer Portal Audit Logs now report Security group changes. You can now see when a security group is attached or removed from a Virtual Guest.  API  Fixed File/Block Storage replicationStatus key to always return a string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 3, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170803/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170803/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added the new Dedicated Host offering to the catalog. A dedicated host is a physical server with workload capacity entirely dedicated to a single client’s use. Corrected an issue where customers were unable to attach more than one dedicated host to a ticket.  API  Exposed the SoftLayer_Virtual_DedicatedHost Service. This allows you to interact with the new Dedicated Host offering. Added the addBulkDedicatedHostAccess method to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170726/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170726/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  Deprecated the blueIdAuthenticationRequiredFlag method and replaced it with the ibmIdAuthenticationRequiredFlag method for the SoftLayer_Account service.
 Added isoCodeAlphaThree to the returned data for the SoftLayer_Locale_Country::getCountries and SoftLayer_Locale_Country::getAvailableCountries methods. This returns the 3 character ISO code for a country.  Backend  Added logic for Brazil and India to support local currency for billing.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 19, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170719/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170719/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  Added the getLocalCurrencyExchangeRate method to the SoftLayer_Billing_Invoice service. This allows users to retrieve the exchange rate used for billing an invoice. Users can now call SoftLayer_Network_Storage::createOrUpdateLunId to change the LUN ID on a block volume. For example, if a user is trying to access multiple volumes from a single initiator, then it is possible that some volumes will have the same LUN ID which may cause conflicts on the initiator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170706/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue where applying security groups may cause errors during the provision of a Virtual Guest.  API  Pushed code to resolve an issue with the resultLimit for SoftLayer_Ticket_Subject::getAllObjects method. Before the fix the API was returning less data than the limit set. Addressed an issue with the PHP Library for the SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_IpAddress_Global::route method. If the endpoint IP address provided is associated with an unrouted subnet a fatal error was being returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 28, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170628/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added the ability to order the Mass Data Migration Service. This offering can only be ordered by the master account user. It allows for the secure migration of up to 120TB of data per device into / out of Cleversafe Object Storage using physical storage appliances housed in waterproof, tamper-evident, shockproof cases. Official Documentation.  API  Resolved an issue that was allowing customers to order duplicate volumes without specifying a datacenter location using placeOrder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 22, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170622/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170622/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Released code to support Volume Duplication. This offering adds the ability to order a new volume, pre-loaded with the contents of a File or Block Volume or Volume Replica, or a snapshot of a Volume or Volume Replica. Changed the default option for monitoring from Basic to None, for VSI order forms. Added the ability to assign Security Groups to an interface on the Virtual Guest order form for customers that are enrolled in the Beta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170608/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170608/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Corrected an issue in the portal where VMware ESXI 5.5 was not showing the licensing cost disclaimer on the order summary page in quotes and at checkout. Added additional Flex pricing information and external documentation links to the Cloud Object Storage S3 order page.  API  Pushed code that improves the performance of SoftLayer_Network_Storage::createSnapshot on Endurance and Performance volumes.  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 1, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170601/</guid>
      <description>Portal  When a server is reloaded customers now have the option to enable LVM on the storage groups during the reload. Added support for performance pricing when you duplicate storage volumes. Rolled out the ability for a user to create a new volume from an existing volume or snapshot. When creating the new volume a user will have the ability to either keep the configuration of the new volume (size, IOPS tier, etc) or make changes to the configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170524/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170524/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Corrected an issue that was causing the order form to not display hardware selection when loading from a Flex Image template.  API  None  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 18, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170518/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170518/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue that was causing SAP Certified servers to not be orderable from a Quote.  API  None  Backend  Resolve an issue where upgrading a Bluemix account to add infrastructure services would occasionally fail but still upgrade the account.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 18, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/20170518/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/20170518/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue that was causing SAP Certified servers to not be orderable from a Quote.  API  None  Backend  Resolve an issue where upgrading a Bluemix account to add infrastructure services would occasionally fail but still upgrade the account.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170510/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170510/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an issue where it was possible to order a clone  API  Added the getHardwarePools method to the SoftLayer_Account service.  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing Virtual Guest image templates to not be imported properly due to mismatched software descriptions. This only affected Windows image template imports.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 3, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170503/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170503/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved a bug that was causing duplicate pricing information to be shown for storage options on the portal order form.  API  Fixed SoftLayer_Network_Storage::storageTierLevel to always return a string value instead of a SoftLayer_Billing_Item object.  Backend  Fixed a bug that would automatically allow inactive image templates to be used for VSI OS Reloads.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170426/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170426/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Pushed code to resolve an issue where mixed case IBMId accounts were unable to upgrade to a Pay as you Go Bluemix Developer Services account. Resolved an issue that was causing NetScaler provisions to fail due to the license not being bound to a valid MAC address on the host system. Pushed code which added the requirement of using an IBMid in order to link a Platform as a Service account to an Infrastructure as a Service account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 19, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170419/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170419/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue that prevented the relevant locations from being returned on replicas with Account Defined Networking. Fixed an issue that prevented the relevant mounting point from being returned on accounts with Account Defined Networking. Resolved a bug which allowed servers to be ordered with IPv6 subnets for the primary interfaces. This causes servers to fail provisioning. Added userData field to the order forms for Bare Metal Servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170412/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170412/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Rolled out code that improves order form performance on page load time. Fixed issue where order validation was not always consistent between regular orders and orders from quotes, such as with hostname and domain validation. Corrected the error message when customers without the MANAGE_USER permission attempted to create sub-users.  API  None  Backend  Fixed a bug causing customer ISO image templates to fail to transfer to new Datacenters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 5, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170405/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170405/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed a bug to enforce correct cancellation order of volumes with replicas. Previously it was possible to cancel storage with replica, but the process would fail as the replica must be cancelled first. The portal will now direct to you first cancel the replica volume.  API  Updated the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest service&amp;rsquo;s getCreateObjectOptions method to not show options that are no longer available, such as old operating systems that are no longer supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 29, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170329/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170329/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Corrected an issue with customers being unable to claim an order quote for Performance or Endurance storage. Fixed an issue where subusers on an account were not able to order Netscaler VPX services even with the appropriate portal permissions. Exception message was unclear when a user without the &amp;lsquo;ticket add&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;ticket view&amp;rsquo; permissions tried to create an upgrade order. New change accurately indicates that the user must have these two permissions in order to create an upgrade order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170320/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue with the customer portal timing out with a large number of billing items.  API  Prevent server errors when using SoftLayer_Product_Package getItemsFromImageTemplate.  Backend  Fixed an issue provisioning Hourly Bare Metal servers that would require manual intervention to resolve. Fixes a problem that was preventing snapshots from being registered by the poller job. Allow hyphens in emails for IBMid Fixed an issue with offline migrations on windows virtual machines Update Hourly Bare Metal servers to check for mis-configurations before considering available  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170308/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170308/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Corrected an issue with ordering Fixed Configuration Servers. When a customer selected an operating system before a datacenter on fixed configurations servers the portal would show errors about storage groups being needed.  API  Added the getBuckets and getCloudObjectStoragePolicy methods to the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Hub_Cleversafe_Account service.  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 02, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170302/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170302/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  Resolved a bug when calling the methods failoverToReplicant, failbackFromReplicant, or immediateFailoverToReplicant from the SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Iscsi class instead of the base SoftLayer_Network_Storage, in which the method would return true, but the process would not be started.  Backend  Created an internal tool to unlink Bluemix and SoftLayer accounts. Customers can now open a ticket to request their Bluemix and SoftLayer accounts be unlinked.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 23, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170223/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Portal Exception message was unclear when a user without &amp;lsquo;ticket add&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;ticket view&amp;rsquo; permissions tried to create an upgrade order. New change accurately indicates that the user must have these two permissions in order to create an upgrade order.  API  None  Backend  Fixed two separate bugs in Endurance and Performance Storage provisioning where provisions were stalling due to API call timeout.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 16, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170216/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170216/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue that was preventing punny code domains from being added using the &amp;lsquo;Add Bulk Domains&amp;rsquo; tool in the customer portal.  API  None  Backend  Added some backend code to help automation issues related to sending automated password reset emails.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170208/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170208/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added a customerWaitTime field on the ticket search page in the customer portal. The customerWaitTime is the time the customer has been waiting for a response on a ticket. Multiple updates by the customer have no effect on this field and a reply by an employee resets the timer to zero. Pushed fix that tests that only numbers, letters, and spaces are allowed for all of the titles for contacts when trying to order an SSL certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170125/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170125/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where the &amp;ldquo;Add to Order&amp;rdquo; button overlaps dropdown list content when the list is too long  API  Published the SoftLayer_Network service for customers to interact with Customer Private Addressing. Refactored SoftLayer_Billing_Order_Quote::getRecalculatedOrderContainer(). Now returns the order container, instead of an array of an order container  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing Virtual Guests to fail reboot when residing on a host that has been marked as disabled for new instances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170111/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170111/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Pushed code to display the correct validation error when a number greater than 999 is used in the % field of Auto-Scaling policy actions. Previously a generic error message was displayed.  API  None  Backend  Updatd our Microsoft Proxy to handle new TLS requirements by .NET. A recent update to .NET for windows 2012 r2 added a much more strict TLS validation for powershell which in turn caused Post Install Scripts to fail during download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 5, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170105/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Pushed code to fix an issue that was causing an incorrect success message to be displayed when a user that has disabled/vpn only status clicked the Unlink button. Updated code to correct an error caused by a previously set VAT ID to be reported when the country selected does not use VAT. Updated the customer portal Order Form to include the new Cloud Object Storage general release offering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161219/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161219/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added VAT id support for Belarus. Added code to cleanup tag references on Virtual Guests/NetScalers/Image templates that have been deleted from a customers account. Added firewall verification during server orders that checks if a selected VLAN is eligible to be used with a server hardware firewall. Added code to filter out firewall-ineligible VLANs in VLAN selection on the order form when a server hardware firewall is being ordered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 7, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161207/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161207/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  Resolved an issue where SoftLayer_Brand::createObject requests coming in from the API were not creating an associated SoftLayer_Policy_Brand record. This bug resulted in user accounts created under the new brand to be unable to log in to the customer portal.  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 14, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161114/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Corrected an issue on the Bluemix order forms where the order form content appear in a different language based on the www.softlayer.com language cookie. The order forms are set to English until all language translations have been completed. Increased the space allowed for addresses when making payments via PayPal. The shorter space was causing PayPal transactions to fail when an account used a bunch of unicode characters. Fixed an issue where users might be immediately logged out after navigating to the order forms due to a non-public API call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161108/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161108/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Improved the ordering form performance when provisioning (Beta) Object Storage offerings.  API  None  Backend  Pushed code that would stop the sending of order completed and approved emails for Bluemix services on Linked Accounts. Resolved an issue that was causing Guest disk billing items to have incorrect category codes after an OS reload order was placed.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161024/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Changed portal layout and color scheme to match the new IBM Bluemix branding. Fixed an issue where SoftLayer tiered support customers could create a ticket with severity level higher than 4.  API  Added the getFileBlockEncryptedLocations method to the SoftLayer_Network_Storage service. This method can be used to get a list of SoftLayer_Location objects corresponding to datacenters which support Encryption at Rest for File and Block Storage.  Backend  When a user&amp;rsquo;s password expired, we are no longer automatically sending the password reset email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 17, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161017/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Updated the page title and icon on the control portal compute order forms to reflect IBM Bluemix.  API  Resolved an issue with the getMappedAccounts method not correctly displaying the accountLinks section of the output. When any sub-brand is created by a brand master account it now automatically has the brand attribute ALLOW_ACCOUNT_CREATION set to 1.This resolves an issue what required Sales Operations to manually set the ALLOW_ACCOUNT_CREATION to 1 on sub-branded accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161011/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20161011/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Updated the error message when ordering Public Subnets on a VLAN with HSRP.  API  Corrected an issue with the information for the getOpenIdRegistrationInfoFromCode method for the SoftLayer_User_Customer_OpenIdConnect service.  Backend  Fixed a potential issue that caused order verifications to fail in certain cases for accounts that have large numbers of Endurance or Performance volumes.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160920/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160920/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  Added the getOpenIdConnectMigrationState to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. This new method allows users to query whether an open invitation exists for a user.  Backend  Resolved an bug that was causing Netscaler provisioning issues due to hostname/domain validation errors. Fixed an issue with NO OS servers that was causing the Evault Bare Metal restore transaction to fail.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 12, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160912/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160912/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Made changes to the order form to align with the change in colored branding to the customer portal.  API  Resolved issues of API response timeout when removing a users API key. This occurred on customer accounts with a lot of Object Storage users.
 Resolved an issue that was causing changes in products and catalog offerings to not be properly reflected in the SoftLayer_Product_Package_Server service. Added the getGlobalIdentifier method to the SoftLayer_Resource_Metadata service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 28, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160828/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160828/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Pushed code fix that filters Vlans with respect to Datacenter selected when ordering Dedicated firewall. Pushed code fix that filters the severs based on Datacenter selected and the price capacity when ordering hardware firewall. Resolved an issue what was causing storage group templates with JBODs to not load correctly in the order forms.  API  Resolved a bug that was causing the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getMemoryMetricImageByDate method to return an incorrect graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160822/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160822/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Resolved a bug that was causing Resets of Dedicated Hardware Firewalls to fail if they were in a High Availablity Pair. Put code in place to ensure that cached disks from image templates are deleted when parent Virtual Disk Image is deleted.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 15, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160815/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160815/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Fixed an issue with servers not being immediately pulled from a Bandwidth pool upon cancellation. Improvements have been made to prevent static subnets and global IPs from being routed to administratively reserved IP addresses.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160808/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160808/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Added some additional Language translations to the order forms in the customer portal.  API  None  Backend  Fixed a bug that was causing duplicate IP&amp;rsquo;s to be assigned to network components during Virtual Guest provisions.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 1, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160801/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160801/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue with initial IPv6 routing for new subnet orders. Fixed a bug that was causing Evault for Virtual Guests to create unassociated billing items. Resolved an issue that was preventing SSH keys from being properly applied during an OS Reload. This only occurred if new software was added during the reload.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160725/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160725/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Pushed code to allow for the ordering of Network VLAN&amp;rsquo;s from the customer portal.  API  Created the initiatePortalPasswordChangeByBrandAgent method for the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. The Brand Agent must have permission to Add Customer Accounts to the Brand in order to initiate the password reset in this way.  Backend  Resolved a bug that was causing Paypal orders to fail due to a missing property for Hourly Bare Metal servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160718/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160718/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed a bug that caused Public node to be highlighted when ordering a Private Virtual Guest. Fixes an issue that prevented the relevant media types from being returned in the ContentDelivery code for CDN origin mapping.  API  Resolved an issue with the getAllObjects method for the SoftLayer_Software_AccountLicense service returning an internal error.  Backend  Fixed an issue creating an IBMid with a mixed-case email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160711/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160711/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Rolled out the code that would allow customers to attach secondary Portable Storage Volumes to an existing Virtual Guest, create bootable images on those Portable Storage Volumes, detach them, then boot from those created volumes into new Virtual Guest&amp;rsquo;s. Resolved an issue that was causing OS Reloads to fail on Bare Metal servers that had inactive or deprecated service offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: July 6, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160706/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160706/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue that was causing the Subnet selection portion of the order process to be displayed when ordering a Network Gateway. Added a UI element to create or associate an IBM ID with an account during the order process. When creating new orders customers will be prompted to associate an existing IBM ID or create a new one.  API  Resolved an issue that was causing incorrect results from different parameters on REST/SOAP calls to Bandwidth functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 27, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160628/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160628/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Added support to determine if multipath is properly configured for block LUNs.  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing OS reloads to fail on Virtual Guests during the image copy process.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160620/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Enabled the ordering of new, larger CPU/RAM capacity Virtual Guests.  API  Resolved an issue that was causing the SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getBandwidthTotal method to fail to properly retrieve bandwidth data.  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 13, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160613/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160613/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue that was preventing a server with Evault Storage from undergoing an Operating System reload.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: June 6, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160606/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160606/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue that was causing slow load times on a checkout of large orders. Fixed an issue in which only the &amp;lsquo;Default&amp;rsquo; health check option would function for UDP load balancer services.  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing OS Reloads to fail on Bare Metal servers that were using NO_OS or where version locked. Updated the host and domain name validation logic to permit a domain comprised of all digits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 31, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160601/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160601/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved a bug that was causing the portal to report incorrect space allocation for Performance/Endurance Storage when creating a retention schedule.  API  Retired the traceroute, ping, and isPingable methods from the SoftLayer_Utility_Network service.  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing newly created reverse zones for IPv6 subnets to be created using an older naming convention. Fixed a bug that would not allow an OS reload on a server running R1Soft backup server when the underlying OS was changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 23, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160523/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160523/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue that was producing an error when customers attempted place an order for an Indian data-center if the user&amp;rsquo;s account address did not have India as the country name. Updated the error message when a credit card order fails to specify the exact department to contact as well as provide contact information.  API  None  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 16, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160516/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160516/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue that was causing slow response during the order process.  API  None  Backend  Resolved a bug that was preventing orders from being edited on Branded Agent Portal accounts. Resolved an issue that was preventing the cancellation of the reclaim process if a server was part of a spare pool. Fixed an issue that was preventing orders for a vCenter Server Appliance license from going through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: May 9, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160509/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160509/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue affecting the ability to edit a Saved Order or a Sales Order Quote.  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue that was preventing a reclaim for Virtual Guests if they were powered off at the time of the cancellation request. Added translations for some email and ticket templates. Customers who set their user accounts to a non-English locale will see some emails and ticket updates translated into their locale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160425/</guid>
      <description>Portal  None  API  Resolved an issue with the syntax for getSnapshotRanges for the methods getMemoryMetricImage and getCpuMetricImage that was causing incorrect values to be returned. Corrected a bug in the Branded Agents Portals in which the count returned by getImpactedAccountCount did not match the result size of getImpactedAccounts  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing host migrations to fail if a Virtual Guest was powered off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160418/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160418/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where R1Soft Server options were not showing up while initiating an OS Reload.  API  Added getVmWareActiveAccountLicenseKeys to SoftLayer_Account service.  Backend  Resolved a bug in which hosts authorized to multiple iSCSI Volumes became deauthorized from all iSCSI Volumes when one Volume was explicitly deauthorized. Resolved an issue that was preventing Local Load Balancers and Netscalers from completing the provisioning process due to an errant RAID card check.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160411/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160411/</guid>
      <description>Portal  To align closer to the IBM Cloud user experience the portal interface color scheme and feel have been updated. All functionality has remained in place.  API  None  Backend  Resolved an issue what was preventing upgrades of Network Gateway Devices in to a High Availability Pair. Added functionality to alert users via email when the email account or password is changed for their portal user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: April 4, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160404/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue in which a ticket was unable to be updated if there was special text in the ticket update. Resolved an issue where the order forms were not loading properly for non-English languages.  API  Resolved an issue where the description for SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getObject was not appearing on SLDN or API metadata. Resolved an issue in which creating a Bare Metal server via SoftLayer_Hardware::createObject was setting the RAM value to 0GB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 28, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160328/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160328/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue that was preventing customers from properly saving modifications on existing quotes from the Customer portal. Fixed a bug that was causing slow response on the ordering checkout page. Resolved an issue that was affecting upgrading a Vyatta to an High Availability pair.  API  None  Backend  Enable Order support for Account Defined Networking Virtual Guests. Resolved an issue that caused snapshot space threshold alerts to repeatedly update tickets with the same information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 21, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160321/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added the ability to create primary storage groups larger than 2TB when ordering. Resolved an issue that was preventing customers with Legacy (The Planet) subnets from viewing them in the customer portal. Fixed an issue with a very small subset of accounts which was causing the order forms not to load properly. Resolved an issue that was preventing customers from ordering static subnets routed to a Netscaler VPX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: March 7, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160307/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160307/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where some exception errors were not getting their messages properly translated, so the actual error message was being masked.  API  Resolved an issue that was causing a call to SoftLayer_Resource_Metadata::getBackendMacAddresses to return duplicate results. Resolved an issue that was preventing Sales quotes from being callable via the API.  Backend  Customers with Private Host VSI&amp;rsquo;s can call to opt-out of host reboots for major maintenance events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 29, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160229/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160229/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue that was causing Managed Hosting orders to reset when a Promo code was applied to an order.  API  Removed defunct methods: SoftLayer_Metric_Tracking_Object::getBandwidthMinMax and SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::getBandwidthMinMax  Backend  Resolved an issue that was causing RedHat licenses to be terminated upon an OS reload.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/2016022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/2016022/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue that was preventing orders from completing on accounts with Account Defined Networking enabled.
 Resolved an issue that was preventing order quotes from being properly saved for later use. Removed the TLS_X cipher option for SSL Offloading on Load Balancers in the customer portal. Furthermore, any attempts to configure TLS_X through the API will now result in a NotSupported exception. Improved Cancellation Error Messaging for Already Canceled Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 22, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/20160222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/20160222/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue that was preventing orders from completing on accounts with Account Defined Networking enabled.
 Resolved an issue that was preventing order quotes from being properly saved for later use. Removed the TLS_X cipher option for SSL Offloading on Load Balancers in the customer portal. Furthermore, any attempts to configure TLS_X through the API will now result in a NotSupported exception. Improved Cancellation Error Messaging for Already Canceled Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 17, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160217/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue where there is an additional forward slash in the return redirect from PayPal ordering. Fixed an issue preventing the warning message from being displayed with improper virtual server configurations on the ordering page. The link to order private node virtual servers in the control portal will now properly direct users to the private node order page.  API  None  Backend  Updated backend monitoring agent APIs, which will make the monitoring services more efficient and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 15, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160215/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160215/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Updated the order receipt page, added some useful links to documentation about the purchased product. Streamlined the form which is used to submit orders.  API  Fixed an issue with SoftLayer_Hardware::createObject that was preventing processor restricted operating systems from being ordered with fixedConfigurationPreset.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 10, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160210/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160210/</guid>
      <description> Portal  None  API  Fixed a bug in SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::createObject that was preventing sshKeys from being properly installed on the new server.  Backend  Disabled quotes that contain products from specific packages: 56, 126, 142, 143, 146, 147, 148, 158, 234 Updated the Linux post provisioning process to output more verbose log files.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160208/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Resolved an issue where private subnets were not populating in the VLAN selector for private networking only server orders. Resolved an issue preventing OS reloads from Image Templates from completing due to inactive packages on the template.  API  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 8, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160214/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue with incorrect placements of order sliders during checkout.  API  API deprecation warning: SoftLayer_Network_Component::getPortStatistics will be functionally deprecated on May 2, 2016. After this time the method will return a deprecated exception. Upon the next release version of the API, it will be removed.  Backend  Fixed a rare bug in Hourly Bare Metal provisions that occurred when a customer had a VLAN on a Monthly Bare Metal server router in the same datacenter as the new Hourly Bare Metal Server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 1, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160201/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue that was preventing the portal from properly enabling Private VLAN spanning.  API  Exposed getAllowedHardwareIds and getAllowedVirtualGuestIds to the SoftLayer_User_Customer service. This helps with API timeout issues on accounts with a large amount of Bare Metal Servers and or Virtual Guests. Resolved an issue where calling denySharingAccess would cause an image template to go in to an inconsistent state.  Backend  Added the ability to specify userdata to Hourly Bare Metal Servers Enabled the automatic migration of local disk VSIs on disabled hosts on VSI power off or reboot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 25, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160125/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160125/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue where internal technical support updates were being sent in the customer facing section of tickets. Fixed an issue with Advanced Monitoring alert emails not being sent to customers. When the option to order a &amp;lsquo;Dedicated Firewall (Dedicated) Option&amp;rsquo; is selected, &amp;lsquo;Bare Metal Server Firewall Option&amp;rsquo; is now deselected to prevent the order form from producing the error when continuing to checkout. Conversely, if a &amp;lsquo;Bare Metal Server Firewall Option&amp;rsquo; is selected, the &amp;lsquo;Dedicated Firewall (Dedicated) Option&amp;rsquo; will be deselected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 18, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160118/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Resolved an issue where Data Transfer tickets were not populating with ship date any notes and/or tracking details.  API  None  Backend  Fixed a bug where the incorrect storage volume name was reported in snapshot threshold alert tickets. Corrected an issue with FreeBSD provisions that was causing non-swap space to be set as EXT3 instead of UFS. Resolved an issue where license updates for RedHat were not properly occurring on VSI&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 11, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160111/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160111/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Replaced the 2014 SOC1 report with the 2015 SOC1 report for users to download from the portal. Fixed an issue where some tickets were not showing as updated by the customer. Fixed an issue where the create date was not set when a new DNS domain was created from subnet page. Fixed an issue where error messages from a previous submission are not cleared when a new Catalyst user submits the signup form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 4, 2016</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2016/20160104/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an issue with OS Reloads failing due to outdated packages. Fixed an issue on the order page where an invalid method name was being referenced, causing no results to return. Added ClickAndBuy as a payment authorization type for ordering.  API  Updated getSubnetCategories to properly retrieve all subnet categories.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 28, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151228/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151228/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an issue with customers receiving alert/alarm emails after their server has been reclaimed. Fixed an issue with customers seeing errors when trying to remove a credit card with the type of PAYPAL  API  None  Backend  None  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 21, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151221/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Introduced the Account Defined Networking option on customer order forms. The Customer Defined Network product is currently in beta and not available on all SoftLayer accounts. Replaced the old SOC2 report with the new one for period November 1, 2014 through October 31, 2015. Fixed an issue that was causing Notifications to show an empty list of impacted devices.  API  The SoftLayer_Account_MasterServiceAgreement::getPdf() method is deprecated. It is recommended to replace its use with the new SoftLayer_Account_MasterServiceAgreement::getFile method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151214/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed bug that prevented setting minimum member number to zero on Netscalers when using purchased vlans. Fixed an issue with Netscaler license renewal notifications pointing to an invalid URL. Added localization for support policy documents.  API  None  Backend  Fixed an issue with hardware testing being skipped on provisions.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 07, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151207/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151207/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed an error that would occasionally prevent the &amp;ldquo;Reconfigure KVM Console&amp;rdquo; link from properly reconfiguring the KVM console.  API  None  Backend  SMTP Inbound traffic from the public internet is now blocked for new accounts by default. This does not effect backend networks. Reverse PTRs for new domain records will be ip4.static.sl-reverse.com and ip6.static.sl-reverse.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 02, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151202/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151202/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed the knowledgelayer link in tickets about XenServer licensing.  API  Added allow and remove methods for controlling SoftLayer_Network_Storage access to a host.  SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHost() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::removeAccessFromHost() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::allowAccessFromHostList() SoftLayer_Network_Storage::removeAccessFromHostList()  Added SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::cancelRequest() which allows a lockdown request to be canceled. Fixed an issue preventing Virtual Guests from being upgradeable when they had an operating system no longer sold. Submitting multiple SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disconnectCompute will now result in an exception to all requests after the first, until the compute instance is reconnected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 30, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151130/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Added an error message when trying to order from a datacenter your account does not have access to.  API  Fixed an issue that was causing migration failures of local disk VSI&amp;rsquo;s to SAN disk VSI&amp;rsquo;s when a metadata disk was attached. Fixed an issue that was causing the preset.totalMinimumHourlyFee to be rounded to the nearest integer when using Hardware.getCreateObjectOptions on hourly bare metal servers. Users must now have permission to access a Hardware or VSI to be able to request an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 23, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151123/</guid>
      <description> Portal API  Fixed an issue where newly provisioned Netscalers were being assigned licenses with near-term license expiration dates.
 Fixed an issue that was preventing reloads from occurring on instances that did not have a backend network component on eth0.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 18, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151118/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151118/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Adds support for viewing and accepting 3rd party terms of service during the ordering process.  API  Fixed an error preventing the storage for virtual guests that have been live migrated to be migrated as well. Renamed SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disableCompute() to SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::disableLockedAccount  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 12, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151112/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151112/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Updates the invoice pdf document&amp;rsquo;s VAT summary page to provide more precise tax information.  API  Fixed SoftLayer_DNS_Domain returning malformed SOAP data when creating any type of DNS record. Networking configuration transactions during provisioning and reloads now run in parallel, improving provisioning speeds. Created a new API method that allows approved brands to retrieve lock information on an account locked by that brand. SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request::getAccountHistory  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 10, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151110/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Improved the error message on the Catalyst self-enrollment page when user enters invalid credit card information. &amp;lsquo;NEW&amp;rsquo; Invoices will now properly display the last 4 digits of the credit card.  API  Fix issue in which objectFilter values for (SoftLayer_Network_Subnet)[http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet] addressSpace and subnetType were being ignored. Fixed an issue that When a SSL certificate is being activated on a load balancer which is already active, the load balancer sends a response which was being improperly handled as an error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 5, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151105/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Next and Pending invoices are cached once requested, greatly reducing the time it takes to download the invoice again.  API  Fixes an issue where tokens were not being properly replaced in the subject field for ticket watch notification emails  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 3, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151103/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151103/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Changed the region sort order on order forms to be more friendly. Removed forum auto-login link. Restrict the length of first name field for credit cards to match those enforced by account first name field (30 characters)  API  Improved Virtual Guest provisioning times by parallelizing some provisioning transactions. Fixed an error preventing some Fast Provision Servers from getting past the SEND_SOFTWARE_INSTALL transaction. Failed post install scripts on unsupported OSes will now include a message that the OS is unsupported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151029/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151029/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Improved device list performance for customers with NetScaler MPX devices  API  New accounts will have outbound port 25 blocked by default. More information here, here and here. This effects any new accounts created through the web sign-up process, and SoftLayer_Brand::createCustomerAccount. Added SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::getTransactionHistory Improved backend performance for block and file storage provisioning.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 26, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151026/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Improved reliability of File and Block Storage provisioning.  API  Brand Master Accounts may no longer place orders Added an API endpoint that allows brands to disconnect, reconnect, and disable their customer accounts. SoftLayer_Account_Lockdown_Request  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 19, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151019/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Storage groups default to max size if no size is specified. Changed generic error messages on Catalyst enrollment to specify more clearly the problem encountered.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151014/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151014/</guid>
      <description> Portal API  Updated documentation on SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::reloadOperatingSystem Improved performance of SoftLayer_Account::updateVpnUsersForResource Speed improvement to Cloud Migrate transaction  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 12, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151012/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Fixed an issue with some Object Storage accounts not being listed properly Fixed an issue where some ticket attachments were not getting uploaded. Adds restrictions on ordering a server in the India DC. More Information Fixed creation of billing item for managed resources that require a transfer price Eliminates false errors from being thrown during bandwidth usage polling Fixes No-OS rescue transactions from failing. No-OS rescues now default to a Linux rescue environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 07, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151007/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Properly display all VAT summary rates on invoices Correct SSL VPN authentication lockouts caused by a set of automated actions  API  The First Name, Last Name, Street Address, City, Country, ZIP, State, Company Name, Office Phone fields must not be blank when creating a user. No longer possible to cancel Endurance Storage while there are active blocking actions happening. Adds getPublicCustomerOwnedImages to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_Block_Device_Template_Group service Fixed a bug when adding new configuration value for a Nimsoft Monitoring Robot causing a failing transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 05, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20151005/</guid>
      <description> Portal  New IBM cloud theme  API  Decreased monitoring robot provisioning time Improved SAML authentication logs Corrects a bug where the replications schedule may not be returned for all Endurance Storage volumes. Improved SoftLayer_Hardware_Server::lastOperatingSystemReload() request performance Adds the ability to order hardware security modules via the API.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 30, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150930/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150930/</guid>
      <description> Portal API  Invalid characters are now being removed from ARIN/RIPE/APNIC registrations Engendered network address translation context awareness in VLAN verification actions.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150929/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150929/</guid>
      <description> API  Adds account creation source record to brand master accounts created during the brand creation process preventing failures during account creation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 28, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150928/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150928/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Correcting ability for Agents to Escalate a Ticket to SoftLayer Sales Group Fixed a minor storage view error The validator was previous incorrectly kicking out firewall orders for servers which have the private VLAN as an inside VLAN but not the public VLAN. This has been fixed and the validator should now allow those orders to go through.  API  SoftLayer_Account.nextInvoiceIncubatorExemptTotal is now depreciated and will be removed in a later version Numbers are no longer valid characters for a lastName field when creating an account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 23, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150923/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixes a problem where some orders would be authorized several times before being collected.  API  Prevents CoreOS Virtual Guests from using rescue layer as it is not supported  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 21, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150921/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150921/</guid>
      <description> API  Improves response time of getUpgradeItemPrices Fixed an issue where doing an OS reload on a virtual guest from Windows to Linux would prevent the virtual guest from deploying properly.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 16, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150916/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150916/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixed a minor display issue with the data transfer service  API  Fixed a bug with location-based pricing and capacity restrictions. This ensures that you can continue to submit standard pricing to the API endpoints, and the back-end will automatically use the right location based prices when ordering.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 14, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150914/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150914/</guid>
      <description> API  Improved resiliency of monitoring robot provisioning  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 10, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150910/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150910/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Properly display an error when setting a tag of greater than 128 characters.  API  Fixed an issue with monitoring email subscriber changes not taking immediate effect. Fix a regression in which the Account.privateSubnets and Account.publicSubnets properties were not able to be filtered. Performance/Endurance storage provisioning improvements Improved provisioning time of monitoring robots  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 02, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150902/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150902/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Correct Display Inconsistencies for Flexible Credit Participants  API  Improve performance of hardware and virtual guest callbacks Upgrades the interface with the APNIC registrar to support their new session based authentication system, allowing for proper modification of rwhois entires.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 29, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150829/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150829/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Fixes a bug preventing editing of storage groups for quotes and orders. Fixed input validation on forward zone creation to allow for long gTLDs  API  Improved punycode validation for domain names.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 8, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150826/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150826/</guid>
      <description> API  Prevents grouped network components from being disconnected Added a lastResponseDate to the ticket object. This lastResponseDate represents the last time a customer facing response was added to the ticket. This is exposed sldn.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 24, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150824/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150824/</guid>
      <description> Portal  Deleted virtual guests should no longer show up in the portal  API  Improve the current workflow for processing nimsoft robots on the landing hub. This should have a significant impact in terms of reducing landing hub related escalations and transaction failures.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: August 19, 2015</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150819/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2015/20150819/</guid>
      <description>Portal  Removed private IP address detection that checks whether or not the IP address starts with &amp;ldquo;10.&amp;rdquo;. This comes necessary now that we support Customer Defined Networks. Correctly identify if the primary ip address is in the private ip space, instead of relying on the &amp;ldquo;10.&amp;rdquo; prefix in the ip address. Updates the order review page to always show transfer/floor pricing. Resolve issues with discrepancy in mandatory fields in add portal user across portals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>