<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Release Notes on SoftLayer API Examples </title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/release-notes/</link>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2014, Enthusiastic Hugo User; all rights reserved.</rights>
    <updated>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180216/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improvement to verbiage shown for servers with active billing for an inactive package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GPU Flavor prices were not factoring the price of the GPU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the master user could set themselves as &amp;ldquo;VPN_ONLY&amp;rdquo; user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix Reloads being blocked when a user suppresses the email for RELOAD_COMPLETE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix Micron Hard Drive Storage Group Member&amp;rsquo;s Grow Flag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update automated messaging update on Data Transfer Request tickets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add dal10 to the list of data centers supporting security groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: February 7, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180207/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180207/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow customers to suppress order emails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;.. to change a user link&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;to edit a user&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exception message should mention &amp;lsquo;Access Denied. Only the Master user..&amp;rsquo; instead of &amp;lsquo;Account 1234 is authenticated by IBMid&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; when resetOpenIdConnectLink is called for subuser&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validator added for bare metal servers orders that use the userData field, the allowed length is 2000 characters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update getCreateObjectOptions to return Spot options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Child user is now unable to delete his/her own Phone Factor authentication using the APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bootMode property is added to the SoftLayer_Container_Product_Order_Virtual_Guest class to allow customers to specify the mode the VSI should be booted in. A bootMode property is also added to SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest_SupplementalCreateObjectOptions so that the boot mode can be specified during when calling SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest::createObject. The data will be verified and the customer informed if they have submitted an invalid boot mode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to getAllObjects on SoftLayer_Network_Storage_Allowed_Host using objectFilters and objectMask&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where fixed configuration preset orders are verified but the preset is not entirely available yet provides more information about why it is failing to verify the order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable the Security Group feature in Dal01, Lon06, and Sea01.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support new VSI type called Spot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the audit log functionality of security groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modified provisioning to use boot mode provided by customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When downgrading the CPU on a Guest with a Dedicated Host, the Guest Type is no longer overwritten as Public Guest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix Storage As A Service orders validation which was previously accepting orders that did not conform to product business rules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix bug that would delay the completion of an hourly volume reclaim process because it would create an unnecessary process instance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adds complex password support for EVault. New passwords will be 12 characters long and contain special characters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 22, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180122/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180122/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes bug when checking for available vGPU resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update favicon on IBM cloud template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an informative popup to properly display entire username when deleting or disabling a user with a long username&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoftLayer_Network_Storage::getAllowableDatacenters() performance improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a SUPPORTED_BOOT_MODE attribute to the SoftLayer_Virtual_Disk_Image_Attribute_Type class to hold what boot modes the image can support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update SLDN doc for Virtual_Guest.createObject to add Security Group parameters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Replace checking for parentId with isMasterUser flag for add/remove device access&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added quantity validation on StaaS orders. SoftLayer_Container_Product_Order_Network_Storage_AsAService can only be ordered one at a time. If quantity is greater than 1, an exception will now be thrown. Before the order was just placed as quantity 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the default SEV4 setting on all tickets created  and require employees to set the ticket severity on the first update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parent user who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the VPN_MANAGE permission should be able to disable or delete the child user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generic message is displayed when sub-user is trying to add External Binding for a child user. This has been changed to a message to indicate only the Master User can add external bindings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve sanity checks and error messages when a user&amp;rsquo;s email field is changed after sending an IBMid invitation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove weak SSL ciphers from LBaaS supported cipher list. Specifically

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DHE-RSA-AES256-GCM-SHA384&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DHE-RSA-AES256-SHA256&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DHE-RSA-AES128-GCM-SHA256&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DHE-RSA-AES128-SHA256&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes an issue where extraneous SoftLayer_Network_Storage::activeTransactions could be present on a volume which actually has no active transactions running.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block Live Migrations for GPU Guests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable Order Support for External Resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Insufficient Resources&amp;rdquo; error has been changed to &amp;ldquo;Insufficient Capacity&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 15, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180115/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;slcli&#34;&gt;SLCLI&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/releases/tag/v5.4.0&#34;&gt;https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/releases/tag/v5.4.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/compare/v5.3.2...v5.4.0&#34;&gt;https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/compare/v5.3.2...v5.4.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgraded Requests and Urllib3 library to latest. This allows the library to make use of connection retries, and connection pools. This should prevent the client from crashing if the API gives a connection reset / connection timeout error&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;reworked wait_for_ready function for virtual, and added to hardware managers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;fixed block/file iops in the &lt;code&gt;slcli block|file detail&lt;/code&gt; view&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Added sub items to &lt;code&gt;hw detail --price&lt;/code&gt;, removed reverse PTR entries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;added-to-cli&#34;&gt;Added to CLI&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://softlayer-python.readthedocs.io/en/latest/cli/ordering.html&#34;&gt;slcli order&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Example slcli order useagecontent/python/ordering_slcli.md&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;](&lt;a href=&#34;https://softlayer.github.io/python/ordering_slcli/&#34;&gt;https://softlayer.github.io/python/ordering_slcli/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;$ ./slcli order
Usage: slcli order [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]...

Options:
  -h, --help  Show this message and exit.

Commands:
  category-list      List the categories of a package.
  item-list          List package items used for ordering.
  package-list       List packages that can be ordered via the...
  package-locations  List Datacenters a package can be ordered in.
  place              Place or verify an order.
  preset-list        List package presets.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: January 3, 2018</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2018/20180103/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Replace &amp;ldquo;formerly IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;formerly SoftLayer&amp;rdquo; in all affected templates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Autoscale: Prevent Multiple Scale Actions per Policy. &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/39696067/invalid-guest-template-for-autoscale-in-sl&#34;&gt;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/39696067/invalid-guest-template-for-autoscale-in-sl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only block BYOL sharing and making it public if the software description is a licensed product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adds support for Spot instances to simple VSI ordering. spotGuestFlag would be used to indicate in a createObject() parameter block if the order is for a Spot Instance. &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/createObject&#34;&gt;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Virtual_Guest/createObject&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added an API to tell if an account is eligible to link with PaaS. &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Account/isEligibleToLinkWithPaas&#34;&gt;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Account/isEligibleToLinkWithPaas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This fixes a problem where volumes could be end up with lesser than assigned quota size.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed deprecated abuse field from RIPE registration person details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 11, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171206/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171206/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adds warning messages to that will pop to alert EU only processing users that they are selecting a data center or package that it not EU compliant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This change will add a checkbox on the WWW order from checkout page that allows customers to opt-in to EU localized support. For a customer that opts-in, any servers they have in an EU datacenter will only be serviced by technicians also in the EU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removes the VSI section from the Server Listings page (of the Control Portal).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update the &amp;ldquo;refreshAuthentication&amp;rdquo; method to accept the POST request with the basic authentication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added EU compliant field to datacenters, ORM flag and enable/disable methods for EU Support on the account. Currently in the EU AMS01, AMS03, FRA02, LON02, MIL01, OSL01, PAR01&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An exception will be thrown if a customer tries to place a BYOL order for Windows on that is not for a dedicated host instance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with removeHardwareAccess not properly removing a user if their premission had been grandted with grantHardwareAccess(id=0)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding EU compliance support to Ticket system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed all code referencing NETWORK_MESSAGE_QUEUE. The Message Queue product is now EOL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made changes so that the order indexes and names/slots of the hard-drives being swapped in get the same order indexes and names of the swapped-out hard drives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent accounts with BAP tier 1 support from enrolling in EU support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the use of PPTP VPN from EU flagged accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prevent setting EU security level for accounts with PPTP usage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enable Security Groups in the AMS01, SEO01, SJC01 and SJC03 data centers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: December 04, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171204/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix issue where LVM was set on storage groups erroneously when editing a configuration on the order form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add a new order approval e-mail notification template for SAP Certified servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added account validation support for combining unicode characters, such as diacritical arabic characters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new check to prevent multiple partitions being set with grow flag.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow the customers who does not have USER_MANAGE permission to see their own login attempts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only master user, parent user or user itself can add API key.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase the permission action description column size to 256&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adds support for upgrading existing File and Block storage volumes. Volumes&amp;rsquo; size can now be increased, and volumes&amp;rsquo; IOPS can now be increased and decreased. Certain limits do apply, see Sales and Support for details. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/softlayer/softlayer-python/releases/tag/v5.3.1&#34;&gt;SLCLI version 3.0.1&lt;/a&gt; supports this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not require customers to explicitly state the billing type (hourly/monthly) when upgrading a volume, as that can be inferred from the volume billing records&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed generic internal error message during an OS reload where the image template is missing to throw correct message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed &amp;ldquo;account.companyName&amp;rdquo; mask from the hardware search, specifically only for the scenario where the user is attempting to export a CSV / excel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scrub Security answers for users based on security level of employee and account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed the issue that getLoadBalancerStatistics API not collecting stats from Retired appliances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cancel image store action jobs when a provision is cancelled&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171127/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171127/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more validation around partition sizeing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed the wording on raid alert tickets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue reclaiming Virtual Servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes bug when trying to find reverse DNS records.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with account link invitations not getting a proper activation url&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug preventing some provisioning transactions from completing automatically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171115/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171115/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where editing virtual dedicated instance orders would display an error message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reworded the error message when trying to un-suspend an autoscaling group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more validation to ordering Direct Link products through the SLAPI to mirror validation done by the portal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adds functionality to allow upgrade for Fortigate firewall appliances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where disk groups would be improperly partitioned when a HOT_SPARE volume was present&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allowed various unicode hyphens through account validation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 20, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171120/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enforce the same set of input requirements for &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_User_Customer/createObject&#34;&gt;SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject&lt;/a&gt; in a linked account, as for a non-linked account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed both a CIDR and IP address to be specified together in the remoteIp field of a security group rule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: November 13, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171113/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where a dedicated VSI would get marked as public if the order was edited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where editing a Bare Metal Server order would make the order invalid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enforce the same set of input requirements for &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_User_Customer/createObject&#34;&gt;SoftLayer_User_Customer::CreateObject&lt;/a&gt; in a linked account, as for a non-linked account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with cloud-init provisioning not configuring the gateway properly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue preventing local disk -&amp;gt; San disk migration from upgrading properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed both a CIDR and IP address to be specified together in the remoteIp field of a security group rule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171025/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added 2 links to the order approval email when ordering MDMS. The links will guide the customers to the User Guide and device Checklist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed the warning on the order forms that 2nd disk is required for Balanced local flavor VSIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a user is created with double quotes in email address from API, Error message pointed to a problem with username. This has been fixed to show the correct error message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added Saudi Arabia, United Arab Emirates to the list of countries that accept VAT ID.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171012/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an error that was being displayed when an end user clicks on “Reconfigure System Configuration” link on complete order page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed the ability to edit or view a users profile via the API if the users status is set to &lt;code&gt;cancel_pending&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: October 05, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20171005/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/blogs/bluemix/2017/09/ibm-cloud-bluemix-load-balancer/&#34;&gt;IBM Bluemix Load Balancers&lt;/a&gt; are now live in the customer portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance and Endurance Block volumes can no longer have their LUN Id changed unless all host authorizations are first removed. This is to ensure synchronization between the customer portal and the storage systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more logic when auto-scaling Virtual Guests. The new logic checks the dates in the logs first and makes sure there are no other provisions or reclaims within the cooldown period of time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Virtual Guests being deployed from Image templates were set to Skip OS updates during provisioning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release notes: September 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170927/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/release_notes/2017/20170927/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;portal&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://console.bluemix.net/docs/infrastructure/security-groups/sg_overview.html#about-security-groups&#34;&gt;Security Groups&lt;/a&gt; are now live in the customer portal at &lt;a href=&#34;https://control.softlayer.com/security/securitygroups&#34;&gt;https://control.softlayer.com/security/securitygroups&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pushed some code to tidy up the Virtual Guest Family size order forms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;api&#34;&gt;API&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Account/enableEuLocalizedProcessing&#34;&gt;enableEuLocalizedProcessing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Account/disableEuLocalizedProcessing&#34;&gt;disableEuLocalizedProcessing&lt;/a&gt; methods for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sldn.softlayer.com/reference/services/SoftLayer_Account&#34;&gt;SoftLayer_Account&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;backend&#34;&gt;Backend&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>