<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>drillDownAttack</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/drillDownAttack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/drillDownAttack/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting::drillDownAttack Overview This method, when given an attack signature ID (available in the return values of getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet and getSubnetReportForEntireAccount) and an IP Address and subnet mask, returns all attacks for that subnet in the specified time frame and direction. Once the results have been filtered, additional data is available, including starting and ending times for the attack, originating IP address and port, and destination IP address and port.
CVE and Bugtraq information is not available at this level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getMainStatistics</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getMainStatistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getMainStatistics/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting::getMainStatistics Overview This method returns the attack statistics for the current user&amp;rsquo;s account and for the entire SoftLayer network. These attacks are recorded and monitored at the entry point to the network, and represent attacks in both directions.
The data returned is: * Top attacks (by attack name) on datacenter Dal01 in the last hour (and last 24 hours) * Top attacks (by attack name) on IPs you own in the last hour (and last 24 hours) * Top IPs attacking IPs you own in the last hour (and last 24 hours) Each one of these lists can contain any number of items, the default is 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting::getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet Overview This method expands on the getSubnetReportForEntireAccount method by offering the ability to filter by subnet or IP address. This method is identical to getSubnetReportForEntireAccount, but allows filtering by subnet. Like in the getSubnetReportForEntireAccount method, CVE and BugTraq IDs are provided, if available.
This method should be called once an attack has been identified using getSubnetReportForEntireAccount (in which case &amp;ldquo;All Subnets&amp;rdquo; is the subnet) or getReportForIpAddressOrSubnet.
Parameters    Name Type Description     IpAddress string the IP address you wish to search on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getSubnetReportForEntireAccount</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getSubnetReportForEntireAccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/services/SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting/getSubnetReportForEntireAccount/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer_Network_TippingPointReporting::getSubnetReportForEntireAccount Overview This method returns specific attacks by name for all subnets on the current user&amp;rsquo;s account.
The data returned is stored in SoftLayer_Container_Network_IntrusionProtection_SubnetReport objects, with the &amp;ldquo;subnet&amp;rdquo; value set to &amp;ldquo;All Subnets&amp;rdquo;
The data is separated into &amp;ldquo;Inbound&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Outbound&amp;rdquo; traffic. A significant amount of outbound attack traffic could indicate that your servers have been compromised.
The data returned includes Attack Count, attack name, extended attack description, and IDs that correspond with the BugTraq or CVE databases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>