<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>resultlimit on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/resultlimit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in resultlimit on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/resultlimit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Event Logs</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/go/event_log.go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/go/event_log.go/</guid>
      <description>This example deals with a few ways of pulling data from SoftLayer_Event_Log. There can be quite a few Logs here, therefore it is recommended to use a filter like in getRecentLogs to limit how far back your search for Events, otherwise you will be paging through Events for a long time. Moreover, this example uses the maxNumberOfEvents value to limit the number of event logs that will be retrieved.&#xA;package main import ( &amp;#34;encoding/json&amp;#34; &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; &amp;#34;github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Event Logs</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/java/EventLogs.java/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/java/EventLogs.java/</guid>
      <description>Event Log This example deals with a few ways of pulling data from SoftLayer_Event_Log. Also, uses the latest version of the SoftLayer API Client for Java (v0.3.2 at the time of publishing this example), which does not support object filters available in the SoftLayer API, so programmatic filters are used instead.&#xA;import com.google.gson.Gson; import com.google.gson.GsonBuilder; import com.softlayer.api.ApiClient; import com.softlayer.api.RestApiClient; import com.softlayer.api.ResultLimit; import com.softlayer.api.service.event.Log; import java.time.LocalDate; import java.util.ArrayList; import java.util.List; import java.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Event Logs</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/events_logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/events_logs/</guid>
      <description>Event Log This example deals with a few ways of pulling data from SoftLayer_Event_Log. There can be quite a few Logs here, so using a filter it recommends like in the Get Recent Events to limit how far back your search for Events, otherwise you will be paging through Events for a long time.&#xA;Get All Events To get all Events logs, We use SoftLayer_Event_Log::getAllObjects(), in this case just the first 50 events by using pagination as resultLimit=0,50, See Using Result Limits in the SoftLayer API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Logs</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/event_log/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/event_log/</guid>
      <description>This example deals with a few ways of pulling data from SoftLayer_Event_Log. There can ben quite a few Logs here, so I recommend using a filter like in the recentLogs function to limit how far back you search for Events, otherwise you will be paging through Events for a long time.&#xA;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; @author Christopher Gallo &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; import datetime import SoftLayer class example(): def __init__(self): self.client = SoftLayer.Client() debugger = SoftLayer.DebugTransport(self.client.transport) self.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tickets</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/tickets/</guid>
      <description>Tickets Tickets are how SoftLayer and you communicate and resolve problems. They can be about anything from general questions, requests for upgrades, monitoring alerts, or anything else that might come up.&#xA;Viewing Tickets To start off, lets see how to go about getting tickets that already exist on our account. There are a variety of helper functions on the SoftLayer_Account service that deal with tickets, and they all work basically the same way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/rest/events/</guid>
      <description>Events SoftLayer_Notification_Occurrence_Events at SoftLayer are how we communicate maintenance, outages, and other disruptive events to customers. In the control portal, you can find these at https://control.softlayer.com/event/announcement&#xA;Get All Events SoftLayer_Notification_Occurrence_Event::getAllObjects()&#xA;curl -u $SL_USER:$SL_APIKEY &amp;#34;https://api.softlayer.com/rest/v3.1/SoftLayer_Notification_Occurrence_Event/getAllObjects.json The output will look something like this, but will have every event that has ever been reported on your account. For brevity I have only included 1 Event&#xA;[ { &amp;#34;endDate&amp;#34;: null, &amp;#34;id&amp;#34;: 2584, &amp;#34;lastImpactedUserCount&amp;#34;: 11232, &amp;#34;modifyDate&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;2016-06-13T08:27:20-06:00&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;recoveryTime&amp;#34;: null, &amp;#34;startDate&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;2014-03-31T00:35:00-06:00&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;statusCode&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;keyName&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;COMPLETED&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Completed&amp;#34; }, &amp;#34;subject&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;IPv6 Sessions Down on FCR02.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provision Times</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/provisionTimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/python/provisionTimes/</guid>
      <description>Goes through orders and prints out each transaction that provisioned a server or virtual server. Calculates provision time from the time the order was placed, till the time the transaction went to COMPLETE.&#xA;Order: 15866609 - 2017-06-09T10:42:04-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time sgtest.cdetest.info, COMPLETE, 57090965, 383.0 Order: 15861187 - 2017-06-09T09:07:49-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time jumpbox.cdetest.info, COMPLETE, 57080823, 774.0 Order: 15860993 - 2017-06-09T08:53:22-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time Order: 15853891 - 2017-06-09T04:47:32-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time d1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/rest/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides a RESTful API in addition to RPC-style API services. Use the REST API in cases where your programming language may not have good SOAP or XML-RPC support but can perform simple HTTP protocol actions and can interpret XML or JSON data.&#xA;REST URLs REST API URLs are structured to easily traverse SoftLayer&amp;rsquo;s object hierarchy. A basic REST request is structured as follows:&#xA;curl -u [username]:[apiKey] -d &amp;#39;{&amp;#34;parameters&amp;#34;: [&amp;#34;first&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;second&amp;#34;]}&amp;#39; https://api.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Result Limits in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>Many of the methods in the SoftLayer API return arrays of data types. In these cases it may be useful to limit the number of results that the API retrieves from your method call. Fortunately SoftLayer provides an easy way to accomplish this via a method analogous to the SQL LIMIT statement that you can apply in the header of your method calls. Result limits are optional for all method calls, and a method&amp;rsquo;s manual page states whether or not it can use a result limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XML-RPC</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/xml-rpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/xml-rpc/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides an XML-RPC interface in addition to SOAP and REST. The XML-RPC API is built to mimic the SOAP interface. We recommend using the XML-RPC API when your chosen language doesn&amp;rsquo;t have proper SOAP support.&#xA;Endpoint URLs The SoftLayer XML-RPC API has one endpoint per available API service. Each endpoint has a unique URL containing the service name of the API services that it calls. For example: https://api.softlayer.com/xmlrpc/v3/&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt; or http://api.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
