<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resultlimit on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/tags/resultlimit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resultlimit on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/tags/resultlimit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision Times</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/python/provisionTimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/python/provisionTimes/</guid>
      <description>Goes through orders and prints out each transaction that provisioned a server or virtual server. Calculates provision time from the time the order was placed, till the time the transaction went to COMPLETE.
Order: 15866609 - 2017-06-09T10:42:04-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time sgtest.cdetest.info, COMPLETE, 57090965, 383.0 Order: 15861187 - 2017-06-09T09:07:49-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time jumpbox.cdetest.info, COMPLETE, 57080823, 774.0 Order: 15860993 - 2017-06-09T08:53:22-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time Order: 15853891 - 2017-06-09T04:47:32-06:00 FQDN, Status, transaction id, elapsed time d1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Result Limits in the SoftLayer API</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/using-result-limits-softlayer-api/</guid>
      <description>toc_collapse=0;Table of contents&amp;nbsp;  Structure Creating a Result Limit    Many of the methods in the SoftLayer API return arrays of data types. In these cases it may be useful to limit the number of results that the API retrieves from your method call. Fortunately SoftLayer provides an easy way to accomplish this via a method analogous to the SQL LIMIT statement that you can apply in the header of your method calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML-RPC</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/article/xml-rpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/article/xml-rpc/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer provides an XML-RPC interface in addition to [[SOAP]] and [[REST]]. The XML-RPC API is built to mimic the SOAP interface. We recommend using the XML-RPC API when your chosen language doesn&amp;rsquo;t have proper SOAP support.
Endpoint URLs The SoftLayer XML-RPC API has one endpoint per available API service. Each endpoint has a unique URL containing the service name of the API services that it calls. For example: https://api.softlayer.com/xmlrpc/v3/&amp;lt;serviceName&amp;gt; or http://api.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>