<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sldn.softlayer.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The SoftLayer Python Library</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/python/</guid>
      <description>The Basics softlayer-python project homepage. For source code and submitting issues. Documentation Covers both the SLCLI and softlayer-python library. PyPi project For latest information about the softlayer-python package, which is kept updated on PyPi. Python 2.7 Support As of version 5.8.0 SoftLayer-Python will no longer support python2.7, which is End Of Life as of 2020 . If you cannot install python 3.6+ for some reason, you will need to use a version of softlayer-python &amp;lt;= 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Account Billing Detail</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/single-account-billing-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/single-account-billing-detail/</guid>
      <description>Account Level Billing This tutorial walks you through accessing detailed billing data for a single specified account using a specified time and date range.&#xA;Objectives Understand how to use multiple API services and methods to access detailed billing data for a specified account using a specified time and date range. Services used This tutorial uses the following technologies:&#xA;SoftLayer Python Library Billing_Invoice Service Billing_Invoice_Item Service Billing_item Service Architecture This tutorial will leverage account Invoice and Billing Item API&amp;rsquo;s to collect and display detailed billing detail for a specified time and date range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Block Storage</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/AutomatingStorage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/AutomatingStorage/</guid>
      <description>The Process Order a VSI with a postInstall script Order a storage volume Update the metadata of the VSI to include the needed information to mount the storage volume postInstall script gets metadata from the metadata service, and mounts the volume Ordering Code This script will order a VSI, based on a configuration in the file, then order some storage, authorize storage to the new VSI, and set the VSI&amp;rsquo;s metadata with the needed information for it to be mounted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-Organization Billing Detail</title>
      <link>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/sub-org-billing-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sldn.softlayer.com/article/sub-org-billing-detail/</guid>
      <description>Sub-org Billing Detail This tutorial walks you through accessing the steps required to access detailed billing data across sub-organization accounts using a specified date and time range.&#xA;Objectives Understand how to use multiple API services and methods to access detailed billing data for all sub organization accounts for a specified time and date range.&#xA;Services used This tutorial uses the following technologies:&#xA;SoftLayer Python Library Account Service Billing_Invoice Service Billing_Invoice_Item Service Billing_item Service Architecture Accounts (refered to in this document as a sub account) can be owned by a Brand Account, which is the top level account type for an organization which can enable sub-organizational level billing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
