<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction on SoftLayer API</title>
    <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction on SoftLayer API</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://softlayer.github.io/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction</title>
      <link>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://softlayer.github.io/reference/datatypes/SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction/</guid>
      <description>SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction Service Datatype   Description The SoftLayer_Network_Subnet_Swip_Transaction data type contains basic information tracked at SoftLayer to allow automation of Swip creation, update, and removal requests. A specific transaction is attached to an accountId and a subnetId. This also contains a &amp;ldquo;Status Name&amp;rdquo; which tells the customer what the transaction is doing:
 REQUEST QUEUED: Request is queued up to be sent to ARIN REQUEST SENT: The email request has been sent to ARIN REQUEST CONFIRMED: ARIN has confirmed that the request is good, and should be available in 24 hours OK: The subnet has been checked with WHOIS and it the SWIP transaction has completed correctly REMOVE QUEUED: A subnet is queued to be removed from ARIN&amp;rsquo;s systems REMOVE SENT: The removal email request has been sent to ARIN REMOVE CONFIRMED: ARIN has confirmed that the removal request is good, and the subnet should be clear in WHOIS in 24 hours DELETED: This specific SWIP Transaction has been removed from ARIN and is no longer in effect SOFTLAYER MANUALLY PROCESSING: Sometimes a request doesn&amp;rsquo;t go through correctly and has to be manually processed by SoftLayer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>